Hey, Nana... Do you remember the first time we met?
I've always been a person who believes in fate,
so I think that fate has a hand in everything.
It's all right if that makes you laugh at me.
God, Jesus, Evil Demon Lord...
Shoji
The sakura flower is blooming
Great!
E-Excuse me. That...
Nana-chan, what are you yelling about?
Ah. You want to rent a movie?
Please ask this guy.
Nana-chan?
As of right now, I'm resigning.
Resigning?!
Thanks for taking care of me this past year.
Please tell the store manager, too.
But also be sure to tell him I want my last paycheck deposited into my bank account.
Huh?
Well, see you and take care!
Have a good day!
Nana-chan!
Spring! Spring has finally come;
Great!
the spring I've been waiting for.
I managed to get into
the college I wanted,
yeah!~~     ^o^
Call me!
I really want to see you as soon as possible, Shoji!
When I was darkness at that time.
With trembling lips in a corner of my room, I cry.
furueteru kuchibiru heya no katasumi de I cry
The more I struggle, the more this wound pierces me.
mogakeba mogaku hodo tsukisasaru kono kizu
A broken promise hurts me.
yaburareta yakusoku hurt me
Nobody can save me.
There’s only one God.
kamisama hitotsu dake
My love seems to stop and split me.
tomete saku you na my love
I need your love. I'm a broken rose.
The scattering sadness, your song,
maichiru kanashimi your song
my lonely life that has no whereabouts.
ibasho nai kodoku na my life
I need your love. I'm a broken rose.
Oh, baby, help me from frozen pain.
With your smile, your eyes, and sing me, just for me.
I wanna need your love.
I'm a broken rose.
Well,
congrats, Shoji, for getting into college!
Cheers!
But I'm proud of you!
The effort this "loser" put in actually paid off.
Don't call me a "loser"!
I'm happy for you, too. I thought you'd fail again.
See?
What do you mean, Sato Kouichi?
Hello? Nana?
What if it's not her?
Did you get my message?
No, no. Thank you.
This proves that he isn't cheating on her.
Haven't I already told you? He could never cheat on her.
Yeah, I'm with Kyosuke and Junko.
We're having a drink at Jackson's.
Yeah, yeah. I've mentioned it before.
It's the bar we always go to.
How about you? What are you doing?
Packing.
Nana said she's coming to Tokyo tonight.
What?
To Mom and Dad
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
To Mom and Dad
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
Take care,
NANA
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
Take care,
NANA
I need a one-way ticket to Tokyo.
Since it's snowing today, the schedule is messed up.
That's fine, as long as I get there.
I'll come and pick you up,
when are you going to arrive?
Which train are you on?
Message me back, I'll wait for
you in the station!!
I'm so nice. -Shoji
I'll come and pick you up,
when are you going to arrive?
Which train are you on?
Message me back, I'll wait for
you in the station!!
I'm so nice. -Shoji
I'll come and pick you up,
when are you going to arrive?
Which train are you on?
Message me back, I'll wait for
you in the station!!
I'm so nice. -Shoji
I'll come and pick you up,
when are you going to arrive?
Which train are you on?
Message me back, I'll wait for
you in the station!!
I'm so nice. -Shoji
Shoji!
Thank you for taking this train.
Due to the weather, our departure will be delayed by forty minutes.
Ah, this many people?
I was planning to find a seat soon and reply to Shoji.
We're sorry for the inconvenience.
Excuse me...
Excuse me. I'm sor—!
What... Why did the train stop so suddenly?
An accident?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Sorry.
I'm the one who should be apologizing.
You got hit by this, right?
That's all right.
Excuse me... Actually... Is anyone sitting there?
Please go ahead.
What a beautiful person...
Or would "handsome" be the better word?
She gives off such a different aura than a normal person.
Very skinny, with a cute, small face... Is she an actress?
What long eyelashes!
That's so admirable. That heavy make-up really suits her.
Indeed, no matter what she does, a beautiful girl is beautiful.
Ah, a Vivienne ring!
And it even says the year it was made!
She's looking more and more handsome to me.
Sorry. Does it disturb you if I smoke?
Ah, no, not at all. Don't worry.
It's not moving.
Huh?
The train. It hasn't been moving.
Ah, really?
What should I do? I'm in a hurry.
Oh, that's troublesome.
No, that's fine...
I'll send a text.
All right. Done.
You're really fast!
I guess I'm not surprised.
High school girls are pretty good at that nowadays.
I'm already twenty years old!
Sorry. We're about the same age.
Ah, she looks so cute when she smiles.
Huh? The same age? No way! You're lying!
Well, you said "High school girls,"
so that makes me think you're not so young.
Ah, I was...
I judged someone by appearances again.
Attention all customers:
Due to the heavy snow, this train will be travelling at a slow pace.
We are sorry to inconvenience our dear customers.
Oh, no...
At this rate, when will I get to Tokyo?
What are you going to do in Tokyo?
It's not really anything big. I'm just moving.
I want to look for a job there.
Oh, so we're the same.
Huh? The same?
Yeah.
Ah, I assumed you were from Tokyo
and had just finished your nationwide tour.
"Tour"?
Like a concert or something,
'cause you brought your guitar with you.
I thought you were a professional musician.
Oh.
So, have you ever been in a band?
I used to be in one back in my home town.
Wow, that's awesome.
Where're you from?
Ah, a text... No, it's a phone call.
Hello, hello? This is Nana speaking.
Ah, Shoji? Hm, yeah. The train isn't moving.
I'm not sure when I'll get there.
Eh? Is that going to be okay?
'Cause I might get there at midnight.
Are you sure it's okay?
Yeah, thank you.
I'll call you when I'm about to arrive, then.
Yeah, see you.
Your boyfriend's from Tokyo?
What a lovey-dovey couple.
I see. You're going to Tokyo to be with him.
No!
Well, actually, yes...
Which is it?
He's not really from Tokyo...
He actually went to school with me in my home town.
But in order to get into Tokyo's art college,
he moved there last year.
Why didn't you go with him?
I told him I wanted to go with him,
but Shoji, my boyfriend, told me not to.
Why?
He said I have neither a goal nor money,
and that travelling just for him would be pointless.
I see.
So I blubbered and stayed in my own town,
until I saved enough money to go to Tokyo.
We promised each other that once he got into college,
I would go to Tokyo.
Once I'm there, he won’t have any excuse to ask me to go back. I'll work hard...
Ah, why am I telling this to a person I just met today?
It's fine, even though we've just met.
Say some more, 'cause we still have a lot of time.
Really? I guess you're right.
Well, to kill some time, you just listen to me, then!
Actually, I wanted to share this with all the others really badly.
Shoji is actually very gentle,
very dependable, and very handsome!
He can sound like an idiot sometimes, though.
You're saying he's like an idiot?
Hey, hey, do you want some beer?
Sure, sure.
Two cans of beer, please!
Well, let's make a toast!
To what?
Well...
For Shoji getting into the college of his choice.
No, that's none of my business.
Then at least for the memories we'll have of this meeting!
Ah, that's a good idea.
Same age, on the same train, going to Tokyo...
This is a rare coincidence.
And there's one more thing.
My name is Nana, too.
Nana-chan.
Do you remember the first time we met?
I didn't know when it started snowing.
The train stopped and started.
It took us about five hours to get to Tokyo,
but I wasn't lonely at all.
I was telling you my stories the entire time.
I didn't ask you anything at all.
It was all right, because I already knew, Nana.
You would've avoided answering any questions I asked.
Nana!
Shoji!
Why are you crying?
You're laughing at me! That's so mean!
It must've been hard, being stuck on a train for five hours.
Yeah...
But... Ah?
What's wrong?
I became good friends with the girl who sat next to me.
I see.
But she's disappeared... I'm sure we got off at the same time.
Maybe she's gone...
I really should have asked for her number.
What? So that means you guys aren't friends at all, right?
Don't cry. Kyosuke and Junko are down there, too.
Huh?
Jun-chan!
It isn't snowing in Tokyo at all!
Hey, what are you guys going to do?
How about we all have a drink together?
But I'm kind of tired.
It's already one o'clock in the morning.
In that case, we'll just go home today.
Sorry. I made you come this far to pick me up.
Don't worry about it.
We'll see each other all the time now.
Let's have all have a drink together next time.
Ah, this feels good.
With the four of us together,
it feels like we're back at art school again.
Instead of just feeling nostalgic,
I felt more relieved than anything.
This counts as my "second family", right?
I've finally arrived in Tokyo, where everyone else is.
Well, see you all later.
Good night.
What are you doing? Nana, let's go.
Uh? Okay.
Endo Shoji
Wait...
Is it a good idea to barge in like this?
Please come in.
Since your arrival was so sudden,
I didn't even have time to clean up the place.
Sorry.
Huh?
This is all so sudden.
You must be a bit flustered, right?
I was thinking of living with Jun-chan
before finding a place for myself.
But I don't think you can now.
They're living together.
What?
I didn't know that! Jun-chan never mentioned a word of that to me!
When did this happen?
It's hard to say when.
Kyosuke just moved into Jun-chan's place all of a sudden.
I see... I see...
Geez. You didn't even take off your shoes,
Tokyo isn't a foreign country.
Those two do look like an old couple...
Old couple?!
But I didn't expect their relationship to move so fast.
This is so wonderful!
What?
You're like a pervert, stripping me this quickly.
Me and Shoji... Will we become like that in the future?
I really want to make up for all of the time we've been apart.
Such happiness...
I'll be back at 6,
take care when you're out.
This is bad!
I was thinking of getting up early to cook breakfast for him.
I must improve my reputation before Shoji comes back.
I feel just like his wife doing things like this!
If I can do all of these things for him and make everything all perfect,
I don't know if I would even be able to express my happiness!
How about I just live here like this?
Shoji will be very relaxed, right?
Welcome home!
I-I'm home.
It tastes better than I thought it would.
What do you mean,
"better than you thought it would"?
Well, because you're not good at cooking.
Th-That's not true.
I was kidding, kidding. It really is delicious.
You're quite good.
It took me three hours to cook.
Ah, right. How was the realtor?
Did they help you find any places?
Well, I was really busy today, so I didn't go.
Why? Ah, I see. You went to look for a job?
How's that going?
Yeah, if I don't find a job, I'll...
Don't tell me you slept in all day...
That's not it! I did the laundry and cleaned the apartment! I've had a very long day!
What are you talking about?
Don't tell me that's why you came here.
Didn't you promise me you'd come to Tokyo,
look for a job, and try to learn to be independent?
Don't give me "What are you talking about"?
I did all of this for you!
Ah... I lost my temper at him.
I feel so overbearing.
I'm full.
I'll clean it up.
That's fine.
I can do it.
I really messed up.
I'm going to take a bath.
I can't keep this up.
Shoji's starting to hate me.
Wha...?
What should I do?
What should I do to make him always, always love me?
Nana,
let's take a bath together.
No way!
What the hell? You were playing hard-to-get?
But I was really embarrassed!
Why?
Why did I...
It's because you and Kyosuke have lived together like hermits for so long that you're used to each other.
"Lived together like hermits"?
The bathroom is so small and bright.
It's like... he'll see every part of me.
I can't do that!
You're too loud.
Anyway!
Maybe I'm just not good at living with a man.
My relationship with Shoji's been long-distance right from the start.
So we're not really used to each other,
and I'm nervous when we're alone.
What are you talking about?
When I saw you two hanging out at home,
you were never nervous.
It's different now that we're dating!
I don't want Shoji to see anything bad about me!
I think it's too late for that.
Hey, I'm going to the realtor in front of the train station.
Do you want to go with me?
No, I'm going to work this afternoon.
No way! I'm nervous, Jun-chan.
Don't act so immature!
From now on, you have to live by yourself,
so you need to be independent.
Yeah,
even though I can't live together with Shoji,
I can't live by myself, either.
Andou Realty
There aren't any good houses with a monthly rate lower than fifty thousand yen.
I can pay a little more if I try.
But can't you lower the deposit and gift fees?
Hm... In that case, would an old apartment be fine with you?
No deposit or gift fees?
It looks really big, but it's very cheap.
Can I buy a bed and put it in there?
Do you want to take a look?
Yeah!
It's hard to find a good house like this nowadays.
It's that red brick building over there.
That mansion must've been built before I was born.
It must be really old.
It looked like it had been influenced by the Western style.
And suddenly, I fell in love with it.
Even though it's seven stories high,
it doesn't have an elevator. I didn't like that very much.
But for me, a girl who's lived in the countryside all this time, when I saw the trees and the river...
Being surrounded by that beauty really attracted me.
How about it? Do you like it?
The view's not half bad, right?
It's hard to find a place like this.
You're very lucky.
Hey Nana,
when we walked along the river...
and looked at the light's reflection on the water...
Please let me hear the melody you sang one more time.
I reached into the sky
My love wouldn't reach you.
Omoi wa todokanakute
The multi-colored balloons...
Chiisaku sora ni kieta
disappeared into the sky, growing smaller and smaller.
Irotoridori no fuusen
I'm alone.
I had no destination,
Ikisaki no nai watashi no te wo
but you gently held my hand.
Sotto tsunaide kureta
Starless night; I won’t look back on the shadow of my past.
Starless night kako no kage furi kaeranai
I want to feel your warmth.
Kanjitai anata no nukumori
Tears are falling down; even when I'm lost,
Tears are falling down mayotte mo hanashi wa shinai
I won't let go of your hand.
Tsunaida anata no te wo