Hey, Nana...
Do you remember the first time we met?
I've always been a person who believes in fate,
so I think that fate has a hand in everything.
It's all right if that makes you laugh at me.
When I was darkness at that time.
With trembling lips in a corner of my room, I cry.
furueteru kuchibiru heya no katasumi de I cry
The more I struggle, the more this wound pierces me.
mogakeba mogaku hodo tsukisasaru kono kizu
A broken promise hurts me.
yaburareta yakusoku hurt me
Nobody can save me.
There’s only one God.
kamisama hitotsu dake
My love seems to stop and split me.
tomete saku you na my love
I need your love. I'm a broken rose.
The scattering sadness, your song,
maichiru kanashimi your song
my lonely life that has no whereabouts.
ibasho nai kodoku na my life
I need your love. I'm a broken rose.
Oh, baby, help me from frozen pain.
With your smile, your eyes, and sing me, just for me.
I wanna need your love.
I'm a broken rose.
God, Jesus, Great Evil Lord...
Shoji
The sakura flower is blooming
Great!
E-Excuse me. That...
Nana-chan, what are you yelling about?
I managed to get into
the college I wanted,
yeah!~~     ^o^
Call me!
You're supposed to be working!
Spring! Spring has finally come;
the spring I've been waiting for.
Looking back on that time,
I think I was about ready to run away from home.
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
To Mom and Dad
However, my family wasn't surprised.
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
To Mom and Dad
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
To Mom and Dad
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
To Mom and Dad
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
To Mom and Dad
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
To Mom and Dad
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
I'll come back very often.
Please say hi to Aunie and Nami.
To Mom and Dad
I finally decided to go to Tokyo!
I'll contact you all once I'm settled down there.
Don't forget to deliver the boxes to me, okay?
I'll buy new furniture in Tokyo,
so just leave things the way they are.
Take care,
NANA
I have an older sister and a younger sister.
Both are two years apart from me.
Normally, my family's home is a very clamorous place.
Considering how I was back then,
whenever I woke up, I wanted to go to Tokyo, wanted to live there.
I only had one thing on my mind.
Maybe my parents thought I wanted to leave them,
and it would be quieter if a noisy daughter left.
Leaving the warmth of my family behind,
feeling sorrow from leaving the town I had lived in for twenty years...
Back then, I didn't have any of those thoughts at all.
Anyway, as soon as I got to Tokyo,
I'd be very, very happy.
The joy I was anticipating filled my heart.
I'll come and pick you up,
when are you going to arrive?
Which train are you on?
Message me back, I'll wait for
you in the station!!
I'm so nice. -Shoji
I'll come and pick you up,
when are you going to arrive?
Which train are you on?
Message me back, I'll wait for
you in the station!!
I'm so nice. -Shoji
I'll come and pick you up,
when are you going to arrive?
Which train are you on?
Message me back, I'll wait for
you in the station!!
I'm so nice. -Shoji
I'll come and pick you up,
when are you going to arrive?
Which train are you on?
Message me back, I'll wait for
you in the station!!
I'm so nice. -Shoji
From that point on, I'd sleep under the Tokyo sky and see my Shoji all the time!
Platform 7
No more need for phone calls or text messages.
We'd be able to talk to each other as long as we want!
Thank you for taking this train.
Due to the weather, our departure will be delayed by forty minutes.
Ah, this many people?
I was planning to find a seat soon and reply to Shoji.
We're sorry for the inconvenience.
Excuse me...
Excuse me, I'm sor—!
What... Why did the train stop so suddenly?
An accident?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Sorry.
I'm the one who should be apologizing.
You got hit by this, right?
That's all right.
Excuse me... Actually... Is anyone sitting there?
Please go ahead.
What a beautiful person...
Or would "handsome" be the better word?
She gives off such a different aura than a normal person.
Very skinny, with a cute, small face... Is she an actress?
What long eyelashes!
That's so admirable. That heavy make-up really suits her.
Indeed, no matter what she does, a beautiful girl is beautiful.
Ah, a Vivienne ring!
And it even says the year it was made!
She's looking more and more handsome to me.
Sorry. Does it disturb you if I smoke?
Ah, no, not at all. Don't worry.
It's not moving.
Huh?
The train. It hasn't been moving.
Ah, really? What should I do? I'm in a hurry.
Oh, that's troublesome.
No, it'll be fine...
I'll send a text.
All right. Done.
You're really fast!
I guess I'm not surprised.
High school girls are pretty good at that nowadays.
I'm already twenty years old!
Sorry.
We're about the same age.
Ah, she looks so cute when she smiles.
Huh? The same age? No way! You're lying!
Huh?
Well, you said "High school girls,"
so that makes me think you're not so young.
Ah, I was... I judged someone by appearances again.
Attention all customers:
Due to the heavy snow, this train will be travelling at a slow pace.
We are sorry to inconvenience our dear customers.
Oh, no! At this rate, when will I get to Tokyo?
What are you going to do in Tokyo?
It's not really anything big. I'm just moving.
I want to look for a job there.
Oh, so we're the same.
Huh? The same?
Yeah.
Ah, I assumed you were from Tokyo...
and had just finished your nationwide tour.
"Tour"?
Like a concert or something,
'cause you brought your guitar with you.
I thought you were a professional musician.
Oh.
So, have you ever been in a band?
I used to be in one back in my home town.
Wow, that's awesome.
Where're you from?
Ah, a text...
No, it's a phone call.
Hello, hello? This is Nana speaking.
Ah, Shoji?
Hm, yeah. The train isn't moving.
I'm not sure when I'll get there.
Eh? Is that going to be okay?
'Cause I might get there at midnight.
Are you sure it's okay?
Yeah, thank you.
I'll call you when I'm about to arrive, then.
Yeah, see you.
Your boyfriend's from Tokyo?
What a lovey-dovey couple.
I see.
You're going to Tokyo to be with him.
No—!
Well, actually, yes...
Which is it?
He's not really from Tokyo...
He actually went to school with me in my home town.
But in order to get into Tokyo's art college,
he moved there last year.
Why didn't you go with him?
I told him I wanted to go with him,
but Shoji, my boyfriend, told me not to.
Why?
He said I have neither a goal nor money,
and that travelling just for him would be pointless.
I see.
So I blubbered and stayed in my own town,
until I saved enough money to go to Tokyo.
We promised each other that once he got into college, I would go to Tokyo.
Once I'm there, he won't have any excuse to ask me to go back. I'll work hard...
Ah, why am I telling this to a person I just met today?
It's fine, even though we've just met.
Say some more, 'cause we still have a lot of time.
Really? I guess you're right.
Well, to kill some time, you just listen to me, then!
Actually, I wanted to share this with all of the others really badly.
Shoji is actually very gentle,
very dependable, and very handsome!
He can sound like an idiot sometimes, though.
You're saying he's like an idiot?
Hey, hey, do you want some beer?
Sure, sure.
Two cans of beer, please!
Well, let's make a toast!
To what?
Well...
For Shoji getting into the college of his choice.
No, that's none of my business.
Then at least for the memories we'll have of this meeting!
Ah, that's a good idea.
Same age, on the same train, going to Tokyo...
This is a rare coincidence.
And there's one more thing.
My name is Nana, too.
Nana-chan.
Do you remember the first time we met?
I didn't know when it started snowing.
The train stopped and started.
It took us about five hours to get to Tokyo,
but I wasn't lonely at all.
I was telling you my stories the entire time.
I didn't ask you anything at all.
It was all right, because I already knew, Nana.
You would've avoided answering any questions I asked.
Nana!
Shoji!
Why are you crying?
You're laughing at me! That's so mean!
It must've been hard, being stuck on a train for five hours.
Yeah...
But... Ah?
What's wrong?
I became good friends with the girl who sat next to me.
I see.
But she's disappeared... I'm sure we got off at the same time.
Maybe she's gone...
I really should have asked for her number.
What? So that means you guys aren't friends at all, right?
Don't cry. Kyosuke and Junko are down there, too.
Huh?
Junko!
Well, see you all later.
Good night.
Huh?
What are you doing? Nana, let's go.
Uh? Okay.
Endo Shoji
Wait...
Is it a good idea to barge in like this?
Please come in.
Since your arrival was so sudden,
I didn't even have time to clean up the place.
Sorry.
Huh?
This is all so sudden.
You must be a bit flustered, right?
I was thinking of living with Jun-chan
before finding a place for myself.
But I don't think you can now.
They're living together.
What?
I didn't know that!
Jun-chan never mentioned a word of that to me!
When did this happen?!
It's hard to say when.
Kyosuke just moved into Jun-chan's place all of a sudden.
I see... I see...
Geez. You didn't even take off your shoes,
Tokyo isn't a foreign country.
This is so wonderful!
What?
You're so eager to get my clothes off.
You're such a pervert!
Me and Shoji... Will we become like that in the future?
I really want to make up for all of the time we've been apart.
Such happiness...
I'll be back at 6,
take care when you're out.
This is bad!
I was thinking of getting up early to cook breakfast for him.
I must improve my reputation before Shoji comes back.
I feel just like his wife doing things like this!
If I can do all of these things for him and make everything all perfect,
I don't know if I would even be able to express my happiness!
It tastes better than I thought it would.
What do you mean,
"better than you thought it would"?
Well, because you're not good at cooking.
Th-That's not true.
I was kidding, kidding. It really is delicious.
You're quite good.
It took me three hours to cook.
Ah, right. How was the realtor?
Did they help you find any places?
Well, I was really busy today, so I didn't go.
Why?
Ah, I see. You went to look for a job?
How's that going?
Yeah, if I don't find a job, I'll...
Don't tell me you slept in all day...
That's not it! I did the laundry and cleaned the apartment!
I've had a very long day!
What are you talking about?
Don't tell me that's why you came here.
Didn't you promise me you'd come to Tokyo,
look for a job, and try to learn to be independent?
Don't give me "What are you talking about"?
I did all of this for you!
Ah...
I lost my temper at him.
I feel so overbearing.
I'm full.
I'll clean it up.
That's fine.
I can do it.
Andou Realty
There aren't any good houses with a monthly rate lower than fifty thousand yen.
I can pay a little more if I try.
But can't you lower the deposit and gift fees?
Hm... In that case, would an old apartment be fine with you?
No deposit or gift fees?
It looks really big, but it's very cheap!
Can I buy a bed and put it in there?
Do you want to take a look?
Yeah!
It's that red brick building over there.
That mansion must've been built before I was born.
It must be really old.
It looked like it had been influenced by the Western style.
And suddenly, I fell in love with it.
Even though it's seven stories high,
it doesn't have an elevator. I didn't like that very much.
But for me, a girl who's lived in the countryside all this time,
when I saw the trees and the river...
Being surrounded by that beauty really attracted me.
Huh?
I messed up the arrangement.
Can we look around, too?
Ah, I'm afraid not.
My customer has already decided to live here.
Ah! Nana!
Ah! Nana! You're Nana! No way! What a coincidence!
Who are you?
I didn't leave you with any impressions at all?
Sorry, sorry.
Are you okay, Nana-chan?
So you do remember!
I didn't realize at first.
You look so different, dressed like that with your hair up,
and you're very rude.
What? Is she your friend?
No, not really.
Yes, that's right!
So you're Osaki-san, right?
What are you going to do? Still planning to live here?
What should I do...?
If you're still not sure,
will you allow this lady to take a look around?
Wow! The kitchen is so cute,
and the bedroom is so big, too.
No way! There's even a kitty footprint in the bathtub!
I want to live here!
Really?
Wait!
Hey, I was here first!
Don't make such a quick decision!
Yeah, sorry.
That's right! What the hell were you thinking?
But it seems like that lady isn't sure about this place.
No, I've decided to live here.
Yokoi.
Wait up!
I can't wait any longer!
I don't want to sleep in that crappy motel anymore.
It doesn't matter where.
I really want to find a place to live as soon as possible.
If you're saying that it doesn't matter where,
please go somewhere else!
I don't have anywhere other than here!
Why don't you live together with that guy?
Did you get dumped?
No, but if this keeps up, I'll be dumped for sure!
Why?
Don't you guys love each other very much?
You're right, but listen to this...
Excuse me...
Forget about things like that
and please decide if you are going to stay or not...
"Things like that"?
You're so mean! I'm stressing out here!
Yokoi!
Yes?
You're doing business with customers.
If you're that insensitive, how will you be successful?
S-Sorry.
You're not just doing your job,
so at least have some romantic feelings!
All right, all right. Please calm down, ladies.
"Romantic"...?
I have an idea.
Who is this old geezer?
He is Andou-san,
a realtor who works in front of the train station.
He's worked in this business for 52 years already,
so he's very experienced.
It seems like you two had a dramatic encounter.
How about you rent this place together?
Look. There's a kitchen and two separate bedrooms.
It not only keeps your privacy,
but will also allow the two of you to help each other in an emergency.
It would be a really good idea to live together.
Not to mention that both the rent and living cost will be halved.
Rent will be halved?
What's half of seventy thousand yen?
Thirty-five thousand yen.
So cheap!
Yeah! Nana, let's do this!
So... Do we break down the commission in half, too?
I can't believe we can live in such a wonderful place!
It must be a dream!
But... Are you the type of person who can keep other people's privacy?
Keep it? Of course!
If you really want to keep your privacy,
I would suggest you put locks on each room.
I'll do that for you right away.
Thank you, Andou-san!
You're such a nice person! Right? Nana?
Osaki-san,
no matter how cheap it is, please don't do this.
Living with other people will only cause you trouble.
Not really.
You're such a lonely man, Yokoi.
Hey, Andou-san.
When can you have the locks put on the bedrooms?
If I start now,
it'll be done before noon tomorrow.
Please do.
I'll move in by tomorrow afternoon.
How about you?
W-Well, me, too!
Then, let's take care of each other starting tomorrow, Nana-chan.
At that time, I didn't know why,
but I was about to cry.
Even though it's hard to explain why...
But Nana's hand was so warm...
that even my heart was set aflame.
I reached into the sky
My love wouldn't reach you.
Omoi wa todokanakute
The multi-colored balloons...
Chiisaku sora ni kieta
disappeared into the sky, growing smaller and smaller.
Irotoridori no fuusen
I'm alone.
I had no destination,
Ikisaki no nai watashi no te wo
but you gently held my hand.
Sotto tsunaide kureta
Starless night; I won’t look back on the shadow of my past.
Starless night kako no kage furi kaeranai
I want to feel your warmth.
Kanjitai anata no nukumori
Tears are falling down; even when I'm lost,
Tears are falling down mayotte mo hanashi wa shinai
I won't let go of your hand.
Tsunaida anata no te wo