Mu, I really think...
I really think I want to become an astronaut.
I believe I can make it to the moon.
H-He beat me to it!
What about you, Mu?
If you're going to the moon, then I'll stay one step ahead.
I'm...
going to Mars.
A big brother should always stay ahead of his little brother.
That is what I have always believed.
But Hibito was always the one moving ahead...
Leaving me behind.
Have I finally caught up, Hibito?
Or are you still...
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that thick veil aside
This simulation's purpose was to perform the next step.
I believe that the CAPCOM schedule indicated that setting B
#99 Life Changes, Promises Don't
would be used on approach to the moon.
However...
In my absence, CAPCOM gave the go ahead to use setting A.
That's the reason this landing ended in failure.
I'm sorry, Mutta.
I noticed your mistake...
But during this training, your performance is under review.
I know why you're having trouble concentrating.
But...
I was hoping you would notice your mistake,
despite everything else that's happening.
Why did you give us the go ahead before you checked with the flight director?
CAPCOM's role is to communicate with the crew.
You do not have the authority to make decisions.
Yes, it was poor judgment on my part.
It's baffling that such a rudimentary mistake could even happen.
This may be a simulation, but that doesn't mean you can be careless.
Act like you're on missions during training, and act like you're training during missions.
That is the attitude we must adopt.
During this simulation, what were you thinking?
I'm sorry.
I believe my mind wasn't on the task at hand.
As I've said many times, we must be on the same wavelength.
I hope you realize that if you continue to underperform, you will be considered unqualified as my backup.
Yes.
Then that's all for this meeting.
I snorted when I heard you tell him to be on your wavelength... Like it's even possible.
This will be my first time on the moon.
I want to ensure that communication with CAPCOM is flawless.
But it seems I was a fool to expect him to deliver.
He has nothing in common with me...
Being on the same wavelength is impossible.
Nothing in common?
You're such a riot...
What's so funny, Pico?
Well, I'd say that you have some things in common.
For example...
You're both members of this huge organization called NASA.
You should try talking to him.
You might hit it off.
Damn it...
What are you so upset about, Nanba?
Hmm?
I've been hearing rumors about Hibito.
How come you call me "Nanba," but you call him "Hibito"?
Because Hibito was an astronaut before the rest of us.
Well, I don't really care.
If you happen to see Hibito, tell him to give me a call.
Have you had dinner yet, big brother Nanba?
Up for some pizza?
Come to think of it,
I met Hibito for the first time here.
Yeah, that's right...
Hey, what was that sound?
It's very familiar.
Bet you haven't heard it in a while.
In Space Pirate Avant-garde,
it's the sound effect when the Avant-garde enters a wormhole.
Oh...
Yeah, that's right. I used to watch that anime.
It's recognizable, so I set it as my ringtone for Hibito's messages.
He was a fan of Avant-garde.
Hey, Nanba...
Do you remember in survival training, when I told you about my little brother?
Sure, Kazuya, right?
Since then,
Kazuya has begun to go outside.
He's going to school and working part-time.
Really? That's terrific!
And he's applied to a company in the space industry where he's always wanted to work.
After passing the written exam, he had an interview.
Wow, Kazuya's doing great!
One of my college friends works at the company.
He was one of the interviewers, and he had nothing but praise for Kazuya.
My friend was very positive.
"Nitta Kazuya is a strong candidate who can stand on his own merit.
He shows promise.
We should hire him right away."
However, it didn't work out...
Huh?
My friend was overridden by a number of his superiors.
According to them,
someone who's given up and become a shut-in before
may do it again.
If that's the attitude our society wants to take,
there isn't much hope.
Here you are.
Pizza Margherita!
Then, how's Kazuya doing?
He's been studying conversational English.
Next month, he'll be coming here to look for work.
Oh... That's really great.
Yeah, I'm sure he'll be fine.
He can make it.
So I don't need to worry about him.
I'm just a little disappointed by the way the world works.
See ya, Nitta...
Drive safely.
Right.
A big brother waiting for his little brother to contact him, huh?
He's going through what I did back then...
Looks like...
I got a message from Hibito.
Y-Yeah, glad to hear it.
See ya.
"It's been a while, Mu.
I was dead for a while,
but I'm coming back to life now.
Right now, I'm wandering around America alone...
I'm sorry for putting you and Apo through this.
For the time being, I won't be coming back to Houston.
I've decided to leave NASA."
Huh?
"But you don't have to worry, Mu."
He's that confident, huh?
He always was able to deliver on his promises.
I feel better, Hibito.
I feel better, having learned that you still don't know how to quit.
Hold on...
Does that mean I'm the one in trouble?
Okay, Hibito!
"From your brother, who is very worried about himself."
Send.
If they remove me as CAPCOM...
Just stop... Don't think about it.
JAXA's busy preparing for a few things.
We'll need to meet their conditions.
This won't be a simple task,
but it's the only way to send Hibito back to the moon.
Understood...
If this is really what Hibito wants,
it's his best opportunity.
It isn't a big deal.
He'll just be called a "cosmonaut," rather than an "astronaut."
That's what Hibito said...
Russia, huh?
I had my doubts...
Yes?
But after watching you fly,
I must ask if you were trained by Deneil Young.
Oh, I sure was...
Mr. Young trained me.
I'm surprised you could tell.
Then, does everyone Mr. Young trains fly the same way?
No, everyone else Mr. Young trained requested a different instructor before they finished.
Uh, Vince...
What is it?
This weekend, would you like to go for a drink?
This is my home.
I'll introduce you to my family.
Come inside.
Thanks for having me!
The time I spent with Vince and his family gave me a hint as to how I could make it.
Six Months Later
While Apo was on a walk,
making some boy's head spin,
I, Nanba Mutta...
Entering built-in hold.
GNC.
Go.
BOOSTER.
INCO.
Go.
FIDO.
NETWORK.
Flight is go.
Mars I is go for launch.
This is it...
And what about CAPCOM?
We're ready. It's a go.
Everything's okay here.
It's a go!
T minus 1 minute.
T minus 10 seconds.
Up you go, Vince.
Ignition.
Liftoff.
At 8:35 AM, on June 10th, 2028,
while everyone
was watching a successful launch...
I was remembering the message Hibito had sent me.
"But you don't have to worry, Mu.
I don't intend to give up on being an astronaut.
I still have a future.
Until next time, Mu.
See you on the moon."
Okay, Hibito...
See you on the moon!
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close