Training
Camp
This is a bit premature, but we should use
Training                                  Camp
Place:                                                                    April deadline,
Time:                                                                          plot still
Goal:                                                                          unfinished
Golden Week for our training camp.
Oh! We should go to the beach!
The beach in May?
Wasn't expecting to hear that
from you, Murakami-san...
There's a reason for that...
April deadline,
plot still
unfinished
We're already past our deadline for the plot.
Right. Sorry.
It's not like I'm not doing it,
I just started doing some rewrites and-
Any more delays would serve to
increase discord between our members,
and our forced disbanding by the student council
due to a lack of results would mean
both the club and our game would be gone...
Make doujin games!
Slack-eyed
Night-owl
Shuttle-runners
Making those doujin games?
I wasn't expecting it to be that hard!
We sure were young then...
Something about having all that free time...
Such a future would undoubtedly be
full of booze-soaked reminiscing.
Aren't you being a little negative?
Is this your first camp, Honda-chan?
Yes!
Well, you just feel free to kick back and
let us upperclassmen take care of everything!
We had ours at Shii's place last year.
That was Teru-senpai's idea.
Really?
Maybe we should do that again?
My house has loud little brothers.
And mine has my folks...
I suppose we can if we
don't have another place.
It's a bit cramped and messy at my house.
Then this year should start with a sweep of the rooms
under the pretense of cleaning up...
Should I remind you this camp is
to help you finish the plot?
I was just kidding.
Glare
You're a tough nut to crack...
Um... well, it's far and kind of out of the way,
but we could have it at my house...
Let's find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
Because there's a world where
only love will carry on
Left all alone like that
But you still can't leave it be
Yes or no, it's always hiding
If you could say it was okay
You could think it was okay
Strange that it was just that quick
The feeling of chasing this kind of thrill
Will be more than you could
have imagined yesterday
Hello, make my day
The magic that we all hold
You'll see the greatest
something of your life
We'll find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
There's a world waiting where
only love will carry on
Broker Items
This is Sonobashi. Sonobashi.
Look at all those fields!
Never been to the end of
the train line before!
This is Sonobashi. Sonobashi.
Never been to the end of
the train line before!
This is the last station.
Thanks for coming, everybody!
The train will now be heading to the yard...
Hi, Miss Sasai!
If it isn't Tama-chan! Hello!
Thank you so much for sharing
with me the other day.
Such a sweet girl.
Oh, don't mention it...
I'll have to give your grandmother
a proper thank you soon...
Is it right to have someone like that
in the pit of carnage we call game making?
Hold on, Murakami-san.
What's with all the stuff?
Well, as long as we're here, I thought I'd take the
opportunity to set up Honda-chan's equipment.
I've also added a server backup
in the event she can't get a signal.
We can use cell phones out here, you know!
And I included bear repellent in the event
one wanders down from the mountains.
This ain't some backwater!
"Ain't"?
Nevermind. I didn't say anything...
I also brought provisions.
Stamina
Glad you came prepared...
And this is my house.
It's huge!
And you must be Tamaki's friends.
Make yourselves right at home!
This is my granny!
Thank you so much for having us.
It's nothing special, but we brought this.
Well, well. You've got fine
manners for a youngster.
Your grandma seems super nice.
She is! She's the best granny ever!
Are you here by yourself, Ma'am?
Tamaki's father lives away for his job,
and her mother is working at the moment.
I see...
And that brings us to why you're here?
Where Tama-chan goes, I go.
This should make for some good backgrounds.
Think you could tone it down a little?
Thanks for coming so far...
Green tea? Did you make this yourself?
Yup. And my mom got everybody some snacks
since she can't see you until
she gets back from work.
Wow, that's sweet!
What the heck?! It tastes just
like green tea ice cream!
You sure it isn't the other way around?
This is good...
It might be worth mixing
with the drinks I brought...
Hey! Now you're just going crazy with it!
I had no idea you were
so good with a computer.
This one was my dad's.
He said I could use it for whatever I wanted.
Well that about does it for the setup.
You've got the shared folders, the chat,
and a few bits of equipment.
Thank you so much.
It feels like you gave me a lot of stuff...
It's fine. I wasn't using any of it.
Wow! It's a tablet!
Wonder if this is her way of telling me
to make sure the pictures turn out good...
Sigh...
Well, then...
So the game we're making...
It's an adventure game!
Kind of a little side-story
to the one we made before.
Adventure...
Yeah!
I get it!
You're almost there.
Don't tease the girl, Shii...
Adventure games are part of a genre
sometimes known as ADVs or visual novels.
Think of them as a sort of
picture book set to music,
but one where the choices
you make affect the story.
Pretty sloppy on the explanation there, Shii!
The games coming out now
have plenty of gimmicks.
Well, I'm not too familiar
with visual novels.
What do you expect?
You make choices...
Yeah!
YEAH!
I get it!
Somebody's into rail carts!
The Plan!
Ideas        Get more members
Concept – Meeting about the setting and other stuff
What we need now is a blueprint
for the kind of game
we're making and the content that goes in it.
Plot                  I'm going to write
the heck out of it!
Assignments from the Leader
Me                Shii            Honda-san!
Write the script        Programming!               Artwork
(Easy!                    (How much time to     Character design
About 300 kb?)     make a website?)         We can use old stuff
Layout design
Wow... This is really starting to feel
like a group project!
Right?
Finally feels like we're
making a game, doesn't it?
Yeah! I feel all excited!
I bet you do!
And we should probably
work on the scheduling first...
Processes? Plans? All's I need to do
is write like a madwoman!
It'll be cake!
Maybe she's improved since last year...
Not to sound like a broken record,
but our main goal for this camp is to...
Finish the plot, right?!
I get it, okay? I'll get it done quick!
I mean, that's what I said...
But I can't think of anything!
And I'm so close!
I'm late because I gave up on
making it a romantic comedy...
But I can't figure out a good ending
for the new story.
I mean, I could use the ending
from the old draft but-
Hey there.
Whoa?!
Why are you getting all
worked up over a plot?
It's just a short story, isn't it?
The old draft was pretty good if you ask me.
It would probably go pretty well with
Honda's artwork with a good rewrite.
And you guys need to ask
me to make some music.
I'm so bored I'm making
all these weird songs.
Is that what you want to hear
at the climax of the game?
Sorry...
Is that a microphone?
And that's not all! I'll put
this in there instead, I swear.
Guess I'll try to figure
something out today...
Someone's fiddling around
with my shishi-odoshi!
Who is it?!
Okay then. Now you want to go into
blend mode and use multiply...
Oh, I see!
I'd better get home for dinner.
Just do what I told you, okay?
Sure! Thanks, Yumine!
See you later.
Um... now I just add the highlights on top...
I can't relax for some reason...
I've been wondering!
Why are we called the SNS Club?
Oh. Well our Captain last year...
We were supposed to submit
the club's application yesterday?
Yeah. I'll take it to the student council
along with a nice apology.
But we don't even have a name yet!
I'll leave that to you firsties.
Write anything you want, 'kay?
I don't really think we have a choice...
Whatever it is, we'll have to stick with it.
And three!
Night-owls
Slack-eyes
Shuttle-runners
And all three sheets were ones I wrote...
Why were they all so negative?!
I just can't draw the lines
right with this tablet...
You need a tablet to draw on a computer,
but it'll be pretty hard if that's all you have!
Is it really that hard
to draw a good picture?
S-sorry! I was just messing around!
This club was our captain
Teru-senpai's idea in the first place.
This here's my buddy!
She'll be doing the programming!
It was a bit of a pain at first, but as the year
went on, I really started to enjoy it...
I think I'd be pretty
bored without this club.
These photos are a record of my life.
Something I'd like to hold
on to as long as I live.
Now you're making me feel all embarrassed...
What I want is a place we can be
without feeling bored.
Don't worry too much about the quality.
I know it might sound bad to
say this is just a club...
But take that first step.
Focus on finishing one thing first.
But I don't even know if I can
draw the pictures right...
That looks to be the case.
I think you might need a scanner.
What's a scanner?
A device that lets you import
the pictures you draw on paper.
But you can use photos
for the characters faces.
This one was pretty good. You can cut it out.
I will not! Honestly...
You're so grim, a romantic, and kind of mean.
But you're a serious person.
You're good people, Captain!
Am I now?
Did my accent slip out again?
Just a little.
That's embarrassing...
Guess you can't judge a book by its cover...
Aw, c'mon...
You really can't judge a book by its cover...
What happened to you?!
Was it a bear?
I made this chirashizushi myself.
Make sure you eat up!
There's so much!
Color me impressed!
My mom makes the best chirashizushi!
It's my little girl's first club,
so she may be a bit rough around the edges.
I do hope you'll take good care of her?
We're glad to have her with us, Ma'am.
Don't be shy, now.
I'll go ahead and draw up a nice bath.
Your mom seems really nice, too.
She is! My mom, my dad,
my granny, they all are!
Who is it?!
Oh, it's you, Seki-senpai.
Hey Honda. Thanks for
letting me use your bath.
I'm back!
And I just finished writing the plot!
I printed it out at the convenience store and
now it's time for a bath, if you don't mind!
If it's the plot you're wondering about,
we're doing a group reading right now.
What I want to know is why
you didn't give us all of it.
This is just one part.
These things cost money, and I wasn't sure
I wanted to leave a paper trail...
I think it's a little late for that...
Alright, then! How about we get
to reading, Honda-chan?
Um... "At a certain place..."
Stop that! You don't have
to read it out loud!
Artist's Impression
"At a certain place in
a certain romance game,
our protagonist Samü stood freshly joined
with our heroine Stella..."
Artist's Impression
Stella         Samü,
I... I have to say it...
Artist's Impression
Stella         I love you!
One Year Later
"But the player had abandoned the game.
And after a year had passed..."
This is pretty meta...
I'm tired of waiting for a scenario
that'll never come in a game that no one'll play!
Stella! We should run
away from here together!
"But tragedy had befallen Stella
in the form of a chronic illness..."
I totally forgot to tell you this,
but I give voice to whatever strong emotions
people around me are feeling.
Plus it's incurable.
What?
But it doesn't just work on humans, right?
Right. I think it's a plot device
for the game or something.
So what's that feeling?
"I'm being watched. What's with the staring?"
"From slender tip to slovenly, unsightly base,
my every nook and cranny..."
"Oh, how good it feels! How I crave it!
I need these flashy flowers
and leaves no longer!"
Sounds more like the tree than the cat to me!
This is so wrong!
"Samü and Stella searched high and low
to find a cure for her ailment..."
"but they couldn't find one
no matter what they did."
"Fresh to the world outside
of an established scenario
and bombarded by the wash
of emotions therein,
Stella's demeanor had become pallid."
"Despite her ever-weakening constitution,
Stella cheered Samü on as he ran
hither and tither for her sake..."
"It was only a matter of time before..."
Thank you for everything, Samü.
I'd stay with you forever if you'd have me.
Maybe you could call what
I have a warm feeling?
"Samü had to make a decision!
The thing is...
Let's get married.
What of their future together?"
"And yet..."
The thing is...
Let's get married.
Confound it all! To be so wishy-washy
when I've got a choice to make!
I could leave it up to the player,
but no one's playing the game!
There's no one to make the choice!
There's nothing I can do!
"And so Samü's adventure came to an end..."
What the heck is with this ending?!
It's way too meta!
That's the bad ending! There's more, honest!
Um... "But had a certain
condition been met..."
The thing is...
Let's get married.
Troubled, are we?
The dialog box talked!
You've kept faith in the face
of the scenario's logic.
I commend you.
You who have found yourself stalled
at the crossroads of many stories.
I'll give you the push you need...
The thing is...
Let's get married.
For what is a man without his pride?!
I won’t hesitate any longer!
Stella, let's be together forever!
I’m so happy. I’ve been
waiting to hear you say that!
I...
Bed         You did it, boy!
Now just get on me and...
Wha...?!
It's happening again...
It's okay! It'll be hard.
Grueling, even.
It won't be easy, but we'll
get through it together.
We'll fight against bitter fate!
I, uh, guess this is the happy ending?
The theme's "There are
two sides to everything."
Who was it?!
Oh, you mean that...
Plus it's something an older guy would say.
And I saved this for last...
Dialog Box (In Human Form)
Well done. I'll be watching over you.
Why does that need to be in there?!
It sounds all forced!
I think it's great!
Really?! You really like this?!
It's oh, so wonderful!
It's really, really wonderful!
So, how do you tell the bad ending
from the true ending?
I don't remember seeing a choice in there.
That's true.
Since I was writing about
going outside of fate,
I thought it would be a little weird to have to
have a choice system inside the game.
And check this out!
When you're playing the game,
true.exe shows up on the desktop...
Then you double-click that
to get the true ending!
Creepy.
Sounds like a virus...
I-it does, doesn't it...
Good work, I guess.
Hopefully we can add some
interesting stuff in.
Definitely.
And I think we can do more with her
being able to hear those voices.
She could hear all sorts of stuff!
And you thought it was wrong before...
Why not? It'll be funny!
And it might be a lot of fun if more objects
turned into people who showed up later!
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Yeah!
Congratulations!
We could do that, but not all of them
have to be old guys...
And we could add in two handsome lovers
for the boy's love fans!
When did you come back?!
That reminds me... I heard you reading
something in your room, Seki-san...
W-well this is the first time we're
making something together!
And it's such a big plan, I thought
I should start with something small!
I like that hustle.
Though I wish you'd found it earlier.
Are you talking about this?
"Behold the evening's dew
upon the leontochir-"
Stop! That's something completely different!
I thought you could go for
some tea and a nice snack-
Are you okay, Granny?!
Why you little rapscallions!
I'm so, so sorry!
We decided to head to the local bathhouse
since we sure as heck
weren't getting any tea.
Women's Bath
Leave your
valuables
at the front.
I'm really sorry. This was supposed
to be our training camp...
It wasn't your fault, Captain!
I'm just glad Seki-senpai was
able to think of a story.
I've got a lot of work to do, too!
Yeah...
I'll start by doing the
artwork for the choices!
Good thinking. Work hard, now.
Kind of feels like those two are getting along now.
Kind of feels like those
two are getting along now.
Fujikawa-san?! I didn't recognize you!
But you're right. Could be good...
Senpai x Kohai...
Yuri... Definitely a possibility...
Hey! What's with the multiplication?!
I should've known!
I had no idea you saw Tama-chan that way!
Whoa, now...
I was just considering the possibilities!
Well Tama-chan...
she'd be the dominant one!
If she were a man she'd be a little skinny,
but in bed she'd always be on top!
Or maybe she'd lure you to her...
That's wrong! You're
supposed to be her friend!
I really don't think it's
a gender thing with her...
I had a lot of fun today, Senpai...
Think I'll try to get in
a little more practice.
How about letting old Marika help you out?
No way. We've got to
finish a game in an hour.
You've got some designing to do, Honda-chan!
Skill Up