Mhmm...
Yes...
Well, you be careful not to
catch a summer cold, Daddy.
Thanks for calling... I know you're busy!
You'd better get going
before you miss your train!
Oh, no!
And here's your lunch.
I made sure to put lots of
sautéed burdock in there!
Thanks!
Okay Daddy, I'm hanging up now.
Mitsukeyou make my day
Yes. I love you, Daddy!
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga aru no sa
See you later!
Sonnan ja hottarakashi de
Sonnan ja hottokenakute
Iesu or noo ha itsumo kakureteru
Daijoubu sa tte ietara
Daijoubu tte omoeta
Akkenai kurai de okashikatta
Konna wakuwaku o oikaketeru kimochi ga
Kinou made no jibun no souzou o koete yuku
Konnichiwa make my day
Minna ga motteru mahou
Isshou de ichiban no nani ka ga mieru
Deaeru yo make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga matteru
Precision Machines
It's July now and I get
to wear my summer uniform!
I got to talk to my daddy before I left,
and there's lots of sautéed burdock in my lunch!
Plus the fortune on the train said
I'd have good luck today,
and the sun feels so good!
Morning, Tamatama-chan!
Morning!
What are you doing here?!
And why did I just high five you?!
Oh, I'm so glad! You remember me, don't you?
Um... it was Teru-san, wasn't it?
Bingo! And how's the club doing?
The club?
The Slack-eyed Night-owl
Shuttle-runners Club!
Didn't even have to take a breath!
I did it, Shinan!
This club was our Captain Teru-senpai's
idea in the first place...
Oh, I get it! You're Teru-senpai!
Oh? Did I forget to tell you that?
They said you were at university now...
Well, these summer uniforms look so breezy,
I thought it'd been too long
since I wore one myself.
And I tried out that game
you made, Tamatama-kun.
What... really?
I get really embarrassed looking at
the pictures I drew for that...
Like there's this girl
Ha-chan who's really good,
Nand she makes me think I
really need to do better...
Really, now...
Are you going to be at Summer Comiket?
Oh, yes.
We're making a game based on
Seki-senpai's old story...
But I'm pretty behind on the
part I'm in charge of...
Then maybe a new hairstyle's
just the refresher you need?
What? When did you...
Now I'm going to sneak onto campus
for a bit of lollygagging!
Er... wait!
My hair's going to get all
frizzy if I don't keep it up...
Really? Don't you worry about it.
But it's so embarrassing...
Maybe I should wear a hairband like you?
Not cat ears... A normal one...
Well I'm not wearing a
cat ear hairband today.
Is that real?!
I'll take a wander around
while you're in class, 'kay?
What a strange person...
Hm? That hairstyle...
Seki-senpai!
Is something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Changed your look, did you?
Your hair looks so nice today!
Huh? Is that...?
Couldn't be. But she's so pretty.
Is she a first year?
She looks a lot older.
What should I do? This is so embarrassing.
It's embarrassing,
but for some reason it feels so... so good!
I wonder if my senpai are in the cafeteria...
It's Ha-chan!
Huh? Did you change your look?
Like you didn't study, failed at drawing,
and had yourself a rude awakening?
Well, you got the first half right...
I thought it was probably
something like that.
What if Tamaki Honda is drawing right now?!
I don't have time to study!
Murakami-senpai's teaching
me the novel engine...
That just leaves the artwork...
The art...
Hate to admit it, but you are good
at drawing those old guys, right?
I don't know if I can do this...
You're such a good artist,
maybe you should just draw the-
Is that how you feel about drawing old guys?!
You want to grow up?
You'd better be ready to draw pictures
hot enough to melt my face off!
Okay! I'll do it!
H-hey! I didn't say that?!
I just happened to be passing by.
I'm Teru, a first year and secret admirer
of the SNS Club, if it pleases you!
Same year as me! Nice to meet you!
You mean first year in college, Teru-san...
This one over here doesn't have enough pride
to do the artwork for Iris' scenario,
so I'm giving her a little encouragement!
Th-that's right!
Ah, yes...
You'll need to work a design
into the UI and everything else...
one that perfectly captures
the Ayachi's whole perspective.
This requires synchronizing with
the wavelength of the world that she sees.
And for that you'll need...
I think you and me are
going to get along fine!
Kind of feels like a knife to the heart...
Well, I'd better get going!
Looking forward to seeing the new game!
What? You aren't going to see the Captain?
I'll spare myself the embarrassment!
Tell Shinan and them I said "Hi"!
She really was just here to hang out...
"Shinan"? Does she mean Shiina-senpai?
You don't think it's rude for
a first year to talk about
the Captain of the SNS Club like that?
I don't care if she's not a member,
she needs to show upperclassmen some respect.
I'm pretty sure you were much ruder
to Seki-senpai, Ha-chan...
Looks like my little kouhai are working hard!
I don't need to see them to know that much!
Shinan's keeping her promise!
Er, Honda-san?
Do you think I could use
that computer for a minute?
There are some old files I
want to get out of there...
Sure. Sorry I've been hogging it!
You don't think you can do a
little better on those faces?
They all look way too bitter.
I'm trying!
And Seki-senpai just gave me some advice.
Oh, you mean Miss Glasses?
Guess some non-creative input
does come in handy at times...
She's really tough on Seki-senpai...
You know you're using a
high spec computer, right?
You need to learn how to use it right!
It's a few years old, and
I've got my own laptop so...
Wait a second. You aren't even a member yet,
so why are you still here?
W-well today's special!
Sorry for the wait!
Oh, Iris!
I can smell the hair wax from here!
You're in high spirits, Aya...
Thank you for the text.
You did promise to tell
me before you stopped by.
Yes, Ma'am! You did say to make sure I did!
Not to mention she needed to
change into the great Iris...
She got the text and she
just flew out of the room.
I was so excited about seeing you today,
Japanese History
I gave all the people in my
history textbook your face!
All of them, huh...
Would you like a snack, Honda-san?
They're just mochi, but...
Actually, do you mind if I use this computer?
No problem. I got all of the files I needed.
This is the folder she was
using. She left it open.
Alt F4, Alt F4, Alt F4!
Er... Sorry about that!
How do you usually come
up with stories, Ma'am?
You know, everyday things...
The yearning for love,
I suppose you'd call it.
Encounters, breakups...
Spinning the ups and downs and wonders
that fill each day into words.
Nothing more...
How wonderful!
The Cat's Pen Collective
(Issue 28)
I found some of your writing from when
you were in the Literature Club...
It was so moving...
I-I appreciate that...
But why did you leave, Ma'am?
Those peaceful days with the Lit Club
left me with a sense of imminent stagnation,
spiraling down into a rut...
I thought you said every
day was full of wonder...
Which means that I'd come to know
every wonder the club had to offer!
I get it now!
She's a mess...
She's really in trouble!
Despite looking so chipper...
You don't think it's weird,
clinging to her like that?!
It's not like she's her girlfriend!
The story was just so fresh...
Such comes from adventure...
Us creators must ever plumb
the depths of experience.
So it really is important
to meet people, isn't it?
That reminds me, what do you think of
that girl with the glasses?
Wh-what do I think, you ask...
I know these...
Oh, I see!
You took them to punish her!
Catch me if you can!
How does she not get it?!
You're getting off topic, Ha-chan...
Isn't there something you wanted to
ask Sek- I mean, Iris?
Right! I can't figure out how to
arrange the stills for this scene!
I was hoping you could
draw the rough sketches!
Hey! Who told you to do the background
for the homepage, Aya?!
Why does it look so scary?!
It's Fujikawa-san...
Which part?
W-w-well, I supposed I
could do a picture or two.
Actually, Iris already made
a rough sketch for that scene!
When did she do that?!
Oh, dear me! This picture is of the great Iris
chastising our girl in glasses!
When did you have time to make a collage?!
Would you look at the time!
Sorry, Iris. I must have talked your ear off!
N-no worries. Thank you for today.
No! Honestly, the pleasure is all mine!
Doesn't this mochi just get
all over your hands, Captain?!
Why yes, it is quite sticky.
I-I'll have you know Iris and I
went to a convention together!
A-and so what? No one loves
her work more than I do!
Who's the better artist,
Senpai?! Me or Ha-chan?!
Me, of course! Right, Ma'am?!
Who's better?!
Me, right?!
It's me, isn't it?!
Well I just got here...
It's me, right?!
Is this one of those lovers' quarrels?
Isn't it a little too late in the day for afternoon soaps?
You're both wonderful, really...
It's a two-hour special.
She left, finally...
I'm pooped...
I still don't know what we
were even fighting over.
Honda-san, didn't I tell you?
Quality's not something worth fighting over.
We want you to be you.
Everybody has their own style of drawing.
And more than anything, I
want to draw a good picture.
Are you saying you'd let
anybody do the art, Captain?
Is it weird I want to do
better than our last game?
You went and made her cry.
Sorry, Honda-san! Don't mind this one.
Er... well...
I-I'm going home now!
Wha... Honda-san, wait!
Goodbye!
SNS
Club
The Captain really got to me...
I'm so ticked off right now...
I need to cool my head...
It really is my fault...
I dropped her computer!
Maybe it's okay...
The screen won't turn on?!
M-maybe it's just on standby!
It's not... the light is still on...
I-I broke it...
My, my...
You've gone and done it now, Tamatama-chan!
Teru-san...
What should I do...
Well you'll just have to
apologize to Shinan, won't you?
Do you think you could come with me?!
I got really angry at her just now and...
This is mine...
Good luck!
Pull it together, Captain!
It feels like someone's been following me.
How do I apologize?
Things didn't go well with
Honda-san in the club room.
I'm off my game today.
I should get home and stud-
Captain!
Mother, I'm home.
Welcome home, Shiina!
Friend of yours?
Yup. She's my kouhai from the club.
This is my mother. She works as
a programmer, mostly from home.
I'm Tamaki Honda. It's nice to meet you.
And nice to meet you!
Shiina only brings her girlfriends home.
Got juicy news on any boys?
Why? I'm not even interested in that.
Well, I'll be working in the back,
so make yourself at home.
Feel free to stay the night if you want!
Oh, I wasn't really plan-
And don't worry, I don't mind two girls
spending the night together!
When she was little, SOMEONE liked to
talk about how she'd marry Aya-
Whatever! Just get to work, okay?!
My mother is such a...
Whatever mother wishes, I'll do...
If that's what it takes
for you to forgive me!
Oh, God! You don't need to do anything!
What is it you want me to forgive?
Well...
Maybe that sounded a little harsh...
I'm, er... sorry about what
happened in the club room.
I got a little carried away.
No, it wasn't your fault.
I'm the one who lost control and...
This is awkward...
W-well...
T-talk about bad timing...
Yeah...
Yo!
Seki-senpai!
Oh, it's Honda-san. What's wrong?
We should be asking you that.
What's with that getup?
Well, my baby brother started
crying when he saw me.
We don't have any makeup remover at my house,
so I thought maybe you'd let me use yours.
And what're you doing here, Honda-san?
I-I needed to talk to the Captain...
That's right.
It kind of ended in a fight
with you two, didn't it?
Not that we don't know how Ha-chan
rubs you the wrong way.
And our Captain here's never been
all that great at pushing people.
Maybe she needs the power to
give her kouhai a nice, Captainly shove.
Bring up anything from the past and I stop.
That is so creepy!
It's like she's two different people!
I'll do it myself! I'm
going to use your bathroom!
Seki-senpai...
Well-
C-Captain!
I-I'm so sorry! I broke it!
You did what? You mean my laptop?
I dropped it after I left.
It's so nice, isn't it?
And it's got all your important files...
No, I've got those backed up...
Waking up from low power mode...
Huh?
The battery just ran out.
What a relief.
I think you're overreacting.
Wha... I think my legs just gave out...
A-are you okay? They don't hurt, do they?
I think you're overreacting.
I wish I had a big sister like you!
You're so serious. And you're so cute...
Don't say that.
I'm a downer who can't even push people.
And calling me cute...
No, you're really sweet
and you take care of your kouhai.
I think you must work really hard
at being so wonderful.
And hello!
Tamaki Honda, what are you doing here?
I should be asking you that!
Murakami-senpai's been teaching me
how to write a game script.
For a few days, in fact.
You and the Captain?
But it must have been fate
that brought us both here...
You shall be my companion, Tamaki Honda!
We're going to blow through
a big chunk of that game today!
Now?!
Well, finals are going
to have us all busy soon,
so we need to do what we can right now.
B-but why?!
I wanted to take my time and
make sure I did the coloring right-
Then do it now!
I brought a tablet you can use!
Just make sure you make something
worthy of my standards!
It's not about winning or losing.
Just think about the schedule...
Could you help me out, Aya?
To think I'd meet you here.
One could even call it fate!
Why are you back in the makeup?!
It's Iris!
Alright! I'm not losing this time!
And you haven't forgotten
what I taught you, have you?
I did say it wasn't about
winning or losing...
What's with all of the hubbub?
Don't think you can get all wild
just 'cause you're young!
Sorry they're staying so late, Mother...
The days before a release
demand cool heads to get through!
We've got drinks, we've got food,
now get down to crunch time!
I'll lay out the sleeping bags.
Feel free to take a bath!
Thank you so much!
Hold on just a minute!
You can't just decide
they're having a sleepover!
This is my room!
Well, I guess I've taught Ha-chan most of
what she needs to know about scripting.
And I guess there's nothing wrong
with a little trial by fire
as long as we make it in
time for Summer Comiket.
And our next Captain is year one,
class three, Shiina Murakami!
Clap clap!
Wh-what... But I-
D'you really think Shiina
can whip us into shape?
Shiina's meticulous, and
she sees the big picture!
You keep the torch lit for the SNS Club.
I want it 10 times bigger than before!
Don't you think that's a little hard?!
Promise!
Promise?
Captain? There's a pose
we want you to look at!
Oh, sure, I'll be right there.
Maybe this counts as 10 times?
To-do-i-te i-ma-su ka
Akogare shisen tsumasaki senobi
Fu-ra-ra na-ga-sa-re
Muchuu no umi o oyogu
Rurabii
Yurara
It's my big sister!
Hey!
I can't accept that.
That's what gives life its meaning!
I think I know why you draw now!
I'd Prefer Not To