Wha...?! Who are you?
I've finally found your little hideout!
After SOMEONE said they were going out
to test their skills against other people!
Bet you felt real good
making a fool out of me!
What?! Who the heck are you?!
Mitsukeyou make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga aru no sa
Sonnan ja hottarakashi de
Sonnan ja hottokenakute
Iesu or noo ha itsumo kakureteru
Daijoubu sa tte ietara
Daijoubu tte omoeta
Akkenai kurai de okashikatta
Konna wakuwaku o oikaketeru kimochi ga
Kinou made no jibun no souzou o koete yuku
Konnichiwa make my day
Minna ga motteru mahou
Isshou de ichiban no nani ka ga mieru
Deaeru yo make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga matteru
Debugging is Serious Business
I-I think you might have the wrong person...
Don't think you can fool me!
I have the right person!
Tamaki Honda, year one, class two!
Don't even try to tell me you
weren't in that club room!
E-er...
As if I could forget last Saturday!
The evening I walked to the club room
and opened your door.
And there was that old guy
with the wooden box...
But I...
I was hoping maybe I could join your club...
Later!
...was thrown out by that girl with
the uninspired glasses!
But don't think I didn't see!
You were in there, too!
She's the one who wanted to join our club...
Sorry, I can't quite recall...
What?!
My big sister told me.
You're a member of the SNS Club.
Your big sister?
The Slack-eyed... uh...
The Slack-eyed Night-owl Shuttle-runners!
Pretty long name for a short stack!
I grow two millimeters every year!
Me and my daddy measure-
That's not what I meant!
Tamaki Honda, you and I
are going to have a bout!
A-a bout?!
I'm in the Illustration Club,
Literature Club
but I can't let an insult
from the SNS Club stand!
This is a battle between artists!
The Cat's Pen Collective
(Issue 28)
This is my favorite book.
The Literature Club put it out a while ago.
You and I are going to design characters
based on a scenario in this book...
then we'll see whose fits better!
And if I win, I want a copy of your game!
Maybe one day we'll have people
out there playing our games...
Maybe I should just give her one...
Oh, wow. That sounds pretty tough...
Why do you look all deflated?
No, I just...
I don't know how good an
artist you are exactly,
but I bet your senpai had to lead you
by the nose so you could make that game.
Plus it's pretty hard to make
a game without an artist.
How could you-
They did help me, but I practiced
a whole lot all by myself!
You went to junior high out
in the boonies, didn't you?
Then you came here for high school.
Still getting used to the new waters?
I-it's not the boonies...
Tondabayashi isn't the boonies...
Sorry, I wasn't trying to
badmouth your hometown...
Let's just forget about that!
You just go flapping your gums and-
So are we battling or what?
The reason I could draw all that stuff
is because my senpai helped me...
I need to win for them!
I'll battle you!
That's more like it.
And there's no way I'm going to lose, either.
This book turned my whole life around.
And I've kept drawing in
anticipation of this day!
Stardust Desires
(Act 1)
By Iris
Wait... Hey!
I've seen that title somewhere before...
Now I'm going to read it.
"My name is Aya...
I am but a girl, fighting in secret against
the shadowy figures who eat away at my town.
I seal away the elusive fiends for the people,
my twinkling stars.
I hear them whisper of
me, the Stardust Maiden.
But I lead a rich private life,
shining like so many stars!
I've even found myself a boyfriend lately.
But there's someone else
who's caught my eye...
A man, holding his umbrella out
for an abandoned kitten.
My heart did somersaults!
Why, oh why, does my heart
beat like a jackhammer?
Why, when I've already found a beau-"
Omigosh, it is hers!
I don't think I should be reading this...
What's your deal?
I was just getting to the good part.
We're supposed to draw
the characters from this?
That's right!
"Me and this man of the umbrella, this Baruta,
have grown quickly intimate.
I found myself at an amusement
park at his invitation.
But who should I run into
there but my boyfriend?
I, Aya, would never stoop to cheating...
But his eyes, gazing beyond the night sky...
'Leave him, Aya.'
His words pierced me like a meteor.
And I felt his arms around me, gentle.
What to do? My feelings
for Baruta had already-"
What the heck are you drawing?
The Heroine
What's with the luckless
bespectacled heroine?
Could you please take this seriously!
I didn't... I just...
"The fiends had come for the Earth again,
bringing my joy to an abrupt end.
They and the Planetary Defense Brigade
clashed in my own town..."
It's a masterpiece, no matter
how many times I read it...
This is what makes life worth living!
Now, onto the next round.
Have you finished designing her boyfriend?
I mean, if you do the same
thing you did with the heroine,
this one is already in the bag for me...
What?! Why does she look so serious?
And the delicate linework. Is she drawing...
Is that an old man?
Wait a second, Tamaki Honda...
Are you drawing the other guy, Baruta?!
Is she passionately rising to
the challenge I've given to her?
No, she looks like she's so fired up that
she doesn't even care what the theme is!
She's so excited, she's putting every ounce
of Tamaki Honda into the tip of her pen!
And you can see her soul
right there on the page!
She's working beyond the bounds of mere
character design! The passion of it!
It's my loss...
Come again?
You'll rue this day, Tamaki Hon-
Ow...
Are you okay?!
Stay away!
I don't need pity from the enemy!
One day... one day... you and your little...
You can have this.
This is your game...
My Captain did say she wants
lots of people to play it.
It's Minaha.
My name is Minaha!
This isn't over by a long shot!
One Way
(excluding bicycles)
"Baruta said that rainy eve,
'I've no choice but to go.
My friends are out there fighting.'"
I knew it...
Morning, Honda-san!
Good morning!
Sure feels like summer, doesn't it?
"O, fateful stars...
why must you toy with us so pitilessly?"
"'You! You're the Stardust Maiden!'
Baruta's eyes were glued to my bosom,
his face the picture of shock and trepidation.
In a single step, a chasm grew between us.
And yet..."
So clear and fresh.
Makes me wish this day would last forever...
"'Wait!' My destiny was right here...
'We should...'"
Run!
I'm sorry, Seki-senpai!
I've been a bad, bad girl!
Honda-san!
Make doujin
games!
Slack-eyed
Night-owl
Shuttle-runners
SNS
Club
I need to get this book back to her.
Wait, what year and class was she?
She said something about a big sister...
Maybe she was talking about one of my senpai?
Maybe I can find her in the
junior high building...
I'm just asking why making games
has to be so hard, you know?
You're asking that now?
I thought I'd make some songs and
the game would be done, just like that.
You don't honestly think it'd be that eas-
You... How could you... It was terrible!
I couldn't stop crying!
I had no idea the great Iris wrote it...
It was like... like every line was
a gentle caress to the heart!
I'd finally found a way to
get to the true ending...
And...
Why'd there have to be a game-stopping bug?!
I'm so sorry! I'm so, so, so sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Your club has a homepage, right?
Just a simple one for now.
The game froze.
I started looking, thinking
there might be a patch...
But the homepage didn't have
a product page or anything!
Who made that thing?!
Over there.
I'm still learning how to make websites...
I thought it'd backfire if I made a product page
while I was still rough around the edges...
Snap out of it, Captain!
I thought the website was pretty cool!
We have an updated version
that should tide you over.
An update!
Finally, a clear path to the true ending!
No way I can wait until I get home!
Do you have a computer I can use?
I want to play it right here, right now!
Oh! You can go ahead and use my laptop.
Thank you so much!
Thanks for being so fast!
And the production quality was top-notch!
Just copying what I learned from
watching other people...
Kind of unstable, isn't she...
Thanks for letting me use your laptop!
What did you work on?
I did the music!
Oh, wow! I thought it was so good!
W-well... I worked on the art-
You're no good.
That art of yours pales in comparison to
a scenario by the magnificent Iris.
Your art pales in comparison...
Your art pales in comparison
You don't even have any stills.
"Stills"?
You don't even know what a still is?
I think I've heard of them!
My senpai told me!
A still is a special picture that
pops up during an event in the story!
You are seriously lacking
in the fundamentals.
Bet you thought you could just draw some
pictures and slap them in there, didn't you?
Lacking in the fundamentals.
Draw some pictures and slap them in.
Draw some pictures
and slap them in.
I didn't think that...
Oh, c'mon.
It was Honda-san's first try.
In deference to me, of course.
And I'm still sore over you
giving me the bum's rush!
Who are you, anyway? What do you do?
You one of those debug slugs?
That's so mean! You can't just
call someone a debug slug!
Anyway, I'm in the Illustration Club
but I've kind of been in a rut lately.
Then I remembered how I was
interested in the SNS Club...
So that's why you came...
Oh no, sorry we were so rough on you.
It's okay! I'm sorry for
saying all that rude stuff...
How about you join up now?
We'd feel better having
an artist on the team.
Well, now I don't feel like joining.
Bet you just want another slug, don't you?
What is it with you and debuggers?!
And why the heck are you being so rude to me?
Maybe you shouldn't have
been so rude to me first.
Like oil on a fire...
I didn't get to talk to you at the event
since you were sleeping, Murakami-senpai!
I'm really sorry about that.
But it's not like you're too late.
Well, I think she was really rude to you!
I'm not giving up yet!
By the way! Is Iris part of this club?
Hmm? Well...
Well, I was thinking she could sign this
next time she's here!
Who are you trying to kid?!
As if someone like YOU could steal that name.
She's the great Iris!
Looks like another no-go.
I'd sure love to get to know you guys better!
Oh! Remember the homepage?
How about I make a nice member intro for you?
Nice! What say we talk about it?
We'd need to have a picture
for each member...
You're talking like we already-
You should be thankful, Tamaki Honda!
Artwork is the face of a homepage!
And I've already done the legwork for you!
Get your best picture and intro ready
and show it to me!
A good picture... A good picture...
A good picture...
Trying to come up with ideas, Tama-chan?
I promise looking scared's not going to help.
Times like this are when you need
a healthy dose of fun!
Fun?
Exactly! Refresh and input!
Potato Senbei
Classy Caviar
Er, Yumine, I'm a little scared...
I don't think we're supposed to
wear our uniforms in a place like this.
What? It's just an arcade, isn't it?
No rules against that.
Gimme something good!
Asking
too much
The Leaning
Tower of Pisa
Pisa!
I had so much fun today!
Well, I'm very glad to hear you did.
So why were you looking
for something good today?
Working on your next story?
Well, we're supposed to make
good introductions for our club's website...
and I think this picture is pretty good!
Do you mind if I use it?
Why would you show the whole world
me in such an embarrassing pose?!
It's supposed to be YOUR introduction!
You have a point...
You can do it, Tama-chan!
Maybe it should be something that
makes you want to click it?
Oh, it was just a joke!
What is it, Yumine?
It looked like a voice actor I liked made
a post that said they were quitting,
which got me to click the link.
Turns out it was a troll to make you hungry.
They got me good...
That's it!
And that's how it happened...
Yumine gave me an idea, and I figured out
what picture I wanted for my introduction.
It's sautéed burdock!
I mean... it was really good!
The trick is to add sesame
oil right at the end...
That's not it at all. She
really doesn't get it.
And Murakami-san chose
a picture of a drink...
Mushroom Soda
Packed with Guarana
A tasty beverage with the rich taste
of soy isoflavones, made even better
with the fragrance of mushrooms.
Where the heck did you find that one?
My brother looked hilarious sleeping on
the sofa yesterday, so I made a sketch...
Sketched?! Is this supposed to be realistic?!
Anyway, I can't draw, so I made
some lyrics into a picture.
And here's the preview...
Tamaki:
Illustrator                                                          Scenario Writer
Mura:                                                               Music
Programmer
Strolling toward town
Brushing the shadow of a cloud
And you said it
Maybe we'll find each other again?
You said Truly, I opened my umbrella alone
Hold it however you want As if
And that's so you Just like custard
Who the heck are we introducing...
Oh, and I... I drew some art
for your game yesterday!
You know, while I was
still basking in the glow!
No matter how many times I read it,
the heroine's pathos...
I don't know, there was
something charming about it.
She's really good...
Er, we're really happy you
drew something and all, but...
you know you're not a member, right?
Do you need an introduction?
I mean, you could join now...
I don't want to!
Jeez!
And you, Tamaki Honda! Where's your drawing?!
Uh...
How's the artist going to look
without her art on there?
Well, I'm not a good artist like you are...
Don't be naïve.
It's not about the art.
Like, what about when someone
gives you a present for your birthday?
Even if it's not that great, doesn't it
make you feel closer to them knowing
that they made it just for you?
My daddy made me a present himself!
What're you mooning over?!
Then I'll draw something!
I'll draw lots of stuff and...
And I'll put it on the homepage!
I like the sound of that.
I need to practice so I have stills
worthy of showing Iris...
And her former work, Stardust Desires...
I'll bring it to life!
I'll be leaving now! Tell
the great Iris I said "hi!"
Probably better not to reveal my identity.
Some things are best left in the past.
Wait a second.
Who was she? Never even told us her name.
Just like that, Minaha was here.
She's probably in junior high,
but I don't know what year or her last name.
But I do know one thing.
She's a better artist than me.
I wonder what's going to happen now...
To-do-i-te i-ma-su ka
Akogare shisen tsumasaki senobi
Fu-ra-ra na-ga-sa-re
Muchuu no umi o oyogu
Rurabii
Yurara
I mean, I tried drawing...
What are you doing to Tama-chan?!
Are you really the great Iris?!
Wait, I say!
Would you still be my Captain?
Skill Up, Part 2