Just feel that cool breeze.
Today's going to be good, I can feel it.
That's what I want to say...
But I'm a mess.
I can't believe I'm drawing pictures
for a game makers club...
Tamaki-chan!
F..F..Fujikawa-senpai!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to scare you like that...
That's cute.
You'll be late if you don't get a move on.
What've you been doing?
Oh!
I just love coming to the
riverbank to relax...
Pretty easygoing for someone
who just started classes.
Let's go together!
Sure...
Oh! What about your bike?
Don't worry about it.
I wanted to talk to you about something.
Wait...
That's Murakami-san.
You're right! It's the Captain!
Hey!
I tried to pretend I didn't notice...
But I guess they aren't going to
keep talking forever...
Good morning.
You don't have your
headphones today Fujikawa-senpai?
I do, but I try not to listen to music
on the way to school.
There are lots of sounds out there.
Lots of input for a sound person.
I figure maybe it's good inspiration
for my song making?
That is so cool!
But you're the one listening to music.
It doesn't exactly seem like you.
Ah... It just feels like people are laughing at me
whenever I'm in a crowd,
so I cover my ears.
Is she okay...?
Did you make another song, Fujikawa-san?
Well, I wanted to get it down yesterday
since I've got my part-time job today.
Wow... what kind of job?
I'm a waitress at a family restaurant.
You're really something, Fujikawa-san.
You make music and you're a waitress.
You can use my first name, Honda-chan.
I'd feel better if you did.
O-okay, then... Kayo-senpai...
I don't know if I can call you that...
So that's what communicating gets you...!
Yo!
Morning!
Good morning!
So the whole SNS Club is all together
first thing in the morning!
Early and in sync!
"Whole"...
Oh, right. It is just the
four of us, isn't it?
I don't know what to say...
We were pretty much useless.
You're the only first year we got...
Oh! I'm so sorry! I didn't
mean it that way...
Don't sweat it. We might get
some new people in later!
Which means the four of us
have to work hard today!
Ah, sweet positivity!
Right. How about we have
lunch together today?
Or did you already promise
someone else you would, Honda-chan?
Ah... no, I'm alright.
Well that's that. Let's get going!
Okay!
Mitsukeyou make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga aru no sa
Sonnan ja hottarakashi de
Sonnan ja hottokenakute
Iesu or noo ha itsumo kakureteru
Daijoubu sa tte ietara
Daijoubu tte omoeta
Akkenai kurai de okashikatta
Konna wakuwaku o oikaketeru kimochi ga
Kinou made no jibun no souzou o koete yuku
Konnichiwa make my day
Minna ga motteru mahou
Isshou de ichiban no nani ka ga mieru
Deaeru yo make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga matteru
A Fun Production
I'm having lunch with my upperclassmen
in the club room today.
Wow! Are you going to show off your pictures?
Oh...
Wait, wait! I'm keeping them a secret!
I just couldn't draw yesterday... and...
Sorry! I need to go!
See you later!
Nothing quite like an old friend running away
clutching something she's shy about...
Club Room
I get embarrassed just thinking about
other people seeing them...
I mean, all I've ever done is copying...
If it doesn't work out, it doesn't work out.
I don't know if I'm up for this...
And so we meet again!
You, who frolic so harmoniously through the wen,
make my garden complete!
Behold the evening's dew upon the leontochir!
I'm your-!
Is she crying?!
I-I'm so, so sorry!
You looked like you were having so much fun!
H..Honda-san! Just wait a minute!
You can't write a scenario that resonates with people
if you don't speak the lines out loud!
And I just wrote some really good ones!
Call it an explosion of catharsis, or...!
Er...!
Just forget I said anything!
That sketchbook!
I want to see it! Show me!
O-okay, but just the first few pages!
Oh, you've been copying our stuff.
Kind of weird seeing someone else
draw artwork from our game...
Well I'm going to start... Um...
Hmm?
I came up with these myself,
so they're kind of all over the place...
Is that right?
Well that horse is already out of the barn.
Plus I didn't get enough
on the way to school...
She's too cute...
So what'd you think of our game?
Well, at first it really threw me for a loop since the art was so different from
the manga I usually read...
But then I started to get into it,
and that made drawing it super fun!
Is that right...
That works.
Who cares about how good it looks
as long as you're drawing with feeling?
That's the kind of raw art I want to see!
Then we're even!
As long as you show me what
you wrote, Seki-senpai.
I'm still writing this one!
I'll show you when it's finished!
O-okay, then...
Then I want to see one of your old ones!
Do you have any?
My old ones?!
Like from when I was in Writing Club...?
Nay, no, not in a million years...
Those are...
Stardust Desires
"Stardust Desires, Act 1. By Iris."
Act 1
Stardust Desires
By Iris
"It was then, on the eve
of my 3,037th birthday,
the sky full a'sparkle with stars that did not
so much shine as weep from the heavens-"
No, Shii!
No reciting! You'd better
forget every single line!
Captain? When did you get here...
We didn't want to spoil the party...
Well try speaking up next time!
What say we eat?
Dewdrop
Tea
Oolong
I'll have you know, Honda-chan, Stardust Desires
is among Lady Seki's finest works.
And it's got some serious twists,
starting with how the heroine-
My lunch tastes like lead...
I'm complimenting you!
My little sister is super
excited for the next act!
Don't go spreading it around!
Could we please stop talking about it?!
Oh, come on!
Honda-san...
Yes?
Are you worried about how
I pressured you before?
I... Well...
Well... I apologize...
I'm looking forward to
seeing your artwork, too.
Right!
Well for our next phase, how about we really put
some work into Samü and Stella's love scene.
It might pop on screen, but personally...
Samü...
I think we need a story that really draws people in.
He was that really cool boy from the game.
Like?
Hmm... Like maybe they buy a house out in Tochigi...
I think I drew him...
Hmm... Like maybe they buy
a house out in Tochigi...
Good luck in life!
The Original
I'll show them next time!
Will this be all for you?
Yes, thank you!
Look at you, Fujikawa-san...
That outfit looks super good on you.
You think so?
Welcome!
And how many are in your party?
Alright, since we're making
a side-story this time,
we're not going to have to worry
about the character design.
We can just use what Teru-senpai
already made for us.
You mean the senior who started this club?
The very same, although she's in college now.
She did the cutest artwork...
And she was a real beaut.
She gathered the three of us out of the blue
and told us we should make a game.
Wow...
Right... And you remember when
she cosplayed as a potato?
A potato?!
Feel free to change the
designs if you want, though.
Exactly.
You're in charge of the artwork, so be sure
to let us know if you have any ideas.
Well...
the art was so cute, plus the characters
and the story were so good...
You're embarrassing me!
It's just, the characters were
all so pretty and so cool.
Like something out of a shoujo manga...
And um...
I thought maybe there's
some room for an older man?
You're kidding me...
Well let's get all our ideas
out in the open for now!
And once we're done with that,
we can work on a plot that'll get the story going.
So what you were writing
this afternoon in the club room...
I was trying to think of
some standout lines...
Standout?! That's what you did before, Aya.
You didn't manage your time properly
and you ended up holed up in that room
with Teru-senpai right before Comiket.
No, no! It'll be fine this time!
"This time"? You started writing Stardust Desires
in
junior high and still haven't written the second act.
Could you please stop talking about that?!
Ladies...
Fujikawa
as a courtesy to our other customers, please hold
your meeting at a reasonable volume. Okay?
S-sorry, Fujikawa-san...
Now back to the subject at hand!
Plot          I'm going to write
the heck out of it!
Assignments from the Leader
Me
Write the script
(Easy! About 300 kb?)                  Shii
Programming!
(How much time to           Honda-san!
make a website?)               Artwork
Character design
We can use old stuff
Layout design
Once we're done with the plot we can
turn things over to Honda-san!
Script debugging
Fujikawa-san
Music, SFX
Royalty-free stuff works
Well this time do it
sooner rather than later.
You got it!
So I don't need to do the art yet?
Aya will need to decide what kind of artwork
she'll need for the scenario first.
Well I guess that's where we are for now...
Any questions, Honda-san?
Honda-san?
Oh! It's just, both of you seem like
you get along so well.
I guess it's really important to be close
when you're working on a group project...
"Close"?
I've known Shiina since way back, is all.
Don't call me by my first name.
What's wrong with that? It's so cute!
Am I right?
Well, Aya...
I think it would be pretty cute if you
dressed in all black like you used to...
Wha...?!
And I remember how you used
to talk just like a ma-
That's in the past!
I don't know why you have to pick
at every little thing all the time-
Grr...
Ladies...
Can't believe she gave us the boot!
Do you think we made her mad?
Nah, she's just serious about everything.
I'll be leaving you here.
See you!
See you again!
Shii has to get herself to cram school.
Full of vim and vigor, that one.
But it's like she said, we didn't have enough time
on our last project because I messed up,
so it looks like I've got to
write my heart out this time.
That's why I've got stacks of material,
and I'll need to use all my energy to-
Sorry! I'll make some of the
characters older guys, too!
It's not that... Er, I'm sorry...
You all just look so in sync, I don't know if I'm
the best pick to help you make your next project...
Hmm...
Well I don't want you feeling
like a third wheel...
We've already finished that project, and now
we want something that's all you, Honda-san.
Oh! And I'm serious about
wanting to see your drawings!
Let's knock this out of the park!
S-sure!
But I really think we should put
some older men in there!
I, uh... I'll give it a shot.
They said they don't need the art yet,
but maybe it's okay if I start now...
I told myself I'd get more serious,
so now I need to actually...
Huh?
This is Ayame's notebook...
The Idea Space
Did you find a notebook
at the restaurant yesterday?
That someone forgot? Can't say I did.
You haven't found it yet?
My secret notebook, second
only to mine own life...!
Maybe if you'd put things
back where they belong.
Um...
This...
It must've gotten mixed up in my things...
The Idea Space
It was really, um...
I mean, I had no idea you wrote such...
Er, mature stuff...
Those're old scripts! You've
got it all wrong, see!
It's not what it looks like!
In fact I didn't even write those!
What's she going on about?
I'm really sorry for asking
you to do this, Yumine...
No way. I've been wanting to
check out your club, Tama-chan.
So all I have to do is
show them this sketchbook?
Yeah. I feel too shy to do it...
But we can't make the game
unless they see it...
Why won't you show them yourself?
B-b-because I'm scared!
They had an upperclassman
doing the art before, and it was so cool...
And when I try to draw,
it all looks like my manga at home...
They might get mad at me
for being a bad replacement...
Her house was always full
of those old manga...
Nothing but hard-boiled characters...
Then you won't mind if I take a look?
It's been a while since I've
seen a drawing from you...
N-not yet.
Anyway, leave it 'til you're in the room...
And try not to look too hard...
Not sure it's possible to
look too hard at a picture...
Please!
The only thing keeping me calm
is thinking about my daddy!
Today's the fourth Saturday of the month!
He's coming home!
All those faces... that is
some serious eye candy...
Make doujin games!
Slack-eyed
Night-owl
Shuttle-runners
"Slack-eyed Night-owl Shuttle-runners..."
That's quite the name...
What are you doing, Tama-chan?
Your grandma's been looking for you!
I'm pretending I'm on the porch!
She pretty much had her
head in the clouds up until junior high...
But she's started making all sorts of faces
since she found this club.
I'm so happy you found
a nice club, Tama-chan!
Excuse m-
Huh?
Excuse us for the dancing...
We weren't expecting a guest so suddenly.
Forgive our carelessness.
We've got snacks if you want...
Th-thank you...
Moving one's body works
to stimulate the brain.
Our club does make things,
and we have finished a project...
Sure...
We do hope you won't go around
spreading bad rumors...
That's really not why I came...
You came to our club PR event, didn't you?
Are you here about Honda-san?
I am. She asked me to do her a favor.
She wanted me to show you this.
Wow. Are you sure?
I also wanted to see what
kind of club she was in...
Don't mind her! It's just our sound director
stressing over a melody!
Look sharp, would you?!
Well this is Tama-chan's first club ever,
and she's really serious
about doing the best she can.
Well she's definitely got
that can-do attitude.
She wants to change, and I want to do
everything I can to support her!
But I was a little worried...
Very worried, actually!
I know she's kind of ditzy,
but is she getting along with the club?!
And what is that sound?!
Could you use some frigging headphones?!
It doesn't sound the same...
I'm not an expert or anything...
But I thought those tracings
of Honda-san's were really good.
Those are are the only things
she showed us, though.
Actually, she was just saying...
I want you to show it to them
while I'm not around...
I get embarrassed when people
look at my drawings...
But we can't make anything
unless I show them...
Every embarrassing bit!
You didn't make her draw
anything embarrassing, did you?!
What are you making her do?!
What is going through your head right now?!
What I mean to say is Tama-chan
has to learn how to do digital art
if she's going to make the
artwork for the game, right?
Sooner or later, yeah...
And do you have someone to teach her?
Hello?
I suppose Teru-senpai might
be able to if we ask...
We can't! We said we wouldn't
bother her anymore after she graduated!
But still...
Hey, Fujikawa-san!
Think you could talk to someone for us?
You listening? Maybe you
could talk to Temawari-san...
Temawari...
You mean THE Temawari?!
The artist who did "800 Devilish and
Delightful Shogi"? She's super famous!
Didn't know she released a book like that.
I love Temawari!
Everyone on the internet knows her!
So I hear...
And she has regular meetups
with this one over here.
Please introduce me...
You scared the crap out of me!
Why didn't you tell me
we had a visitor?! Geez!
You're saying that NOW?!
So you're a friend of Honda-chan's.
I'm Kayo Fujikawa, the sound director.
I'm Yumine Fuda. I'm a first-year.
What I want to know is why you can't pay attention
to what's going on while you're making music?
Sorry about that...
I was making songs for a boy's love CD
Temawari-san is making
and I'm having a pretty rough time with it...
The great Temawari's making boy's love...
What's this, then?
The illustrations are super nice!
Well if you're looking for someone to
help her do digital art, I think I could help.
Really?
But we can think it over
once we take a look at her drawings.
Here we go!
I knew they'd be hard-boiled types...
And it looks like she went all in...
Wha... That's mean! You don't have to laugh!
What would Tama-chan think if she heard you?!
Sorry, sorry!
But I don't think she has a
thing to be worried about.
She might be worried because her style's
so different from Teru-senpai's,
but she's really good!
And it looks like she had fun!
"Fun"...?
We had her sketch something at the event.
She made such a nice face...
Drawing with a face like that,
I figured that our characters would look all happy...
And instead we get these manly men...
Pretend all you want, you're not fooling me!
Sorry. She's always been like this...
I'm coming in!
W-welcome back, Yumine.
Did you show them my sketchbook?
Yup!
And...?
Well...
Why can't I just say it...
Saying something about how nice she looked
drawing doesn't quite get the point across...
They said, "Work hard.
You've still got a long way to go..."
I knew it...
Sorry! I was just kidding!
Wha...
They said you're fine as long as you
look happy while you draw.
And the characters are probably happy, too.
As long as I look happy...
I'll see you later!
Thanks!
But I really think you
should show them yourself.
You're the one who drew
the pictures, Tama-chan.
I see... so that's what we're going for?
The world of art is ever expanding. Why not?
Right? What's the point of doing it
if we don't have you draw something fresh?
Got it! Now I need to make
sure the scenario fits.
Really...?!
And I can help you with the digital stuff
if you're okay with it, Tama-chan.
Sure!
But I thought you were busy
with the Illustration Club?
Well, then...
maybe you can help me
when I need help drawing?
Of course! You can count on me!
No!
I'm definitely not thinking of how adorably
embarrassed you'd look drawing boy's love!
I'm not!
Yumine?
To-do-i-te i-ma-su ka
Akogare shisen tsumasaki senobi
Fu-ra-ra na-ga-sa-re
Muchuu no umi o oyogu
Rurabii
Yurara
Who was it?!
We should run away from here together!
And who might you be?
Stop!
Just focusing on finishing up one first.
But I...
Broker Items