Wow, that sure is a long line...
Kind of strange coming to a convention
when I don't know the first thing about them...
We're selling our game, aren't we?
We sure are.
We're selling the game we walked through
the flames of Hades
to make to these fine people!
Captain?!
Shii?!
Are you okay, Captain?!
She's burning up!
I can't go on...
I hereby bequeath my treasure to you...
Captain...
Captain!
This station doesn't provide connections for
delayed final CC and Express Line trains.
Take care of yourself, Captain!
I know this trick...
She's got a real knack for
the pre-event affliction.
In Junior High...
You get your butt to this
sports meet right now!
I mean, I'm here!
In Junior High...
What?! Another fever?!
You think she'll be okay?
Something tells me she'll
find her way to bed.
How about we get back to the venue?
We've got a booth to set up!
S-sure!
Mitsukeyou make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga aru no sa
Sonnan ja hottarakashi de
Sonnan ja hottokenakute
Iesu or noo ha itsumo kakureteru
Daijoubu sa tte ietara
Daijoubu tte omoeta
Akkenai kurai de okashikatta
Konna wakuwaku o oikaketeru kimochi ga
Kinou made no jibun no souzou o koete yuku
Konnichiwa make my day
Minna ga motteru mahou
Isshou de ichiban no nani ka ga mieru
Deaeru yo make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga matteru
Direct Sales
Go ahead and unpack the bag.
It's got all our stuff in it.
Sure!
She said it was her treasure...
It's my treasure. Hoppity-hoppity hop...
That's from our last
Captain's personal stash.
Hello! We're looking forward
to working with you.
Y-yeah! So are we!
Doujin Disc Only is now starting...
H-here we go!
Remember, no pushing and no running.
It's nerve-wracking thinking of people
looking at my pictures...
Just take the 300 yen if people want a copy.
And I give them back 700 yen if they pay
with a 1,000 yen bill, right?
Exactly!
I think we might be waiting a while...
Maybe you should put down the money?
All the people here either make games
or want to buy them, don't they?
That's about right.
It sure is a lot... Wait.
Yumine?!
Tama-chan! Is this the event
you were talking about?
Sorry! I can't go over there yet!
I need to hurry and get myself lined up
for Temawari's newest release!
See you later!
Angelic Idols
Everyone else's art is so amazing...
I knew it. Nothing brings them in
like a little razzle-dazzle.
No wonder no one's buying ours...
Maybe my art was just that...
That's not what I mean.
I'm talking about posters and stuff
that makes your booth stick out.
Some people even let you play
their games right there.
But the most important thing...
Is the promotion that we didn't do!
We didn't even tweet it!
But conventions are like that.
Besides, this is our first event.
Unless you want to tell me
you didn't give it 110%?
You're right, but...
How about you look at this picture
and cheer yourself up?
I'm going to get out there and sell!
I bet we've got a few friends out there!
Why don't you draw while you wait?
She sure is fussing a lot over me.
Long time no see! Made
a visual novel, did you?
That we did! How about we trade?
They took care of me all day yesterday.
I really need to say thank you...
A hearty
thank you
to you
Hello!
Should I be drawing?
Should I really just be sitting here?
Excuse me...
Excuse me!
Um, hello...
O-oh!
Someone's here!
Are you the one who did
the artwork for this game?
I am...
I...
I feel so bad.
Everyone here's made such amazing stuff...
I don't even know why I'm here...
I'll take one.
This is exactly the kind of art I'm into!
And if you wouldn't mind...
I'm back! Made a nice trade or te-
Oh! Seki-senpai!
What does it mean when someone
wants you in their sketchbook?
It means they want you to draw something
here at the convention.
You mean they want me to draw
in their sketchbook?!
Sounds like it.
I mean, if it's okay with you.
I-I mean of course it's okay with me!
You can take 10 copies if you want!
Hey!
I don't need it right
now. I'll stop by later!
Got it!
Doujin
Disc
Only
Thank you so much!
Another happy customer, Honda-san!
People really start swarming
in during the afternoon.
But that last guy was
definitely a businessman...
You really do get all sorts at a convention.
I know you're happy, but you think you could
at least pretend to pay attention?
I'll take one!
Yumine!
Oh! But before that...
Wh-what are you doing?!
Those ears are so cute!
I have to take a shot!
And don't move!
Show me that face!
No way!
Could you please stop?
And done!
Do you think she'll like it?
That is a great picture!
I see you really put some effort into it!
Thank you.
Do you really like it?
Of course! I'll treasure it forever.
Oh, and could you sign it for me?
What?! I don't even have a signature!
Or maybe just how you feel right now...
A little message.
Okay!
Dear Daddy, I'm so happy right now!
DADDY?!
Thank you so much!
No, thank YOU!
Look over here, Honda-san!
Okay...
What do you think you're doing?!
I couldn't help it. You looked so sweet.
I'm going to need you to send me that!
Come see our new release!
Doujin Disc Only is now over.
That's 13 copies today!
I'd dare say they like us!
Of course, that's the nine
I traded plus four sales.
And one of those was to Fuda-san...
Oh, it's a text from Fujikawa-senpai.
She says she's on her way.
Really, now?
Then maybe she can help us clean up.
Right. I should let Teru-senpai
know about our day...
Teru-senpai,
We've had a heck of a day,
but the SNS Club just keeps
running along!
Oho! Looks like they're having fun!
The businessman cosplay's heck on the hips,
but I think I'm glad I came!
The club and the little
kitty are hard at work!
Maybe they deserve another
little treat soon...
Good job today, Honda-chan!
Fujikawa-senpai!
Hey, there! Did you make any sales?
We did, but just a few...
It's like that the first time.
Oh, and listen to this!
Someone asked me to draw
in their sketchbook today!
That's amazing!
How'd it turn out?
I managed to draw her something,
though the face was a little uneven
And where's our dear scenario writer?
She's...
Rock...!
Paper...!
And one more time!
...playing rock, paper, scissors
at the post-event giveaway.
I've never seen someone look so serious
in a game of rock, paper, scissors...
Just think, if I'd hit four rocks in a row, I could've gotten
that limited edition I couldn't buy last year...
You're still talking about that?
Honestly, I never pegged you as
a collector of anime stuff...
I try to keep it on the down low...
I mean, I'm just another otaku.
My pin's from an anime, too!
What? Really?
Really. It's got the name
on the back and everything!
But that was one heck of an event!
Got me in the mood to write a nice novel!
And there were so many good artists.
It was a little overwhelming...
You should've been there, Fujikawa-san.
Well, after I sent Murakami-san that music
last night, I slept for 17 hours straight.
That's way too much...
I'm getting a call from Shii.
The Captain?
Hello?
Aya, tell me about the convention!
You okay, Shii?
I probably am...
I've got a fever of 98.9 degrees.
It must have been all of those people...
But suppose I'd fallen deathly ill...
Unable to go outside, a
burden on the rest of you...
I wanted to apologize in
case anything happened!
I get it, I get it. You're
forgiven, so just rest up.
Take care, now.
That would explain the absence...
Yup. Ran off this morning saying there were
too many people at the station...
And 98.9's normal temperature!
But enough about that!
What about the wrap up party?!
What? Without the Captain?
Give her two days and
she'll be right as rain.
Sounds good! How about
this weekend at your place?
Why my place?
I beseech thee, o Iris!
Who said you could use my handle?
And how long are you going
to wear the bunny ears?
Man, my muscles are killing me!
Which muscles?
My senpai worked hard,
I drew a lot of pictures,
and we somehow got a whole game out of it.
I know I'm not exactly a good artist,
but maybe someday there'll be
people out there who know who we are?
Just the thought of it got
my heart all fluttery...
So that weekend we had a party
at Seki-senpai's house.
Yumine came as our plus one.
And the king is...
Who?!
M-me? What should I...
You'll make a great king, Captain!
And we'd love to hear a kingly word!
I could start with a coronation speech...
Having dragged myself here today
to the SNS Club wrap up party-
A little less honesty, please!
When I first started as Captain
I was a nervous wreck,
but we made a game, and it was all thanks to
Honda-san and the rest of the club.
Pretty thoughtful...
Maybe one day we'll have
people out there playing our games...
I'm going to do my best!
And I'll be helping from the shadows!
What happened to Fujikawa-san?
She said she just thought
of a good melody, so...
E, G sharp, A, G sharp, E, G, E...
You're a darn mess!
The king is who?!
Me, is it?
Well, as long as we're all here...
Why don't we play your game?
And I want to hear all about the journey!
Oh! That's a great idea!
I might notice all sorts of things are off
if I look at the artwork now...
I really don't know if I want everybody
reading through my scenario...
And the code I wrote during
crunch time was all buggy...
That's a "nay" on all counts.
Oh, my...
I'm next, eh?
I've got something I need
to tell you, Honda-chan!
What? Me?
Sorry for throwing you in at hte deep end
when you're still a newbie.
Plus, I heard someone stuck up for me?
Oh, no!
We all were just really stressed,
plus I had a lot of fun working with everyone...
You are such a sweetie, Tama-chan!
You're abusing your power, King-kun!
What's wrong with that?
Nothing wrong with a little
skinship, is there?
She... she's not like that at all!
You don't know the first thing about her!
I should know, I've been watching her
since elementary school!
Tama-chan's a top!
If she were a man, she'd DEFINITELY be a top!
And Fujikawa-senpai would be the bottom
with the come hither stare...
Are you sure they need to be men?
You're with me, right Seki-senpai?!
Why d'you gotta... Why're you asking me?!
I know my instincts are right!
You fantasize about it too, don't you?!
Remember our little talk
about multiplication?!
D-did we talk about that?!
Um, what's a "top"?
What, indeed?
Definitely not something to
call a sweet girl like you.
No! I just...
The most angelic character can be
full of unbridled passions...
Awaken those passions in a side story and,
oh, how they'd bloom!
What the heck are you making me say?!
Welp...
Looks like I'm king!
I command you to forget what was just said!
You don't want to talk naughty
with me, Seki-senpai?
I do not! Aaaaand forgotten!
You SURE you want to forget it?
What's with you, Shii?
Teru-senpai was a big fan of your writing
when you were in the Writing Club.
That's why she wanted
to make a game with you.
That set the very foundation of this club.
Do you really want to be so callous?
Well...
Which is why I think we should do
a group reading of your old work.
Anthology
I've got your junior high
anthology right here.
You cut that out!
I'd love to hear about the old days!
Sure thing.
Wait a minute...
Fujikawa always had this
angry look on her face.
And Aya talked like a boy
until her third year.
Well you were always shaking like a leaf.
Yeah! Remember home ec in
year five? She totally-
Th-that's too far back!
You went and caused an insurrection...
I guess it's better not to talk about that!
We should pick something nicer...
I know!
Let's talk about love! I'll go first!
I love my daddy so much!
He had so many nice things
to say about our game!
Huh?
I bet you just wanted to brag, Tama-chan!
It'd sound a little crude
if I said it myself...
I don't know if I'm ready for all that yet!
You've got something don't you, Fujikawa-san?
Like your stuff with DTM Research.
Not like what you're thinking!
You know I try my best to be a beauty,
but you get too beautiful,
and no one wants to approach you!
Cut around the 300Hz range...
Of course she's hard to approach...
Add reverb to the pad to open up some space...
Making music with that weird face...
Well, I did get a love letter once,
if you want to hear about that...
Really? That's news to me.
It was around my second year in elementary.
A lot of things went through my head,
but I found it hard to believe
someone would be interested in me...
I thought maybe they had the wrong person.
Or that they lost a bet...
Luring me with sweet nothings
just to break my heart...
I didn't really have a reason to think that,
but maybe someone out there
was tired of having me around...
So I gave it to my teacher.
What do I do, Miss...?
Are you okay?! Is someone bullying you?!
She's so negative! And super cringe-y!
And before I knew it, the party was over.
Maybe one day they'll tell
me about Teru-senpai.
She's the one who founded the club.
Shouldn't you ask them?
That's right!
Seki-senpai told me we
had something of hers...
What is it?!
I'm the king now!
Those look good on you no
matter how you slice it!
I know that.
You're going to take them off?
Didn't you get those from the last Captain?
Even if you don't like them,
you've kept them all this time.
Doesn't that mean they're important?
That's a secret.
I gotta say you wear it best, Honda-chan!
So you showed your dad the game?
Yeah. It's proof of how hard we worked!
The Magic of Stella...
Hm? Did you say something?
Nothing at all.
It sure is nice...
My family's not too open-minded
about subculture stuff...
I remember we got into this big fight
when they told me to throw out my manga...
I told them it wasn't affecting
my grades or anything.
I was so stubborn...
I ended up shouting them down
and now I guess they kind of tolerate it.
I guess I'll have to draw lots of pictures of old guys
to convince my dad if that happens!
Do you think that'll work, Tama-chan?
Sorry, Yumine.
I need to stop in the stationery store!
Then I'll come with you!
It might take some time...
Don't you have a curfew?
Well... I guess we'll have to split up here.
See you later!
Later!
A club that makes doujin games.
A lot of work, and all that crunch time...
It must be hard,
but it has to be good if it makes
Tama-chan smile like that!
I'll take this!
To-do-i-te i-ma-su ka
Akogare shisen tsumasaki senobi
Fu-ra-ra na-ga-sa-re
Muchuu no umi o oyogu
Rurabii
Yurara
I've always felt this way...
I love you!
I need to fix this!
What's wrong?
They're going to make a kid?!
Bet you felt real good
making a fool out of me!
First Memories