The Slack-eyed Night-owl
Shuttle-runners Club...
I've found it!
Their members' website!
Slack-eyed
Night-owl
Shuttle Runners
Topics                     About Us                   Journal
Journal
They don't even have their games on here?!
Are they even trying with this website?!
They don't even know who they have...
How valuable, how wonderful she is!
I'll read them their last
rites, one by one...
Let's find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
Because there's a world where
only love will carry on
Left all alone like that
But you still can't leave it be
Yes or no, it's always hiding
If you could say it was okay
You could think it was okay
Strange that it was just that quick
The feeling of chasing this kind of thrill
Will be more than you could
have imagined yesterday
Hello, make my day
The magic that we all hold
You'll see the greatest
something of your life
We'll find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
There's a world waiting where
only love will carry on
First Memories
That party really was a blast!
Really? Glad to hear it.
You found yourself a good club, Tama-chan!
Your senpai are so nice.
I was a little worried at first,
to tell you the truth...
You're just like my daddy, Yumine!
I guess I could take that as a compliment...
Oh, yeah!
This manga you let me borrow was so good!
Really? Why don't you tell me
what you thought about it later?
I've got to pop into my
club before classes start.
Got it! Good luck!
Yumine and I have been friends
since elementary school.
We ended up in different schools
for junior high, but we ended up
going to the same high school.
She's one of my most special friends.
Lyrics?
Yeah. I've let other people
write them until now,
but I've got Teru-senpai asking me
to turn one of my tunes into a whole song.
It's not like you can't
just spit one out, is it?
No way.
The good vibes haven't hit me just yet.
Well we're going to need you on the next one.
We're fleshing out ideas right now.
I'll think of you as long as I can.
Give me the power to stir your heart...
Did those vibes hit you?
Yesterday was my first
manga binge in a while...
It was like they turned the pain of
hiding your love into a work of art...
Wait. Is that Fujikawa-senpai?
You were my everything...
Even if fate should leave you without me,
know that I've always loved you.
Oh! Hey, Honda-chan!
Um... Just now...
Oh, I was just writing
some lyrics to my senpai.
Your senpai?
They're really important to me, so I want to
do my best even if it's not all that great.
Senpai...
I love you!
Well, they'll definitely
understand how you feel!
Hm?
There it is! Why don't you help me out?
What?
You want ME to help you?
Why not?
We're going to have to get started on
making the next thing once I'm done with this.
You're telling your senpai how you feel?!
And who's next?!
Who?
I guess...
...Seki-san?
You mean forbidden love?!
I love you!
I mean...
if it's a girl, I don't think you can
just go with anybody!
Wha...
Anyway, think you could
come to my classroom at lunch?
Fujikawa-senpai's trying
to find her way to love!
I need to help her!
I... I don't have much
experience, but I'll try!
I want to hear all about your love life!
Like father-daughter stuff.
I love you!
I love my daddy!
I don't know if that's relevant!
I mean, it might get a little complicated!
But don't you think a sticky, difficult,
hopeless production might have more impact?
Man stealer!
You're not supposed to do that!
I really don't know if this is okay...
Wonder what's got Tama-chan so worried?
Here.
A note!
A young lady in love, perhaps? You okay?
A young lady
in love, perhaps?
You okay?
She's sharp...
Fujikawa-senpai's in a
sticky love situation
and I have to help her.
It's over for you!
You've gotten too close to my senpai...
You've saved me, Honda-chan.
Just what I needed...
That little, blonde...
Makes me a little jealous how into the zone
you get when you're composing.
Really?
It's not like a kid couldn't
make the same stuff I do.
Maybe I just don't have the grit for it.
Grit...
Maybe it's better to say I've got the love.
Even if it stresses me out,
I'll put my life into it, you know?
She...
She's so cool!
But you know it's not that easy
to make a living in a creative field...
Let's forget about me becoming a pro...
We're talking about my
attitude towards music.
Like, a lot of the time I can't even sleep
with all the stuff running through my head.
Don't you think that's a little reckless?
You need your sleep.
This is all for nothing
if you don't stay healthy.
You need to take a cool
look at the big picture.
I'll be fine.
The Newlywed
Fujikawa-senpai's really fired up,
The Canny Missus
but the Captain's really calm...
Oh!
Honda-san!
Whatever she picks, I
think it'll be wonderful!
Huh?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Why don't we talk in DTM Research's room?
Sure!
DTM
Research
Well, then. C'mon in!
Er... are we making it now?
That we are.
A child, that is.
Examining Love
Poetry
Here? I mean, I'm a girl and-
That's fine. Just take a seat.
Boy, girl, does it really matter?
That's right. There was a scene like this
in the scenario my senpai gave me...
Your feelings, placed
within a cramped cell...
A deceitful tryst, masking
the pain of it all...
Wh-what are you doing?!
What are you putting on me?!
I need to fix this!
Fujikawa-senpai uses this room for both clubs,
and I'm all alone in here with her!
Hm? Did you have a question?
You and me are making one, right?
A kid, I mean...
That's right.
But since we're making it for my senpai,
it'll probably end up theirs anyway.
Now where'd that scenario go?
That sounds like a pretty
complicated family...
I mean, it might cause trouble or...
You're saying it's even
better when it's sticky?
No it isn't!
And Murakami-san did give me
a pretty good tongue lashing.
Told me I need to take a cool look-
And why wouldn't you?!
But anyway, how about we
get down to the making?
I...
Um...
Let's start by having you take
a look at the scenario...
No!
Whoops... sorry!
Tama-chan!
Yumine!
Huh? What's wrong?
She...
She's on day-shift today!
She's got stuff to do, so bye!
Honda-chan!
You okay, Tama-chan?!
Yeah. I kind of feel like
I got the wrong idea...
What idea?
Fujikawa-senpai was talking
about a scenario...
I think I get it!
I think she meant that for her,
her songs are like her own kids.
Kids?! Who's talking about kids?!
Well she said we should make a kid together.
And I got all flustered...
It's all your fault, Senpai...
Playing with my emotions like that...
Are you sure your emotions are
the only thing you want played with?
I! AM! NOT! FANTASIZING! ABOUT!
MY FRIEND! BEING A MAN!
DARN THESE CONDITIONED REFLEXES!
Yumine...
I may not have all the information,
but I'm on your side!
Uh, sure...
Thank you...
And after that...
All the misunderstandings were cleared up,
and I was so relieved...
But I'm glad Yumine was
so worried about me...
And now that I think about it, Yumine's the
whole reason I got into making games.
We did visit the SNS Club at the PR event.
But that's not all...
There was a time I thought
of making my own games
before I even thought of joining the club.
Back then...
I think we'll let Tamaki
Honda take care of that...
Honda-san?
I'm listening, ma'am!
We'll have none of that window gazing.
Would you mind delivering today's worksheets?
Er... where?
I knew you weren't paying attention!
To Fuda-san's house...
You live in the same neighborhood, don't you?
Yumine Fuda...
Fuda-san and I were in
kindergarten together...
But she was always sick,
so she spent a lot of time in the clinic.
Really...
And when she was there
she mostly just played by herself.
She's kinda hard to talk to.
She's probably not a fan of crowds.
It's kind of like she's stuck in
her own world or something.
It's gonna be hard for
her in elementary school
if she doesn't learn how to be more social.
Honda-san? What're you staring at?
I didn't mean to!
Maybe Yumine and I can be friends?
Just letting you know
it might be pretty hard.
Go straight that way and
you'll get to her house.
See you tomorrow!
See you!
People always called me spacey...
I thought there was a chance
Yumine and I would get along.
I'm Yumine's friend, Tamaki Honda!
I was hoping she could play!
Welcome! Go right on up!
Coming in!
Is there something you want?
Hi, Yumine-chan! I, um...
I brought you your worksheets!
You could've left them at
the door with my mom...
What's this? She said she
came to play with you.
Make yourself at home!
Sure!
Nice to meet you! I'm Tamaki Honda!
Hey, how about we play something?
Wha... No.
I'm sick, so I can't play outside.
Plus I'm playing a game right now.
Okay! Then I'll just draw!
I can't relax...
Honda-chan! Are you having dinner here?
I'm eating at home today!
Look at the time!
I get to have dinner with my daddy today!
Bye, Yumine-chan!
We should play again tomorrow!
"Again"? Did we play today?
Hello!
I'm coming in!
You were out today again
weren't you, Yumine-chan!
Well I don't want to go to school.
And I kind of have a fever.
I thought about it, and you and I
didn't really play yesterday...
She finally noticed...
So today...
Tada!
I told my granny and she let me
bring my gaming device!
How old is that thing?
I've never even seen that one.
But why?! It's a small gaming
device and everything!
And exactly what software
were you planning on playing?
Soft? Like softball?
Okay! We can talk, then!
Today I was eating my bento with my friends,
Nozomi-chan and Karin-chan!
Nozomi-chan really hates green peppers,
so she said she'd give them to us...
Clinic
Yumine-chan's kinda hard
to talk to, isn't she?
It's like she's all gloomy or something...
Sick kids always get to be the teacher's pet.
And I don't like them, either...
But Karin-chan said you
just have to get used to
them and then they're really
good so I tried them and-
Go away...
Huh?
Go away!
I don't want to hear about friends!
Hey, Nozomi-chan, why are we friends?
Are you talking philosophically?
The Game of Life
Philosophic...
Well, we sat close to each other.
We ate lunch together...
Then we started talking and playing together.
Looks like you’ll be
repeating a year.
Take a break.
Life as an intern
sure is hard!
Take a break.
Look who's got a job at a big company!
Lucky! I'm not getting anything!
I can't really play with Yumine...
And I couldn't talk to her either.
I've been getting ones this whole time...
What do I do?
Hey, Honda-san!
How about you roll the dice for now?
Oh, that's right!
Always so spacey...
Lemme play!
Sure!
It's so cool when you can bring something
you can play inside on a rainy day.
We're only allowed to play at lunch
and after school, though...
Maybe I could play board games at her house?
Happy birthday!
Collect $30,000
from each player.
But if you're too pushy you
might just annoy her...
Plus this is a game you're supposed to play
with lots of people.
Are there any board games
you can play with two people?
Maybe shogi?
Or go or chess?
But I don't know the
rules for any of those...
Oh...
Here's an idea: Why not
just make one of your own?
So I went home, took out my notebook,
and drew up a board game.
It wasn't as pretty as one
you could buy in a store,
but I gave it my best shot with
little letters and everything-
Yumine-chan!
Let's play!
So, I roll the dice again?
W-wait!
I just had to wait five turns
'cause I was struck by lightning and now...
I have to go back eight spaces?!
Don't ask me!
Didn't you make these dice?
W-well, yeah...
But I didn't think I'd stop
on all these bad spaces...
You're so weird, Honda-san...
Bifco
After that, I started putting the
games I thought up in my notebook
TAKE A WALK
WITH A BEAR
START
TAKE A CANDY
and playing them with Yumine.
I tried lots of things.
The idea that someone would
play something I made,
and that it made them laugh that much...
I thought it was just the
most wonderful thing.
Why's this piece look like an old man?
I thought it would be kinda cool...
Good morning!
Yumine started smiling more.
She started coming to school more, too.
And she had more friends.
Wow! You sure do know a lot about
manga and games, Yumine-chan!
Hey, d'you think we could
come play at your house?
Sure! I can let you borrow some manga
if you want to read them!
Really?! Awesome!
Thanks, Yumine-chan!
Who knew she was this much fun?
I brought a new game today!
I borrowed Yumine's handheld
gaming device, too.
And it's all thanks to her
that I started drawing.
I really like the main
character in this manga.
They're just too cool!
I dunno... Their dad is so much better!
And then...
I've made up my mind!
My next characters are going to be
sticky, sticky BL brutes!
Is the Illustration Club going to let you
draw that in their books?
I'll convince the editor-in-chief to let me!
You just go home without me, Tama-chan!
Whoa?! Yumine?!
Yumine ran off, so I'm
heading home alone today.
She seems to be having a
lot of fun in her club.
It makes me happy to see
that, for some reason.
Games are the reason she
and I became friends,
and led to my meeting the
Captain and my senpai.
Maybe making games means
I'll be friends with even more people...
Wha...?! Who are you?
I've finally found your little hideout!
After SOMEONE said they were going out
to test their skills against other people!
Bet you felt real good
making a fool out of me!
What?! Who the heck are you?!
Have they reached you?
Longing gazes, standing on tiptoes
Washed away, reeling
Swimming through a sea of dreams
A lullaby
Swaying
You and I are having a bout, right now!
Why does she look so serious?
Probably better not to reveal my identity...
It's sautéed burdock!
Debugging is Serious Business