It's early, but the rainy
season is in full swing.
Oolong
Tea
Plum and
Cherry Blossom
Habanero
I pick a hot drink today.
The stray cat greets me on my way to school.
It's a day like any other.
But I guess I could say my kouhai Honda-san
and I are getting along a bit better.
It's been three months since
my appointment as Captain...
I feel like I'm getting
into the rhythm of it...
Captain!
Honda-san? What's wrong?
Captain...
If I couldn't draw anymore,
would you guys hate me?
Would you say you don't need me?
W-well...
You wouldn't leave me, would you?
Would you still be my Captain?
Let's find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
Honda-san...
This isn't the place for all of that.
Let's get you to school!
Because there's a world where
only love will carry on
Did she make her cry?
And such an adorable girl, too...
Maybe it's a lover's spat...
Left all alone like that
But you still can't leave it be
Yes or no, it's always hiding
If you could say it was okay
You could think it was okay
Strange that it was just that quick
The feeling of chasing this kind of thrill
Will be more than you could
have imagined yesterday
Hello, make my day
The magic that we all hold
You'll see the greatest
something of your life
We'll find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
There's a world waiting where
only love will carry on
Skill Up, Part 2
A slump?
Yeah, I kept thinking of how much better
that girl was at drawing than me...
Now I can't draw...
And I had a nightmare this morning...
You can't draw, Tamaki Honda!
The SNS Club is done with you!
Yaaay! Yaaay!
Sorry, Honda-san.
We choose to be with her.
Wait, Captain!
Wait! Please don't leave me!
C-Captain?! Is that blood?!
I-I'm okay.
Went down the wrong hole...
Plum and
Cherry Blossom
Habanero
What should I tell her?
"You'll be out of that slump in no time?"
That'd be a bald-faced lie...
I don't know that for sure.
Why don't you start by getting
her out of your head?
We've got those aptitude
tests coming up, after all.
Okay. I'll try...
I think I might've given her bad advice...
Programmers don't even have slumps...
Maybe Fujikawa-san or Aya
could've done better...
Hey! Listen up, everybody!
Stardust Desires is such a work of art,
I think future generations
should know about it!
Aya would drop dead if she saw this...
Minaha-chan?!
What are you doing in my classroom?
A mere coincidence, Tamaki Honda.
A battle demands not only
strength, but good allies...
Which is why I've been singing
the gospel of this book!
The Cat's Pen Collective
(Issue 28)
Don't tell me you're here to battle me again?
Oh, no... I've come for something big-
Hey!
What are you doing to Tama-chan?!
Yumine?!
Ha-san! Being little miss
self-important in the
Illustration Club wasn't
enough for you, was it?!
Now you have to come after Tama-chan!
What'd I do?!
And let me say this...
Hikono-kun gets passed around.
Okay, okay... How about
we stop with the fighting?
You! I can't believe you!
Wha...? There is only the
pure love of Oji x Hiko!
That's straight from the artist!
You are so naïve, reading
all that extra stuff.
Oh, Yumine knows her since
they're in the same club...
Why don't you stick to canon?!
And she calls her Ha-chan
since her name is Minaha!
And why are you using "chan," Tamaki Honda?!
Don't you think you're being too-
Okay, okay. Let's get you
back to your classroom.
I'm really sorry for the ruckus, Captain...
Hm?
Class is starting, Tama-chan!
Honda-san seems to have a lot of friends.
I'm sure she'll be fine.
She didn't even need to ask me for help...
Morning, Shii!
I couldn't give her good advice...
I think I might've even
made the problem worse...
Maybe there was another way
to make her feel better...
We probably shouldn't have
invited her into the club...
Wha?
Slumps happen to everybody...
Not that it's not a big
deal when you're in one.
I hope she gets out of it...
Well, we can have a good talk
when she comes to the club room.
And if she doesn't?
I think that's about enough
of the negative forecasts.
Yo!
S..Seki-senpai!
You're not coming in, Honda-san?
Well, I don't think it's right for me
to come in right now...
I mean... I tried to draw...
But all of my drawings turned out like this!
Not really sure what's different...
Hey, Honda-san...
Do you like me?
I do like you.
I thought you looked really cool
working so hard during crunch time...
Is it... is it okay if I like you?
If you like someone there's
nothing wrong with telling them.
You worked hard then, and
you're working hard now.
That's what I like about you.
What happened to the
Honda-san from back then?
She's still here, and her right hand
is still working, isn't it?
Right.
Then you'll be out of that slump in no time.
That's right! You haven't
had lunch yet, have you?
I made a little too much.
You can have some if you want.
Wow, are you sure?
I'm no match for her...
That was so good!
I need to get back to class now...
Alright, see you after school!
See you later!
Captain...
Hm?
I feel like you'd do a much
better job than I could.
Aw, no way...
I mean, you're the one who's good
with the nitty-gritty, Shii.
That's why I respect you,
even with stuff like this.
You take care of the scheduling,
you plan stuff for the whole year.
Oh, about that...
I need to tell you about Summer Comiket-
There's just one more thing.
Smile a little more and you'll be perfect!
Oh, dear me. I do believe
we're behind schedule.
Who is THAT supposed to be?!
Don't say that. All you need's a smile!
You're creeping me out.
Lunch is almost over, Ha-chan!
Do not call me Ha-chan! I'm
a first year, same as you!
What? You are?!
What did you think I was?!
Hm? Did you forget something, Honda-san?
Sorry for the ruckus.
Ha-chan said she wanted to
come to the club room.
You're a sneaky one, aren't you?!
I wanted to meet the great Iris...
Is that the girl from before?
Kind of hard to tell without my glasses...
Don't tell me YOU'RE Iris?!
W-well... I am. Possibly...
Who is she supposed to be?
Your book is my bible, Ma'am!
Could you please sign it?!
Oh, but of course!
This is so great...
I've made up my mind. I'm
joining the SNS Club!
I want to make a game out of your story!
What?!
Y-you can't just decide for yourself!
Besides, I'm the artist!
Oh, listen to Honda-san!
No! I want to do the art!
I want to make the game!
I've dreamed and dreamed of
making something with the great Iris!
Well, what if you did the art together?
You wouldn't need to fight then.
Wha-
Is it okay for us to do that?
Well, if you can do the same style of coloring,
multiple artists shouldn't be a-
Hold on!
Wait, I say!
You wish to make a game
based on such an old story?
You believe that Iris, the living storyteller,
would permit such a thing?!
I say!
Is there anything I can do?!
I've always loved your work!
But my love, my efforts have
yet to reach their peak!
My heart hurts...
What was it you said, "If you like someone
there's nothing wrong with telling them?"
Curse you...
That's right... I say!
We won't be able to show off
anything new we make because
we're out of Summer Comiket!
There's no need for us to work
faster than we have to...
About that...
we've been talking to a circle Fujikawa-san
is friendly with about
selling our games together.
That means that we might be able to
have our game at Summer Comiket...
Is that true?!
That's such good news!
But it's in two months.
That's going to be a pretty tough schedule.
In which case I have no qualms
with increasing our staff.
And two artists would cut
Honda-san's workload in half.
Plus, since we already have a finished story,
we won't have a bottleneck
trying to work out the plot.
Fine. Very well! You have my approval.
Then that's that.
Stardust Desires
by Iris
Our new game for Summer Comiket
will be Stardust Desires.
However! Your entry into this club hinges on
your meeting my expectations!
You work with Honda-san,
even after the game is finished!
Can you manage that?
Yes! I'll do my best!
Seki-senpai?!
That worked out well.
The SNS Club is going to Summer Comiket,
and it seems like things are going to be
different from now on.
Actually, what is Summer Comiket all about?
Summer Comiket?
Well, it's a huge doujin convention
they hold during the summer.
They've got all sorts of different
industries there with
people coming from all over the world.
Wow, that sounds really amazing.
If I dilly-dally, Ha-chan might end up
doing all of the artwork...
I need to work hard!
Good morning!
Good... huh?
Er... Yumine?
Hm?
Since when was a beautiful
girl like that in our class?
Oh! That's Marika!
I read something that changed me...
Stardust Desires
(Act 1)
by Iris
I'm going to live the stardust
life from here on out!
You've changed another
person's life, Seki-senpai!
Note: Yamato Nadeshiko is the feminine ideal of Japan.
It perfectly describes the Yamato Nadeshiko
that every young girl should aspire to be, I say.
That's what it's about?!
Um... I think you might want
to keep that under wraps.
You know, make sure it's a secret...
But why?! It's such a good story!
Seki-senpai wouldn't be
happy if people find out.
It's probably better not
to mention her by name.
W-well, it wouldn't be good for a
Yamato Nadeshiko to have too many rivals!
Oh, I get it! I'll be extra careful.
Inbox
You have a new message
Receiving message...
Inbox
Yumine Fuda
A girl in my class says that Seki-senpai
described the Yamato Nadeshiko
every girl should aspire to be
in one of her old stories!
A girl in my class says
that Seki-senpai described
the Yamato Nadeshiko every girl should
aspire to be in one of her old stories!
It looks really good, though! It's so silky!
Thank you kindly!
I had to get up at five
this morning to do it!
So I'm super sleepy!
That's amazing!
Must be hard being a Nadeshiko...
As long as you're here, mind if I sketch you?
Hit me with it!
I guess I should, too...
What should I do with my face?
Should I make it like a shoujo manga?
No, you can just make a normal one.
She doesn't seem too
different on the inside...
Beauties looking back!
Oh, are you sketching her?
Oh... Yeah...
Isn't her right arm kind of off?
Y-you're right. You know
how to draw, Iino-san?
Well, my little sister
knows a thing or two...
Hey!
Would you stop trying to peek?!
You know this is a sketch, right?!
I wasn't moving! Just
stretching my neck, is all!
A Yamato Nadeshiko? I don't know...
But her hair really is pretty.
Must be because she's a half...
Being half's got nothing to do with it!
You're beautiful, Honda-san!
You're a Yamato Nadeshiko!
I'm really not!
Plus I'm kind of having
a bad hair day today...
Do you like to wear your
hair long, Honda-san?
Yup. I want to be a beautiful lady!
My mommy used to wear her hair long,
and I thought my daddy might
like it if I did, too...
Alright, then! Let's switch!
You're embarrassing me!
Hold on, Tama-chan!
Do you think you could make a face like
the ecstasy of a boy just before he
playfully teases another boy?
I've never done anything like that!
I-I'll never be a bride, Daddy...
Okay, okay. How about you settle down?
Fine, then. Could you
help her out, Marika-san?
Got it!
Cheer up!
Try holding Marika-san's tie
all cool-like, Tama-chan!
Um...
L-like this?
We're like the prince and the princess!
Looking good, girls!
You don't think that's a little unrealistic?
Class is starting, people!
Thanks, Tama-chan!
Aw, I wish you could've
added some more detail!
You're a pretty good artist, Shimizu-san!
Thank you kindly! There it is!
This is why they called me Alstroemeria des
Concours D'arts in elementary school!
Not Yamato Nadeshiko?
Isn't she a better artist than you?
I mean, you can't even-
Honda-san?
What's wrong?
Iino-san? How do I draw better?
You're asking ME?
You said something about your sister...
Oh, well my sister...
It's like whenever I look
at her, she's drawing.
I see...
It's like studying.
If you like it and you keep doing it,
you'll probably get better.
Er... even in class?
Oh, this just makes my notes
a little easier on the eyes.
Actually, I can kind of tell a sketch is off
even if I'm just looking
over someone's shoulder.
Really...
Tell me, Honda-san.
Have you just been copying manga up to now?
How did you know?
Oh, just a hunch.
It really is like studying, though.
Even if you're bad at it or
don't like it, you gotta do it.
Right, for example...
Like when you tell yourself,
"I'm gonna pay attention in class!"
SNS
Club
I can start getting better by drawing
one more picture than I usually do.
You see that? You and me have
completely different styles.
Wha...?! What are you doing here?
I'm here to return a book
Murakami-senpai let me borrow.
It's like she said, "it's not going to look strange
or weird if our coloring matches."
What's matching coloring?
Coloring is coloring.
Like, digitally coloring!
Don't tell me you don't even know that?
I think they told me about it at camp.
But with the game we made
they just used my pictures as-is.
That makes sense, actually...
Ha-chan! I have something I want to ask you!
You're going to want to
keep the shading simple.
Now you make a copy of the
sketch layer and put it on top.
Okay...
Then you use a smudged brush to
add some reddish-orange to the bangs...
It gives it a nice, fuzzy feel.
I didn't know you could do that!
And last, I guess they're kind of highlights,
but adding a white border around the hair
can really change the whole look.
Thought you might be in here!
Hello!
Looks like you two are doing
some serious research.
Feeling more chummy?
Wh-why would we?!
Well we brought some good news!
Temawari-san's letting us
put our game in her booth.
Temawari-san, she's pretty famous, right?
That's the one Yumine really, really likes.
But we're going to have to help her sell.
Really?! Then the great Iris' new game
is going to be on the world stage!
I don't have time for this!
You'd better hurry and get those skills up!
Sorry to say, but this is it
for our club meeting today.
The school's closing early today.
What?
But why?
"Why?"
We've got tests tomorrow.
It completely slipped my mind.
We've got tests tomorrow, don't we?
They're just aptitude tests.
I'll figure something out.
But now it feels like I'm not that bad
an artist compared to Ha-chan.
It's impossible for me to learn
how to color on my own, though...
Character Pose Collection
Basic Poses
A Guide to Being
a Better Artist
It's like Iino-san said...
I've just copied manga until now,
I never paid much attention to sketching.
Sketching...
This screen might be a little
too small for sketching.
Let me transfer it.
There's the file...
Now print...
Tama-chan!
I've got loquats if you'd like some?
S-sorry granny!
I think I'm fine for now!
Drawing yourself is harder than I thought!
I'm not even pretty!
Plus I'm kind of stumpy...
Wish I was taller...
And why are my hands so rough?!
Is it from drawing all those old guys?!
O-okay, one more picture and
then I'll hit the books!
I'll try a harder pose this time!
I ended up drawing until I fell asleep.
But it's fine. The tests aren't
on any specific chapters!
How much did you study, Yumine?
Don't talk to me. I'm trying to keep
these formulas in my head!
Maybe I should take another
look at my notes...
Honda-san...
You didn't mean to send a photo
anywhere you shouldn't have, did you?
Good work! We've got classics next, don't we?
Those math questions we
had, I reviewed those.
I really should've studied a little more.
Time to switch gears, Tama-chan!
Nothing more important than gear switching!
Humans have limits, you know?
A flower's beauty's in its evanescence!
Was it hard getting your hair to do that?
What?
Too happy and embarrassed to study after getting
all those texts talking about your writing?
Oh, my...
Have they reached you?
Longing gazes, standing on tiptoes
Washed away, reeling
Swimming through a sea of dreams
A lullaby
Swaying
Oh, Iris!
Thanks for the text!
Promise!
You did what?
Whatever mother wishes me to do, I'll do.
Precision Machines