Previously on
Space Brothers
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
Born under a lucky star, younger brother Hibito becomes the first Japanese moonwalker.
A lunar accident has left Hibito struggling on the sidelines, suffering from a panic disorder.
But he's able to pass a test to return to active duty.
Older brother Mutta continues his long quest to the moon,
having finally been selected as a
backup member for a lunar mission.
And he's about to begin training for the moon.
Hey, Hibito... Can you hear me?
Huh? Yeah...
Wait, who is that?
Come on, Hibito...
We ate silkworms together.
Buddy!
I'll be taking over as CAPCOM.
First, watch out for the gondola above you.
Why?
You have to ask why?
EVAs are supposed to be done with a partner.
Congratulations, Hibito!
Great job!
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that thick veil aside
#92 Lonely People
There were a few close calls, but he aced the test!
Hibito's a true samurai boy.
I wish you could have seen him...
Yeah, I expected as much.
And don't forget that I'm the samurai boy's big brother.
Once you got home, did you give Hibito a celebratory hug?
A big hug!
Now look here, Lowry...
In Japan, brothers don't hug.
Unless we're talking about a miraculous reunion,
after being separated as children twenty years earlier.
That's too bad...
Everyone else gave Hibito hugs.
Everyone else?
Including Karen and Olivia?
Of course.
Seriously?
Hibito, you lucky bastard.
I wanna take a test like him...
By the way, will this be your first time meeting the rest of the backup crew?
Huh?
Y-Yeah.
It isn't set in stone...
Everyone involved with CES-62 should come this way.
Well, my crew's meeting over there.
Space Man!
Sorry, Lowry...
In Japanese, that really just means "alien".
Andy!
Hey.
Oops...
You're also on the CES-62 backup crew?
Yes.
So am I! I can't wait to work together!
I guess the other crew members are already here.
One of them is right next to you.
Huh?
You knew these were headphones?
Wait! You're Hibito's brother!
Yah, man! Yah, man!
Yah, man!
Yah, man...
My father was Jamaican, my mother American, and I was born in Argentina.
The name's Philippe Louis.
I grew up in Argentina and Brazil, and now I'm enjoying life in Houston, USA.
I see...
That explains your sunny disposition.
Yah, man!
Okay, everyone's here?
Welcome to the Desert RATS training for CES-62.
I see some gloomy faces.
I've been named this group's training instructor.
I'm a geologist, George McGuire.
Giant and dreads!
You're astronauts, right?
Yes.
Yah, man!
I thought so.
I am able to accurately analyze both rocks and people.
Both of you, step forward.
Next...
You there, with the ugly hat!
You must be an astronaut.
Looks like you're talking about me...
Bingo.
I knew it.
Step forward.
Yes, yes...
I must obey my destiny.
I guess I just have the aura of an astronaut.
And who's next?
I am.
Sorry, but I didn't feel like waiting for you to find me.
You?
If you hadn't stepped forward, I would have identified you.
There should be one more.
Hey.
One more backup astronaut...
Who is it?
I'm right here... Right here!
Come on, look at me.
Hey! Over here!
Hey!
Is it you?
No, it isn't.
Hey, who is that?!
Is it you, then?
No.
It must be you.
It isn't.
What about you?
No.
Then, you.
Nope.
You.
No.
Thought so.
So it must be you.
It's not.
Could it be you?
Yes, it is...
As always, I was right.
Now step forward.
That counts as being right?
Okay, we have our five astronauts.
I'm sorry to say that I couldn't see the aura of an astronaut coming from you.
Huh?
Yah, man!
Ladies and gentleman, pay close attention.
The five astronauts standing before you
will be your responsibility.
They are the CES-62 backup crew.
It isn't set in stone...
But the backup crew members you train with
are very likely to be the crew members with whom you'll go into space.
These are the people I'll be going to the moon with.
And...
There's a beautiful lady!
I feel so lucky!
Okay, other groups would hold an orientation session now,
but I believe in practical training.
Let's head out!
North Arizona Black Point Lava Flow Training Grounds
Barren earth, craters,
treacherous cliffs, steep slopes,
extreme temperature swings between day and night,
dried-up riverbeds, and clouds of dust with every step.
Well? Are you excited now?
It's as good as a theme park.
Well...
I'm pretty sure a theme park would be more fun.
But I'm one of the weirdos who can get excited about barren desert.
Look.
It's the prime crew of CES-62.
They started training three days ago.
Hey, Vince!
Wow, they all look important...
Hey, backup crew members!
Let's train hard!
Yes!
Yah, man!
Okay, time to unleash my dreads!
Huh? The prime crew has six members?
Then we're one short.
Is that supposed to happen?
It's so hot...
And it's supposed to be December?
I must thank the heat!
Yeah, this woman is built...
A heart tattoo... On her left shoulder!
Just like Apo!
Funny thing...
Eh?
My pet dog also has a heart-shaped mark on his left shoulder.
Oh? Really?
I think we'll get along great.
Indeed.
Yes, that is definitely
not what would happen!
Who wants to be compared to a dog?
I almost screwed up.
What are you looking at?
Want me to sock you?
N-No, s-sorry...
Sh-She's strong.
She's really strong!
And scary.
You're such a fool...
You can't stare at Betty for longer than two seconds.
Why do you think they would assign a beautiful woman like her to a crew full of men?
It's because she's manlier than the rest of us.
Whoa.
Okay, here we are!
Thanks for driving safely.
But it turns out that any idiot can drive this thing safely.
This would place last in a Formula 1.
But it rules on the moon.
Hello, everyone...
I'm Tully.
Nice to meet you all.
So, I'm supposed to teach you how to operate this thing.
But I imagine that some of you already know how it works, right?
Am I right?
As you know, this is the SEV, also known as the Beetle.
It cost seven billion dollars to develop!
On my salary, I couldn't afford that in a thousand lifetimes.
Well, if I become a Hollywood star in my next life, I might have a chance...
Yes! I have hope!
Tully, stop getting sidetracked.
Oh, of course...
Sorry, George.
Damn that ape.
You're the distraction here.
Keep your mouth shut!
That's why your wife left you.
Not that I have a wife.
In my next life, I hope to be myself again.
The tires can turn 360 degrees, so it can move sideways, like a crab.
There are living quarters inside, so it's like a lunar RV.
Does everyone like to camp?
I hate it.
You already know that the spacesuits attach to the back, right?
Right now, they're inside the glove.
Oh, the glove is this cover.
Reminds you of larva, yes?
Its purpose is to protect spacesuits from regolith.
It's a convenient tool, but astronauts hate using it...
Honestly, do they realize how hard we're working on their behalf?
Does anyone have any questions?
Nope... Of course.
Okay, raise the glove.
There they are!
Spacesuits for walking on the moon!
I'm about to put one on?
It's finally time!
You'll start by learning to put the spacesuit on.
Who wants to go first?
Then, I'll go first.
Hold on...
Huh? What is it?
And that is exactly your problem.
Betty...
You should have the honor of going first.
I appreciate it, Carlo.
But you're still a chauvinist pig.
Yeah, oink oink.
I didn't want you to wear the spacesuit first.
After all, you probably don't wash those dreads.
I wash them! Once every five days!
Five days?
These guys are so noisy...
Don't just stand there like a moai...
Tell that sleazeball off, man.
You should wash them every day.
You go first.
O-Okay.
What's up with this team?
Take a sniff... They don't smell!
No way.
Pathetic.
Keep it down! There are two more spacesuits!
I can't see myself going to space with them.
The CES-62 prime crew features a strong lineup...
Angus, Bold, Larry, and Tara.
They should do just fine.
However, the sub crew concerns me.
What do you mean?
The sub crew is comprised of some unique characters.
With his silence and giant size, Andy Tyler can scare people off.
Betty Rain's aggressive tone and behavior makes it seem as though she's keeping people away.
Carlo Greco is disliked because of his haughty demeanor.
Philippe Louis is usually too loud and happy for everyone else.
I understand... This could be a problem.
Unfortunately, no one wants to go to space with them.
That's why we ended up putting them together.
We assigned the lonely astronauts to the same team,
and then we added Nanba Mutta.
Whether this works or not will be a gamble.
And with one more person,
the captain of the crew,
it just might work.
Do you know who you'll turn to?
Yes.
When I sent an e-mail, I was turned down...
But I have a candidate.
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#93 In the Corner of My Heart
If he agrees to be captain of Nanba Mutta's team, it just might work.
Meanwhile, Sharon has come to Houston.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"In the Corner of My Heart"
Mr. Hibbit!
What's going on?
Fire detected in Module 5.
Fire-suppression system is malfunctioning.
Possibility of explosion.
Don't we need to get out of here?
But we can't leave until Beetle finishes charging.
So we have nowhere to run?
Isn't there anything we can do?
Let's find a way!
Everyone, it's time to combine our powers!
Use whatever you've got.
Freddy Dog can provide experience and leadership.
Damian Hawk provides technical expertise.
Buddy Gorilla provides brawn.
Red Panda Linda and Karen Cat provide knowledge and support.
It's time to unite...
I'll let you guys handle this!
Wait up, Hibbit...
Are you going to Module 5 alone?
It's too dangerous.
Someone has to go and stop the place from exploding!
But...
Let me do this!
All I can provide is courage and energy!
Yay!
H-Hibbit!
Don't go, Hibbit!
See you next week!