Previously on
Space Brothers
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
Born under a lucky star, younger brother Hibito becomes the first Japanese moonwalker.
Older brother Mutta continues on his long quest to the moon,
having finally been selected as a
backup member for a lunar mission.
Meanwhile, a lunar accident has left Hibito struggling on the sidelines,
suffering from a panic disorder.
But he's about to take a test to return to active duty.
He must pass the test, or he will never go back to space.
My temperature regulation system is busted.
I'm not getting enough water...
My body is freezing.
Well, let's go.
Hibito's gonna run out of oxygen!
Stay calm, Buddy...
We made it out, Damian!
Freddy! Buddy! This is Hibito!
Karen! Linda! Do you read me?
Eight minutes of oxygen left...
Eight minutes, huh?
Damn!
It's time...
Am I gonna die?
My body is burning up...
The doctors believe that the helmet's confined space is triggering the panic attacks.
I'm going to find a way to get rid of this disorder.
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that hot veil aside
#91 How to Help Hibito
This will greatly reduce the time required for various tasks.
Eh, he'll be fine...
Say, Hibito...
If you stay ahead of Mutta and lead the way,
Mutta will be right behind you.
If you ever stop,
I'm certain
Mutta will give you a push from behind.
I've opened the DCM purge valve, but the warning hasn't stopped.
Since I won't be able to perform my assignment, I'm heading for the airlock.
The test is being called off?
He's expected to stop.
Is everything all right with the CO2 inside his spacesuit?
It must be another green card that asked for a warning to come up.
But it isn't the green card I requested.
His heart rate has slowed somewhat.
I was worried that he might suffer an attack...
You really hung in there, Hibito...
This is Gates's doing...
He issued an unnecessary card, causing the test to be canceled...
Mission Control, this is Gates.
Yes.
I'm issuing a green card to have a CO2 sensor malfunction warning displayed on the HUD of Hibito's helmet.
Are you sure about that?
Just do it.
Chief...
It seems they want to talk to you.
You're...
I'm in the airlock.
I'll hook up my spacesuit to the umbilical cord.
Okay, Hibito.
This is harder than you'd think.
Be patient, Hibito.
I'm hooked up.
Good!
Okay, the warning's gone!
Once I confirm everything is fine, I'll head back out.
Roger that, Hibito.
Pretty Dog...
Never thought this would help more than drugs.
Hey, Hibito... Can you hear me?
Huh? Yeah...
Wait, who is that?
Dude... You don't know who this is?
Come on, Hibito...
We ate silkworms together.
Buddy!
I heard everything from Mutta.
So I decided to come and watch your test today.
And right now, I have a pretty lady with me.
Hello, Hibito. Are you doing well?
Karen...
Freddy and Linda are currently working overseas, so they couldn't make it.
We told them what's going on.
They're praying that you'll pass the test.
You have support all around the world.
Okay, Hibito.
I just swiped the manual from Mission Control.
I'll be taking over as CAPCOM.
Are you sure about letting his friends handle this, Chief?
Wasn't the purpose of this test to put Hibito under pressure, to see if a panic attack would result?
Yes, that was my intent.
But after hearing what they had to say, I changed my mind.
First, you need to open the hatch and go outside.
Time for a lunar stroll.
Okay, Buddy!
Don't trip and fall, Hibito.
This feels very familiar.
Head straight for the solar panel Sunflower.
Got it.
Hold on. First, watch out for the gondola above you.
Gondola?
Why?
You have to ask why, Hibito?
EVAs are supposed to be done with a partner.
Damian...
You came, too?
You bet.
How could I not...
Well, let's get started, Hibito.
No need to worry about falling off a cliff on this moon.
What is the purpose of this exercise?
Are we testing Hibito?
Or are we helping him?
I'd hoped to accomplish the latter,
but it seems I had the wrong method.
Isolating Hibito,
forcing him to overcome pressure and fear, was incorrect.
Instead, we will help
Hibito remember his happiest moments.
That is how
Hibito's fellow crew members want to help him.
Thanks for coming.
Tomorrow's class will begin at the same time.
Whew, it's finally over...
Hibito's test ends in another fifteen minutes?
If I sprint over to NBL 2, I might make it in time.
Should I go?
But you know...
It'd be embarrassing if someone saw a big brother sprinting over to support his little brother.
Okay, I won't go.
Nanba!
Kitamura?
I haven't seen you in a while. How are you?
I'm doing great! Just look at my appetite!
Oh, Serika should be here soon. She's over there.
Mind if I join you?
Go ahead.
Let's eat!
Delicious!
But I might have gotten too much.
I heard the cafeteria hired a Japanese chef.
Huh? Really? I had no idea...
No wonder the food's so good... That's great.
Hey, Nanba.
Isn't Hibito's taking his test now?
Are you going to check in on him?
Nah, it's probably already over.
And you know...
At times like this,
it's better for brothers to keep their distance.
I see...
But you must be worried.
It probably isn't over yet...
I just heard that the test was extended by forty-five minutes.
Huh?
That's what the people over there said.
Ena has super sharp ears.
I hear all kinds of gossip...
Extended...
You should go, Nanba.
If you run, you'll make it in time.
That's true.
But when I run after eating, my sides hurt.
Doesn't it seem a little weird for a big brother to run to watch his little brother?
I think it's cool.
Eh?
I think that kind of thing is really cool.
Of course!
Then I'll sprint over.
First, finish your lunch.
Oh, right...
Okay, now I'm ready to go.
Bye!
Hibito, Damian...
Time to move on to the next task.
Okay.
Hook up the connector to the Sunflower's power transmitter.
Roger that.
We're getting a little hungry, Chief.
Due to an unexpected card, we're running over.
Can you hang in there a little longer?
Damian, can you check the manual for the panel's angle and direction?
Okay.
Ronald...
You weren't able to overcome your accident's aftereffects,
and you decided to leave...
Hibito's going to return to being an astronaut.
I wish you could see this, Ronald.
Still, Hibito's heart rate is rather high.
Is he all right?
It does appear to be higher than normal.
I don't believe there's any problem.
When Hibito was on the moon,
his heart rate was always this fast.
It's because he's excited.
Not because he's worried or nervous.
We're almost done, Hibito.
Yeah.
Hey, Hibito...
You have me, Buddy, Karen, and everyone else.
Don't forget that!
You aren't the only one who wants to see you back in space.
Thanks.
Yeah... He's right.
There are many people who showed concern for me.
I am an astronaut.
Hey, Hibito...
Don't go that way.
There's machinery in the way.
I am...
an astronaut!
It's freezing outside!
My sides...
Hey, Hibito... Good work.
Any attacks?
Th-This is killing me...
I bet that good luck charm helped.
Well, I knew you could do it.
That should work.
Thanks.
Congratulations, Hibito!
Great job!
Congrats, Hibito.
Damn it, Hibito...
I killed my sides for nothing.
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#92 Lonely People
Hibito has completed his test,
and I finally train with astronauts who will be going to the moon!
This crew has some very unique characters.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"Lonely People"