Previously on
Space Brothers
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
Born under a lucky star, younger brother Hibito becomes the first Japanese moonwalker.
A lunar accident has left Hibito struggling on the sidelines, suffering from a panic disorder.
But he's able to pass a test to return to active duty.
Older brother Mutta continues his long quest to the moon,
having finally been selected as a
backup member for a lunar mission.
And he's about to begin training.
However, his fellow crew members are a unique bunch.
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that hot veil aside
#93 In the Corner of My Heart
Unfortunately,
no one wants to go to space with them.
That's why we ended up putting them together.
We assigned the lonely astronauts to the same team,
and then we added Nanba Mutta.
And with one more person,
the captain of the crew,
it just might work.
Do you know who you'll turn to?
Yes.
When I sent an e-mail, I was turned down...
But I have a candidate.
After this meeting, I plan to see him in person.
Well, it looks like everyone's here.
Then let's get started.
Yes.
I am Daniel Morrison, representing the astronomy team.
We have brought a new proposal for the joint development, alongside NASA, of a lunar telescope.
We hope you like it.
Thank you for bringing me, Hibito.
It was nothing.
That's the astronomer with ALS...
Our original proposal to build a telescope on the moon was rejected due to a number of issues.
The construction would have been performed by many astronauts, over a long time.
Given how difficult it is to move around on the moon, construction would not be as precise as planned.
The large mirror ran a significant risk of being hit by debris.
An extensive mission would be required for repairs and periodic maintenance,
which would, in turn, increase costs.
However, Dr. Sharon has a new proposal that addresses all of those concerns.
I think it went well.
Everyone from NASA seemed happy with it.
Yes.
I know this will work.
I have faith.
How are you doing, Hibito?
Oh, I'm fine now.
I can go back any time.
I just have to wait to see which mission I'll be assigned to.
Really... That's wonderful.
Thank you, Hibito.
Say hello to Mutta for me.
He'll be upset that he didn't get to see you.
Huh?
What's with the antique camera?
Oh, while you're focusing, press the button halfway,
then snap away.
It isn't in video mode, is it?
Let's see... That should do it.
Okay, here I go.
Go for it.
Yah, man!
Are you here for sightseeing?
Has the heat made you daft?
It's only seventy degrees...
That isn't considered hot.
You have a heart that's hot, but I guess your body is just as—
Can you shut up?
I'll kick your ass.
Yah, man!
Damn it...
Whatever.
When I show her these pictures, Sharon will be thrilled!
I'll send them over later.
Since this is the first time I've worn a lunar spacesuit...
I look awesome!
These spacesuits are so lame.
Can't they improve the design?
You're in luck! We're working on a new design right now!
You're gonna finish in time?
I think so, probably!
Hurry it up, then.
I see... This proposal is very realistic.
We'll give it serious consideration.
However, it will require a great deal of work.
Are there any astronauts who would take interest in this project?
That...
That shouldn't be a concern.
Nanba Mutta?
The lunar telescope is the astronomy team's dream.
It is also a wish of mine.
When he was a child, Mutta promised me that he would grant my wish.
And Mutta is currently training for the moon.
It...
It will depend on his instructors' review of his performance...
I can't guarantee that he'll be assigned to this mission.
Yes, that's fine.
I'll keep it in the corner of my heart.
I understand.
The corner of my heart...
This is unusual...
The chief paying a visit to an astronaut's office.
None of your predecessors would have done this.
You're the only person I could think of.
The only captain who could control that group of misfits.
Are you interested in joining the sub crew for CES-62 and training for the moon...
Eddie?
Like I said in my e-mail, I'm already—
Actually, Eddie...
Betty Rain is one of the crew members.
Betty?
She returned to NASA?
Yes, her desire to go to space is tremendous.
Still, I'm not like Betty.
Consider my age.
I've done enough.
I'm satisfied.
One of the fans in ISS Node 3 still has writing left there by an astronaut from the shuttle era.
The Zvezda module is so noisy, if you look under one of the aerobike seats, there's a box of earplugs.
I bet you didn't know that.
I spent a total of seven hundred days on the ISS.
I know everything there is to know about the station.
But the moon is different...
It's a completely different world.
I don't have the motivation to start from scratch.
No idea how you can play this...
I've been playing it for over twenty years.
Asking me to go to the moon is like asking me to learn to play piano.
I understand that...
But Brian played both.
Hey, Eddie...
Just keep this in the corner of your heart.
I want to hear you play the piano.
Look, Bro!
It says that they'll last in space!
Winter
I really want one!
Ninety dollars, huh?
Is that expensive?
Pretty expensive.
Brian Jay (Age 11)                                           Eddie Jay (Age 13)
In that case, I'll ask Santa to bring two for Christmas.
One for you and one for me.
Good idea.
Then I'll write a letter to Santa.
Yes! Awesome!
But do you really think they'd survive space?
Wanna find out, Brian?
When we go to the moon,
we can put them on display.
Count me in!
Uncle Brian, I haven't seen you forever!
Hey, Tommy.
Have you found true love?
No, I'm busy studying.
Is that so?
Must be hard being a kid...
This is a surprise.
What's up?
Yeah, I'm itching to take these up...
So I dug them out of the closet.
Well? Remember these?
You still had them?
You bet... Don't tell me you'd forgotten.
I'll give you the Eddie figure.
While you wait to go to the moon, you can keep it wherever you want.
As for the Brian figure,
I'll be leaving it on the moon during the mission in two years.
I remember the promise we made...
But it's already been decided, Brian.
I applied to go to the moon,
but only you were chosen.
The bulldog with glasses doesn't understand.
You may not have a chance now.
But once he retires, things could change.
You'll get your chance to go to the moon.
I find it hard to believe.
Even if I eventually get a chance,
I'll already have retired by then.
It'd be stupid to begin training for the moon now.
Hey, Tommy...
Aren't those clothes for your band?
You promised to wear normal clothes for school.
We have today off...
It's Founder's Day for real.
How many times was your school founded in one year?
It's okay.
Today really is Founder's Day.
They'll be practicing in the studio today.
Hey, Dad... Look at the lyrics for our new song.
Huh? Oh, you finished it already?
Let's see.
"Blood-covered Soul"?
"Apocalypse cometh.
Angels are brought to their knees by the pain fate deals.
I am eternally consumed by hatred.
Blood-covered soul, your destination is hell.
It is like the stuff of gods.
Blood-covered soul, your destination is hell."
Not bad...
I didn't understand any of it, though.
Really? Great!
Except for the "blood-covered soul" part...
Wouldn't "blood-dripping soul" sound stronger?
"Blood-dripping soul"?
That's awesome, Dad!
You've earned my respect!
"Blood-dripping soul" is way better!
No kidding.
Peace out! Respect the man!
Is the whole following in his father's footsteps idea just a myth?
Why does he want to go to hell instead of space?
That's probably because you make going to space and coming home look so ordinary.
It's too normal for him.
Space is part of everyday life. He's learned it from you.
Space is part of everyday life?
I guess hell is much more exciting, then.
Say, hypothetically speaking,
if I were to tell you I was looking to go the moon, would that be ordinary?
Just kidding.
Blood-dripping soul...
Destination is hell, huh?
You see, Eddie...
During the CES-51 accident, Hibito happened across something.
Yeah?
Freddy, the captain, took pictures.
But we didn't tell you because Hibito wanted you to see it for yourself on the moon.
I agree with Hibito,
but since you've decided not to go to the moon,
I might as well show it to you...
I'll leave the pictures here.
Take a look when you feel like it.
What is it pictures of?
Brian left you something that's waiting on the moon.
You'll get your chance to go to the moon.
Hello, this is Eddie Jay.
Ah, what is it, Eddie?
So, I guess...
My blood-dripping soul says that my destination is hell.
What do you mean?
Can you make it easier for me?
I'm saying...
that I'll spend what's left of my life to go to the moon.
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#94 Exciting Teamwork
As we continue training in the desert, I realize something.
This crew of misfits doesn't have a leader.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"Exciting Teamwork"
In that case, I'll be the leader!
Mr. Hibbit!
Yay!
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
Super
Fire
Extinguisher
I just have to use this to put out the fire.
Fire-suppression system in module 5 is malfunctioning.
Possibility of explosion.
The fire's too strong for the fire extinguisher to put out.
What do I do?
Wh-What now? Hibbit's in trouble!
Stay calm, everyone.
Let's think of a way to put out the fire.
The fire-suppression system doesn't work.
Module 5
So we'll need to seal off module 5, to cut off the oxygen and starve the flames.
I was able to fix the wiring.
I'll cut off the oxygen flow to module 5.
Okay, do it.
Do you read me, Hibbit?
Seal off module 5.
That will kill the fire.
Got it!
Close Doors to Module 5
It won't work... I'm trying to close the doors but nothing's happening!
Module 5 danger level increased.
High risk of explosion.
In that case, I'll have to close the doors with the emergency lever inside!
Don't do it, Hibbit!
You'll be trapped inside!
There's no time to waste...
Yay!
This is Hibbit! The fire's out!
Danger
I'm suffocating.
Can't breathe...
Y-Yay...