Previously on
Space Brothers
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
Born under a lucky star, younger brother Hibito becomes the first Japanese moonwalker.
Older brother Mutta continues his long quest to the moon, having finally been selected as a backup member.
A lunar accident has left Hibito struggling on the sidelines, suffering from a panic disorder.
But he's able to pass a test to return to active duty.
However, NASA decides that Hibito,
having succumbed to panic disorder, cannot be assigned to a mission,
and Hibito disappears.
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that hot veil aside
#98 The Ultimate Astronaut
I'm gonna hit the jackpot this time...
Because everyone said that store sold to lots and lots of winning people!
Furukawa, from the laundry place, won 500,000 yen.
And Shimada, from the Buddhist place, bought five tickets, and won 300,000 yen.
I can feel it coming, dear...
Billions, billions, billions!
What will we do?
Lots and lots?
Two winners count as "lots and lots"?
Two is a lot!
Lots and lots.
Hey, Mom!
Hibito's missing again, and it's dark outside.
What? Again?
He wanders off lots and lots.
L-Lots and lots? He's only done it twice!
How can you guys be so relaxed?
Two is a lot.
Lots and lots.
I'll go out and look for him.
It's freezing...
Man... Where did Hibito go?
Why do you have to run off without saying anything?
Mr. Mutta.
Are you listening, Mr. Mutta?
Oh, yes. Sorry, I'm listening.
It appears that you don't understand who this meeting is for.
During the last simulation, communication was a jumbled mess.
You omitted information you should have transmitted to me,
and you also lose points for interrupting me while I was talking.
Right.
It's funny because Vince is usually the one who's constantly interrupting people.
We must be in sync at all times.
If there is any miscommunication, we will be unable to follow the procedure manual.
Next time, try to concentrate harder.
A moment's lapse can lead to a mission failure,
or even cause an accident.
Yes.
I screwed up...
On the first day, I did fine...
But I've been having trouble staying focused.
Did you tell Hibito that he can't go to space anymore, Butler?
No, I wasn't that blunt about it.
But that's probably how Hibito interpreted what I said.
He hasn't shown up since last Friday.
Damn...
Hibito's ignoring me?
He could at least send a reply.
It's been six days since Hibito vanished.
I've asked the neighbors,
his NASA friends,
Mom and Dad...
But no one knows where Hibito is.
I'm home...
Hey, Mu.
Let's go to bed.
Is that all you have to say?
Sorry about that.
I went to the park to take pictures of Virgo.
But all I got was a bunch of dark pictures.
Wanna see?
Man...
If you wander off again, I'm not gonna look for you.
Sorry, I'll let you know next time.
Or I'll leave a note.
"Hey, hey! I'm in the park right now, Mu!"
That's the message I sent you with telepathy.
You didn't hear it?
How could I hear that, fool?
Okay, then do you know what I'm thinking now?
I'll send it over!
How would I know, stupid?
You want me to teach you how to take pictures of Virgo with a camera.
Wow, you're right!
That was amazing, Mu!
Just so you know, it isn't possible with that camera.
So telepathy works!
I guess I'm just as amazing.
Then from now on, I'll use telepathy.
Is he not coming back?
I guess that's fine with me.
Since I'll have this huge house all to myself.
And I can drink all the beer.
And I can sing all I want!
And I can watch whatever I want on TV!
Hey...
There isn't any particular reason for this, but help yourself.
What's this about?
This isn't necessary, Mutta.
Thanks Ozzy, Ova.
See you tomorrow.
Yep, sure thing.
Good night!
Good night, Mutta.
Good night.
Looks like Hibito still isn't back.
Yeah...
I didn't expect Hibito to go missing.
Tomorrow, we're looking at sunshine in Texas.
With some clouds rolling in, and a chance of rain.
But if you keep a smile on your face, rain can't force the sunshine away.
And if you start crying, you'll be raining on any sunny day.
I don't recognize this number.
Hello?
Oh, Mr. Mutta.
It's me... Butler.
B-Butler?
I've been getting concerned because it's been a few days since Hibito came in.
I could have called him directly,
but I thought he might not want to talk to me.
Did something happen?
Then he didn't tell you anything.
Medically, Nanba Hibito is fit.
He meets all the requirements for an astronaut.
But...
NASA has concluded that sending him back to the moon on a mission
isn't worth the risk.
Why did you run off without saying anything to me?
And you didn't leave a note like you promised.
Where are you?
Say something, Hibito.
I thought you could use telepathy.
I can't hear a thing!
What do you mean?
Didn't Hibito pass the test to return to duty?
He completed the test without an attack.
Doesn't that mean he passed?
During the test, there was a point when Hibito's heartbeat jumped.
Of course, this happens to all astronauts...
But a few of the examiners considered this the sign of a panic attack.
One of them is the program manager.
I'm sure you can see that, without his approval, Hibito can't be assigned to a mission.
Is the program manager that Gates person?
So if I talk to him and convince him to change his mind...
No, you don't want to do that, Mr. Mutta.
There's a petition requesting Hibito's reinstatement.
Four veteran astronauts signed it,
knowing that they would be subjecting themselves to scrutiny.
Damian, Freddy, Eddie Jay, and Azuma.
Azuma...
But that still wasn't enough.
You should keep your mouth shut.
One wrong move, and you could lose your chance to go to the moon.
Butler...
Does NASA truly believe...
that Hibito is...
The weather's too nice.
I came too early...
Damn.
Hibito, don't tell me you lost your cell phone.
"Hibito...
I don't even know if you're still alive.
Give me some kind of reply.
If you don't want to bother, an "A" will work.
Even Mom and Dad are beginning to worry.
If you don't message us, they'll ask the police to start searching for you.
Tell me if you're alive or dead."
I even added a light joke that Hibito won't be able to ignore.
Send.
CAPCOM, this is landing module Altair.
We have 233,351 kilograms of fuel remaining.
This should be sufficient.
Let me confirm.
Fuel consumption is within expected levels.
The mission is a go.
You're doing well.
Roger that.
I need to run to the restroom.
Oh, okay.
Thanks, Damian.
I heard you signed a petition requesting that Hibito be reinstated.
I only did what was right.
After a near fatal mistake, I've received the chance to return to the moon.
It makes no sense that Hibito wouldn't be allowed to return, after saving me.
Yeah...
This makes no sense at all.
Don't they understand how hard he worked to get here?
Do they not have any respect for my brother?
CAPCOM, this is Altair.
Er, yes! This is Houston.
Confirm that all thruster nozzles are operational.
Thruster...
Er, yes! This is Houston!
Crap, I interrupted him again.
Is it okay to leave the thruster angle and output on setting A?
Let me confirm.
Ah.
Right, the flight director isn't currently here.
Let's see...
Is setting A standard procedure?
Well?
Yes, it should be fine.
Use setting A.
Roger that.
We will now commence landing sequence.
Current altitude is 2,300 meters.
A warning has sounded.
Please confirm.
We're heading away from the designated landing spot.
At this rate, we'll have to land in a rocky area, thirty kilometers away.
What do we do, Houston?
Huh? What?
Why?
We confirm the warning.
We will search for a safe landing area, and communicate it to you.
CAPCOM, what's going on?
Butler...
Does NASA truly believe...
that Hibito is an unfortunate and weak person?
N-No, certainly not.
In my mind, Hibito is the exact opposite.
After the lunar accident,
he saved his fellow crew member from the bottom of a dark ravine,
making all the right decisions to return alive.
Afterward, he demonstrated that he had conquered his panic disorder.
Hibito knows the fear of being in space better than any other astronaut,
and he has overcome that fear!
If you ask me,
he is the ultimate astronaut.
I feel
the same way.
Hello, this is Butler.
It's been a while since we last talked, Butler.
It's unusual for you to give me a call,
Mr. Hoshika.
Are you available to meet right now?
I'm in Houston for a meeting on asteroids.
I'd like to talk to you about Nanba Hibito.
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#99 People Change,
Promises Don't
Hibito has yet to return.
But he has made a decision about his future as an astronaut.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"People Change, Promises Don't"
Mr. Hibbit!
I was hoping for one last bite of a space carrot...
Wh-What's this light?
I can't see...
Are you...
Sorry, I was curious about Earth's technology, so I was fiddling around your base.
I meant no harm.
As an apology, I'll give you this.
Take a bite.
You'll feel better.
I-It tastes great!
Yay!
Huh?
You okay, Hibbit?
Hibbit!
There he is!
Hibbit.
Let me look at him.
Strange... Nothing's wrong with him.
The moon rabbit saved me.
What?
Oh, it appears something is wrong with him.
It was totally worth the trip up here!
Let's fix up the base quick...
And go find them!
I'm sure they're somewhere on the moon.
Wait for us, moon rabbits!
Yay!
And that's the end!