Okay, Apo...
Don't move an inch...
I told you to stay!
Apo, stay here, so you can say hello.
Why do you listen to Hibito?
Come on, Mu...
Huh? Right.
Hello, Space Brothers viewers!
We wish you a happy new year.
We hope that you will continue...
...to give your unwavering support...
...to this show.
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that hot veil aside
#88 Pretty Dog
Support divers are in the water.
All preparations are complete.
We will now begin the scheduled training.
Why do we have to be here?
Isn't this just normal EVA training?
No, we require your presence here as witnesses.
Okay, send him down.
Roger that.
Please watch closely...
To see if he can complete this training without any issue.
Issue?
He suffers from panic attacks that cause a complete breakdown.
If he fails this training, his career is over.
Yes, if he fails, it's over.
Looking good, Hibito.
Stay calm and follow instructions.
Got it.
H-Hey... What is this?
It's completely dark.
What's going on?
Come in!
Is this part of the test?
There's been an accident... Water's entering my helmet!
Pull me up! Do you read me?!
Hurry!
Pull me up...
Sorry...
C-Could you pull over for a moment?
Are you okay?
Are you getting out here?
Talk to me.
You can go...
Has all my hard work been for nothing?
Come on...
I can't let a stupid dream...
trigger a panic attack!
Damn it.
Someone also left a cosmos here this time last year.
Was it you?
Yes.
At first, I was going to leave a rose,
but Mu said that was stupid,
"Brian's an astronaut, so give him a cosmos."
So last year, I started leaving these.
Sounds like something he would say.
Did you leave the yuri lily?
Yeah, I placed it there earlier.
Was that a play on Yuri Gagarin?
Certainly not.
You helped to introduce me to Ivan...
And thanks to his unusual methods, I've been recovering.
That's good.
Then, have you talked to Mutta?
I haven't told Mu yet.
I'm hoping to recover before he finds out.
I see.
Before he finds out...
Why do you want that?
Huh?
Why...
So, did you get a chance to talk to Brian?
Eh? Brian?
When you were visiting his grave.
O-Oh... I guess, maybe.
If you had an attack with all the directors watching,
what would you do, Brian?
When you aren't sure what to do, you can ask Brian for advice,
and you'll always get a response.
That applied when he was alive,
and it still applies now.
I have to agree.
The Brian inside me always has a response.
As an only child, Brian was like an older brother to me.
Oh, actually, I felt the same way.
He was like a father...
Like a brother.
When you feel you've hit a wall,
you can talk to our big brother.
He'll probably give you his usual offhand response.
But if that still doesn't help,
you can talk to your real big brother.
You have another big brother you can turn to.
What am I supposed to do next,
Brian?
Sorry, Hibito...
Look at my getup.
I'm on vacation for now.
I'm off to Hawaii for an Elvis concert...
Looks like there's something bothering you.
Then I have some advice for you.
Before you start asking the dead and God for help,
you should look around...
Talk to your big brother who's alive.
So you're telling me the same thing...
Welcome.
Hey! I've been waiting for you, Mu.
Huh? You're completely soaked.
Did you ride your bike here?
I left my bike at NASA.
Well, if you want to know why I'm soaked, it's a long story...
Today, I want to talk.
When she's asleep, she's pretty.
When she's awake, she's pretty.
No matter where she is or with whom she is, she's pretty.
She's the Pretty Dog!
Pretty Dog is out for another pretty walk.
Hey, Pretty Dog.
Where are you headed today?
Oh! Look at that dog!
She's wearing a dress to go with that ugly face.
It looks so pretty!
Look at Pretty Dog go...
Once again, she's the center of attention!
Seriously...
We've reached the point where they've made a cartoon about a pug.
Are you happy, Apo?
Nice, isn't it?
Don't sit so close to the TV... You're too close.
Yes, she lives to go on walks!
We'll be back right after these messages.
Yes, put on a Pretty Dog headband, and dress to be the center of attention!
You can also get the brand-new Pretty Dog hairbrush and Pretty Dog mirror.
Let's be pretty!
Oh, thanks.
Hibito?
"I'm at the Seelook Pub right now.
Why don't we get a drink together?
It's raining, but would you come out here?
There's something I want to talk to you about."
Hibito wants to talk to me?
I didn't expect you to turn to me for help.
This is as rare as an annular eclipse.
Yeah, that's true.
So? What's up?
Well...
I'm not really sure how to explain this...
Mu,
do you know what "PD" stands for?
"PD"?
Oh.
You mean Pretty Dog. What about it?
Not that!
Huh? That's wrong?
Th-Then it must be...
Palladium?
The chemical symbol is Pd.
"Panic disorder."
It's an anxiety disorder.
Oh, that's what you meant.
Panic disorder?
That's what I'm currently suffering from.
My heartbeat jumps, I get dizzy, and I can't breathe.
Basically, I freeze in place.
In my case,
I suffer panic attacks from wearing a spacesuit in an enclosed area.
It probably doesn't sound that bad, but it's harder than you'd think.
Wh-When did this start?
When I came back to Earth, from the moon.
It hasn't gone away since.
I've been removed from active duty.
So, next week, the directors are making time to watch me take a test.
This test will decide if I can return to space.
But in the taxi home, I had a nightmare that triggered an attack.
As it stands, I don't see how I'll be able to pass the test.
Eat some more.
I'm buying.
Drinks are on me, too.
Still, this is a surprise.
You're the last person I'd expect to get PD.
Huh?
I mean, you'd expect sensitive people like me to succumb to that kind of thing.
Hey, can I get another?
Coming right up.
But if a carefree guy like you can get it...
It worries me about how I'm gonna cope.
Here.
Thanks.
If I were in your shoes,
I'd probably run away from the test.
But while a carefree guy like you may worry, you'll go through with it.
That's how you are.
Right now, if I told you to quit, you'd still take the test.
Because deep down, you have things within you that are definite.
Sorry, Hibito.
Can I borrow some money?
Seems I'm short.
Take this umbrella.
Huh? What about you?
I need to drop by the grocery store on the way home.
I have the money I borrowed from you...
Are you worried about getting home?
I'll be fine.
Oh... That's right, Hibito...
If you ever feel like you're going to have a panic attack, just say this...
"Here comes the PD... Pretty Dog!"
Like that.
You're pretty drunk, Mu.
Wait, that'll lodge the image of Pretty Dog in your mind.
Or the image of Apo's stupid look.
And one more thing.
You seem to be concerned that you had an attack in a taxi.
But I think you should be relieved.
Huh? Why?
That means the spacesuit isn't causing the attacks.
We grew up dreaming about spacesuits.
The spacesuit is on our side.
Did something good happen, sir?
You have a big smile on your face.
Oh, really?
Yeah, you're my happiest customer today.
Say, mister...
Mind if I ask a strange question?
Do you know what "PD" stands for?
"PD"?
PD would be that...
panic something.
Nope.
I was talking about "Pretty Dog."
The starlight illuminates my future, It's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#89 Last Words
As Hibito prepares for his upcoming test,
the other astronauts are assigned to their new missions.
You will be the next one to go the moon.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"Last Words"