Previously on
Space Brothers
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
Born under a lucky star, younger brother Hibito becomes the first Japanese moonwalker.
Older brother Mutta continues on his long quest to the moon,
having finally been selected as a backup member for a lunar mission.
Meanwhile, a lunar accident has left Hibito struggling on the sidelines,
suffering from panic disorder.
But he's about to take a test to return to active duty.
He must pass the test, or he will never go back to space.
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that hot veil aside
#90 A Small Note and a Big Lucky Charm
Hey, Mu! Check this out!
Mu!
What is it?
Come over here!
Why don't you come over here?
I found this awesome trick!
See this mirror?
Stand behind me and watch.
Here I go!
Look at me! My face looks hilarious!
Hibito, you just realized this?
I discovered that trick three years ago.
Three years ago, you were the same age I am now.
Yeah, you're right...
Look at this!
I'm an alien with only one nostril.
Are you watching?
My face is funnier!
Th-That's great!
Wow, why's it doing that?
What are you talking about?
We will be conducting a brief seminar for everyone involved with the Desert Rats training, so please wait inside.
Okay!
I'm on my way, Hibito.
It's your turn to start training for the moon now.
I was against the idea at first,
but Butler kept pestering me.
Yes, that's right.
This elaborate test is being conducted for the sake of a single astronaut.
Yes.
Will he return?
No, I doubt it.
It was never going to happen.
But Butler forced us to schedule this test.
It's a problem.
Yes.
Oh, it's the chief.
I'll call you back.
The test is about to begin, Gates.
Why aren't you by the pool?
We're watching through a monitor, so watching from here won't be any different.
Hibito, are you finished changing?
Yeah, I'm ready anytime, John.
Mutta asked me to give this to you.
What is it?
What's this?
A lucky charm.
A lucky charm... I see.
Oh, I've seen those before!
It's a Pretty Dog mirror.
If you push the paw, it opens.
This is one small note.
"I did some research on PD (the panic version),
and looking at yourself objectively is supposed to help."
Look at yourself objectively...
Wow, why's it doing that?
What are you talking about?
Look at the corner.
I can't look myself in the eye. It's like seeing myself through someone else's eyes.
You just realized that?
I figured that out when I was four or so.
This is a pretty big lucky charm.
Are you ready, Hibito?
You bet.
Thank you for coming to observe this test.
I appreciate the support.
Let's start.
Hibito,
your lucky charm.
Right.
Can you secure it?
Hibito...
I prepared something for this day!
Huh?
There's something I want to tell you.
This is my message to you.
I asked Mutta if there were any words in Japanese
that would inspire the soul of an astronaut, to help you return to space.
The soul of an astronaut?
Mutta was very helpful...
You're lucky to have him as a brother, Hibito.
So come back to us, Hibito!
Alien
Be a spaceman!
Thanks, Lowry...
You look good.
Okay, send me down.
Lowry... Olivia.
Thanks for helping see me through this.
Hibito...
It's okay.
This is the last step...
Houston, do you read me?
I've landed in the quiet ocean.
This is
the astronaut, Nanba Hibito!
Nanba Hibito is underwater.
Okay, Hibito... Ten more meters until the floor.
Five meters to go.
Is he okay?
Please don't let an attack happen...
Okay, Hibito. We'll proceed as planned.
First, descend to the bottom, then make your way to the C-1 airlock.
No attack, please...
Roger that.
Good.
He hasn't suffered an attack.
He's off to a good start.
But the real test is yet to come.
I still believe assigning Hibito to the safety department was the correct decision.
After the lunar accident, improvements have been made to the spacesuit to increase safety.
And the software used for the helmet HUD has been overhauled.
However, it's unfortunate that he is unable to wear the new spacesuit.
Well, he seems to be doing fine now.
Does he really suffer from panic disorder, Chief?
Yes.
My nephew also suffers from panic disorder, so I know the symptoms.
He has us watching him, divers surrounding him,
and he's in the dark, trapped in a spacesuit that restricts underwater movement.
The current situation is filled with catalysts for a panic attack.
This still isn't enough to prove that he's fit for active duty.
We will be adding an additional test.
There will be an accident that he doesn't expect.
A green card, huh?
What kind of accident?
That's good, Hibito...
Let's move on to the next task.
Hook up the capsule to the cable.
Roger.
It's almost time.
Carbon Dioxide Level Rising
My carbon dioxide levels are climbing?
Is this a green card?
The warning is only for show.
We aren't endangering his life by increasing his carbon dioxide level.
At the moment, Hibito is probably ninety-percent sure this is a green card.
However, every astronaut will always consider the worst-case scenario,
so he'll believe there is a ten-percent chance that this is a real accident.
That ten percent is more than sufficient to trigger a panic attack.
Mission Control,
I have a warning that my CO2 level is rising.
Terminating mission.
I'll open the helmet purge valve to see if that helps.
Mission Control,
this is Gates.
It looks like he's managing to stay calm.
Hibito...
Good, keep it up.
That's odd.
I've released the carbon dioxide,
but the warning's still there...
So my response had no effect.
Something is malfunctioning...
CO2 Sensor Malfunction
What?
Now something's wrong with the sensor?
The CO2 level is ten times normal?
Huh? What's happening?
Stay calm.
A warning appeared that the CO2 sensor is malfunctioning.
After that, Hibito's heart rate began increasing.
What's going on?
I-I'm not sure...
Wasn't this part of the green card?
No, the card I arranged was...
Now I have a warning that something's wrong with the CO2 sensor.
I'll open the DCM purge valve again and see if that works.
Hibito...
John, get ready to pull him out, just in case.
Go away, stupid PD!
Silly me.
The spacesuit...
The spacesuit is on our side.
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#91 How to Help Hibito
Hibito's test continues.
Hibito, you should be fine!
I think.
The test takes a turn I didn't expect.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"How to Help Hibito"
Mr. Hibbit!
We've safely made it to space,
and after three days traveling through space...
Yay!
We've landed successfully on the moon, and are heading for Moonbase.
Here we are.
This will be our base of operations, while we search for the unidentified object.
Purrfect.
What's that?
This place is too dark for me.
Turn on the lights, Freddy Dog.
Hold on.
Finding the switch shouldn't take long...
...using my sharp nose.
Then hurry up!
Karen Kat?
What is it, Hibbit?
Wait, you're over there?
What's this?
Yes, it looks like something took a bite out of it...
Found it. This must be the switch.
Good! Turn the power on, Freddy Dog!
Okay, power...
Right, we're good—
Wh-What?
What's happening?