Previously on
Space Brothers
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
Born under a lucky star, younger brother Hibito becomes the first Japanese moonwalker.
A lunar accident has left Hibito struggling on the sidelines, suffering from a panic disorder.
But he's able to pass a test to return to active duty.
Older brother Mutta continues his long quest to the moon,
having finally been selected as a
backup member for a lunar mission.
And he's about to begin training.
However, his fellow crew members are a unique bunch.
Hey, Mom...
I'm gonna turn six soon.
Yes, you're right.
Is there a particular toy you want?
Nope, I don't want any toys.
I really want a globe of the Earth.
And on Christmas, I'll ask Santa for a moon globe.
Really? I think that's wonderful.
I was very happy...
His words made me very happy.
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that thick veil aside
#95 Our Future
Eh? Really?
What about homework? Are you finished?
If you have any questions, ask Grandma and Grandpa.
Yes, I'll be home soon.
Good night, Chris.
It's almost here.
There isn't anything special about this.
Haven't you seen it often enough?
Nah, it'll always be a treat to behold.
It should be to our southeast.
Yep! There it is!
Yeah, that's nice.
The ISS...
Houston, Houston.
This is Ravel, on the ISS.
This is Houston CAPCOM.
We've completed our day's tasks.
Roger that.
You have two hours before bedtime.
Why don't you enjoy space?
Good job today, Captain Ravel.
Thanks, Betty.
Begin reentry sequence.
Temperature of outer hull rising.
Parachutes successfully deployed!
Orion has landed!
Welcome home.
Good to be back.
If Chris grows up and says he wants to go to space, I'd be thrilled.
I like the sound of an astronaut family.
But they say kids usually don't turn out the way you hope.
But this boy has two astronauts' blood flowing through his veins.
I have a feeling he'll be interested in space.
I hope that happens...
And so,
my brother, Hibito, was able to overcome his panic disorder
and pass the test to return to active duty.
Really?
I had no idea that he suffered from panic disorder.
So, when will Hibito start training again?
Oh, good question.
Well, it should be soon.
Who's up next?
Let's have Betty talk about herself.
Me?
Mutta's the only one here who doesn't know your history.
You want me to tell him?
Mutta discussed his brother, Hibito, with us.
I don't see why you can't tell him about your son.
Eh? Your son?
You have a son?
That's right.
I have an adorable son.
His name is Chris.
Right now, he's eight.
Oh, he's named Chris...
Chris?
After I had Chris, I quit being an astronaut for a while,
so I haven't been to space yet.
My husband was also an astronaut, so Chris grew up loving space.
But...
Hey, do astronauts get to ride rockets?
That's right.
You both get to ride rockets?
Yes, I'll get to ride one someday.
So can you run on the moon?
Can you fly like a bird because it's really light?
What do the stars look like from the moon?
I haven't been to the moon yet, so I'm not sure,
but I'll tell you everything when I get back.
He's become a big fan of space.
Yeah.
You have to answer his question, Tuck.
I know.
We will now introduce the three crew members of CES-43.
Michael Aaron.
Tuck Ravel.
And the captain, Brian Jay!
So is he back yet?
Don't worry. He'll be back soon.
The reentry module Orion carrying the three astronauts has just entered the atmosphere.
Communications will be restored soon and we will be able to see the spacecraft.
Communications with Orion have been restored.
Cut the alarm!
We can't talk over that noise!
Roger.
I just checked the monitor!
Damn it, the parachutes are tangled!
Tuck, keep Mission Control updated.
Send as much detail as you can.
Michael and I will calculate our current velocity and time remaining before impact.
R-Roger!
The data from this accident will be very useful.
Twenty seconds until we hit the surface.
Damn, there was so much left I still wanted to do.
I never got to listen to the CD I just bought.
And I only watched up to episode 6, season 2, of Last World.
You chose a good place to stop, Michael.
Huh?
After episode 6,
that show really sucked.
After the accident,
I never expected to be an astronaut again.
I thought it would only make Chris worry.
But three years after the accident, he asked me for a globe and began to talk about space again.
Hey, Mom... What does Earth look like from the moon?
It made me so happy.
I want to give him an answer...
in his father's place.
I like the sound of an astronaut family.
I hope that happens...
The landing module uses reverse thrust to slow its descent.
That sends sand flying everywhere.
So the landing needs to occur far from the base or any equipment.
When returning to Earth, only the top part of the lunar module is launched.
The landing stage is used as a launchpad, then left behind on the moon.
So, at this rate, the area around the base will become a landing stage graveyard,
and we'll have to land farther and farther from the base.
Th-That's certainly a problem.
So CES-62 is supposed to be the first step to a solution.
I see. Thank you very much.
Next, we have a question from a magazine.
What is your oldest treasure?
Hey... Morning, Vince.
Good morning.
My oldest treasure, huh?
I guess it'd be this.
I got this watch from my father, who was in the military.
It's an old watch, but it's been to space with me.
I see... That's a lovely story.
If you're interested in astronauts and their treasures,
you should talk to Vince.
Mr. Bold?
Stop it, Larry.
What's the problem?
Tell them about that thing you can't throw away.
What kind of treasure is it?
It isn't a treasure.
It's nothing more than a tool...
to remind me of my treasure.
Hey, how's your side?
Looks good. Don't see any issues.
It's secure.
I have a son.
His name is Chris.
Chris's father was an astronaut
who died in the CES-43 accident.
Naturally,
everyone objected when I said I wanted to return to being an astronaut.
My parents and relatives wouldn't have it.
In the face of everyone's objections, I didn't have the courage to return to NASA.
But my son, Chris, was the sole person to tell me it was okay.
We're here. Get out.
What's that?!
That's what I saw earlier.
Listen up, people.
This will be the last stage of your Desert RATS training.
You'll be working with the main crew.
Ow!
What is this?
Stop it!
How do you like the speed on my Cockroach, Mutta?
I never dreamed that you'd be chosen as Vince's backup.
I think Butler's lost it...
Hey, Pico!
Whoa! Don't step on my Cockroach!
Oh, it's Pico.
So this is the sub crew?
Yeah.
You've got a fine bunch here...
I almost thought it was some kind of a joke.
Why not call yourself the "Jokers"?
I like the name Jokers!
Er, you mean like the playing card, the joker?
Sure...
You guys are like the jokers in a card deck.
Five jokers.
And Captain Eddie's the lucky fella who got dealt this hand.
Pico, that's enough chitchat.
Let's begin.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, ladies and gents...
I'm going to explain what this huge thing is.
This is a new landing module that I'm in charge of developing.
Lunar Module
Landing Stage
It has the lunar module, which carries the astronauts, and the landing stage, which acts as a launchpad.
But in between,
we have a new Altair equipped with STITCH, legs with wheels.
After Altair lands, it will extend the six STITCH legs and carry the lunar module away from the launchpad.
The lunar module will move, on its legs, to the base, and dock with the air module.
The astronauts will never have to step outside.
And after the lunar module launches to send the astronauts home,
the STITCH legs can be used to move the landing stage.
Which means that STITCH can be used to gather the landing stages in one area,
so astronauts can always land at the same point.
Super...
Convenient...
So let's begin by having the main crew get inside and try the controls.
Whew, it's all over...
I finally get to drink.
Weren't you drinking earlier today?
Still, I never thought we'd make it happen.
Make what happen?
Remember when Rick told our futures?
Rick would become a flight director,
relaying instructions to you, the astronaut.
And you would be riding in a spaceship I built.
But Rick's no longer here.
Yeah, we're missing a link.
But when you fly my Altair to the moon,
the astronaut serving as CAPCOM, at Mission Control,
to guide your landing
will be Mutta, your backup...
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#96 Astronaut and Father
We're also training hard,
though under different circumstances than Mu and his fellow crew.
And we still don't know what we're training for.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"Astronaut and Father"