Previously on
Space Brothers
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
Born under a lucky star, younger brother Hibito becomes the first Japanese moonwalker.
A lunar accident has left Hibito struggling on the sidelines, suffering from a panic disorder.
But he's able to pass a test to return to active duty.
Older brother Mutta continues his long quest to the moon,
having finally been selected as a
backup member for a lunar mission.
And he's about to begin training.
However, his fellow crew members are a unique bunch.
Hello, this is Eddie Jay.
Ah, what is it, Eddie?
So, I guess...
My blood-dripping soul says that my destination is hell.
What do you mean?
Can you make it easier for me?
I'm saying...
that I'll spend what's left of my life to go to the moon.
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that thick veil aside
#94 Exciting Teamwork
No, a helicopter just passed by.
Then, talk to you later, Mom.
Look after everything for me.
I'll be back next week...
Yeah, bye.
In the morning...
it's nice and cool.
Three, two, one...
Reggae time!
Come on!
Morning... Morning... Morning dance!
Morning... Morning... Morning dance, yeah!
Morning... Morning...
Are you going to do this every morning when you wake up?
Yeah!
Give me a break.
Come on, Betty...
In order to live, certain functions must be performed.
Breathing.
Sleeping.
Eating.
And...
Morning dancing!
What was that?
It's already seven?
Carlo!
Rise and shine...
Time to get up!
He was drinking last night.
Hey, everyone...
Why don't we run together as a group?
Well? How about it, Betty?
Are you an idiot?
If I run at your pace, I won't break a sweat!
Yah, man!
Hey, Philippe...
Can't you stop dancing while you run?
Well, this is how I run, more or less...
Man, why is this happening?
Carlo's hungover and not even trying.
Andy is still stretching...
We can't even act like a team during a morning jog.
How will this work?
Yeah, that was an excellent workout...
Now I'm wide awake.
Look at the sparkling sweat on my body.
Don't you think it's like shooting stars?
Took you long enough...
Andy beat you here, even after starting later.
He didn't beat me...
I let him finish first.
Besides...
After seeing him sprint by like an animal,
first thing in the morning, I lost my motivation.
You never had any motivation!
Now, now... Calm down, Philippe.
You're spitting pancake everywhere.
This crew has no leader.
Even I can see that.
In that case, do I have to play leader, and bring the team together?
I must become a leader who can keep everyone motivated and calm.
So it's finally my turn...
Everyone!
I realize that as the newest astronaut, I shouldn't be doing this, but this is it.
Next, we'll be training to drive the Beetle!
Finish your breakfast, and let's move out!
What do you mean, this is it?
Why are you trying to act like a leader?
It doesn't suit you at all.
If you realize that you're the new kid here, act like it.
Uh...
Yeah... You're right.
Don't try so hard.
This is as fast as it'll go...
It's a slow machine.
It's so damned hot...
Don't these windows open?
If they opened, we'd be in trouble.
Since we're in a lunar rover.
Say, about that tattoo on your shoulder...
Is that a "C"?
Or the moon?
It's the moon.
And could you stop staring?
I'll knock you down!
Oh, okay.
Can't I take a peek every 1.8 seconds?
Are you an idiot?
If a human can eat good food, drink good wine,
and surround himself with beauty,
he'll have the happiest life imaginable.
In other words...
I wanted to ride with Betty.
If I weren't stuck with you, I'd be happy right now.
I'm alone.
Don't you have anyone to ride with, Andy?
It's just as hot outside.
Welcome back.
So how was the ride?
Eddie...
I wanted to take the Beetle for a spin...
I've gotten an itch to go to the moon.
Let me join in.
That's...
Hey, Brother...
It's an honor to meet you!
I'm Nanba Mutta!
Let me introduce the new member.
Stop talking, people!
Starting today, veteran astronaut Eddie Jay will be joining in this training as the sixth astronaut.
He will be the leader of the sub crew.
Hey, hey...
You can call me the leader, but when it comes to the moon, I'm a beginner.
Just like the rest of you.
So when I finally stand on the moon,
I'll be just as thrilled as you will.
Let's go to the moon together.
It only took a moment for everything to click.
A leader is someone who can keep everyone inspired and calm.
And this man was our leader!
In middle and high school,
they typically assign extremely strict teachers
to the classes that are full of troublemakers.
But for some reason,
our crew of troublemakers was assigned a friendly leader.
What's she doing?
She's always so fast!
Yeah, Eddie...
Our crew's always like this.
I see.
I like it...
I'm getting excited.
It seems they have a long way to go...
I wouldn't say they aren't getting along,
but it's rare to see crew members act so completely independently.
They're the least organized bunch I've ever seen.
At this rate, that crew will never be assigned to a mission.
Hold on... Their leader just arrived.
We should wait and see what he can do.
Thanks, Betty!
Let's eat!
Hot!
What the hell?
It's like I'm eating a bottle of pepper!
I know, okay?
I'm a bad cook.
If it tastes bad, just say so.
Uh, well...
It's a little spicy...
Only a little.
You dumped a week's worth of pepper in this!
Why don't you repeat that?
I'll dislocate your jaw!
Did she mean me, too?
If you have any complaints, address them to Eddie.
We could be eating pre-made meals,
but he decided we should cook instead.
He's got issues.
Now, now...
It's more fun this way.
I'll make dinner.
I'll eat anything that doesn't have pepper...
Well, it's a good thing we got Betty's cooking out of the way now.
Thanks, Eddie.
If I hadn't found out till we were on the moon...
Hot!
...that could've been quite an accident.
I'm back...
Okay, time to eat.
Took you long enough.
Oh?
This is more food than I usually get.
Eat it all.
It's punishment! Punishment for tardiness!
Houston!
This is the lunar module Altair...
It looks like we're way off on our landing.
This is Houston.
We read you.
We are unable to confirm your current position.
Tell us what you can see.
We'll attempt to draw a sketch.
Roger that.
Okay, go for it.
Let's see...
At twelve o'clock, there's a rock?
A bunch of rocks...
And mountains going, "Wham! Wham!"
And another "Wham!"
Wham.
No one understands that idiotic explanation!
Give us a description we can actually draw!
There's a pile of sand.
It zigzags...
Zigzags?
Wait.
It's jagged.
If you guys had really had an accident, you'd be stranded for the rest of your lives.
Let's see...
There's a lovely striped cliff.
It reminds me of waves rolling softly in the morning.
Alternating lines, dark as a summer tan
and pale as a fair maiden's skin.
It's a beautiful sight to behold.
That was long.
Wow, you're good at this.
Huh?
Really?
But it looks like a mess because I followed their instructions.
Hey... Don't look!
Eh?! You want us to go running now?
Now, now.
I'm thinking about changing up our morning jog tomorrow.
Think of this as a rehearsal.
We're only running two kilometers.
What kind of change do you mean?
It's simple.
We won't be running in circles around the camp.
We can make it more exciting and fun.
Not happy?
I've already got permission.
Here's what we'll do tomorrow morning.
First, the six of us will get in this truck,
and they'll drop us off at an unknown location a few kilometers from camp.
We'll head for our camp,
keeping a pace so that we arrive at a predetermined time.
We can't arrive early or late.
Simple, right?
And I'm the only one allowed to wear a watch.
Okay, here we are...
Two kilometers away.
It's 8:30 now.
Our target time is 8:50!
I get it.
Eddie's good.
In this situation...
Okay, let's go.
Start!
Oh?
What's wrong, guys?
You're free to spread out like usual!
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#95 Our Future
Before our training in the desert ends, Betty reveals her motivation.
Mutta's the only one here who doesn't know Betty's history.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"Our Future"
I have an adorable son.