Previously on
Space Brothers
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
And his younger brother Hibito, born under a lucky star,
is left struggling on the sidelines after a lunar accident, suffering from a panic disorder.
But he's able to pass a test to return to active duty.
Older brother Mutta continues his long quest to the moon,
having finally been selected as a
backup member for a lunar mission.
And he's about to begin training for the moon.
Meanwhile, Kenji and Nitta have learned they won't be going to the moon,
as they continue to train every day.
Great Baby Names
Not sure what I want...
We'll be living in Houston for a while,
so we should pick a name that's easy for Americans to pronounce.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, Fuuka...
What should we name the baby?
An!
An?
An... Makabe An.
That's cute!
Why An?
An, I'm your sister.
Ankoro and Me
Author:     Yauchi Mayako
An!
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that hot veil aside
#96 Astronaut and Father
Will you be home late again?
Yeah,
I have a spacecraft-operation test in Russian coming up.
Nitta and I will be staying late to run Russian simulations.
Okay.
But starting the 23rd, I'll be on Christmas break.
If you start having contractions, let me know.
I'll come running.
Okay, be careful.
Yeah.
I'm off.
Brighty bright bright!
Morning, An! Time to wakey up.
Every morning, I take Fuuka to her preschool.
It's my one chance every day to act like a father...
Nice to meet you. Time to wakey up.
An! An!
Thank you.
Hi! Good morning, Fuuka.
Good morning.
Today, we'll be practicing the dance for the upcoming recital.
Uh-huh! Yay!
She's fitting in great.
In NEEMO training, we had a clear objective,
as we were simulating life on the moon, and the missions we would undertake.
But now that we can no longer go the moon, there isn't a clear objective.
Today, you'll be operating a new spacecraft.
We want to hear what astronauts have to say about the controls and the display.
Each group will need to submit a report.
How long did the switchover take?
Not too long.
Okay, on to the next one.
I don't know if it's because NASA's trying to protect its secrets,
but a lot of information isn't passed on to astronauts.
We continue to train as instructed,
not knowing what we're training for...
We're back...
I'm home, Houston.
Huh? A dance?
That's right... It's a country dance!
After seeing Serika again, I feel cleansed...
Some dance instructors will arrive early for an hour-long lecture.
If we want, we can participate.
Wait, what?
Are you going, Serika?
Yes, Ena and I will be dancing.
I can't wait.
Why don't you join us?
Quick, quick, slow...
I s-s-sure will!
Are these the basic steps?
Okay! I'll have them memorized in a day!
Yahoo!
Quick, quick, slow.
Quick—
Yo, Mu! Welcome back.
Oh, Kenji!
Right, Kenji.
About the...
Mu, sorry...
I'd love to catch up,
but I'm in a hurry right now.
Oh, really?
Let's talk later.
O-Okay... Roo-ra!
They're all amazing...
Everyone... They're amazing.
Did she make this?
I'm home.
By now, they must be asleep.
I'm an astronaut and a father.
Both dreams have been achieved...
Still, it feels like treading water or acting without a goal.
I'm an astronaut and a father.
But time continues to pass without my doing a proper job at either.
See the look on Nanba's face?
If we didn't have another assignment, we could enjoy ourselves...
No kidding, I could use the rest.
I was looking for both of you.
This is perfect.
Chief Butler...
I need to talk to both of you.
Why don't we get some fresh air?
I'm due in two weeks.
Yes, that's right.
We found an OB/GYN run by someone Japanese.
Yep, it all worked out.
I was hoping for another natural childbirth.
Onigiri!
In two days, my parents will be here...
H-Hey, Fu!
Honestly...
Oh, hello?
Sorry...
More onigiri!
One for Daddy.
One for Mommy.
One for Fuuka.
One for An!
I need to talk to both of you.
Why don't we get some fresh air?
I-It's cold out here.
Shall we go back inside?
No, it's okay.
There's a lot of noise inside.
To be honest,
I'd have liked to have had a white mustache and red suit to give you the news...
Consider this an early Christmas present.
You've been officially assigned to a mission.
Quick, quick, slow. Quick, quick, slow.
Quick, quick, slow.
Nanba, we're supposed to step back.
Oh, okay.
Right, left, left, right.
Mu, you're gonna trip over yourself.
This is pure bliss...
I'm so grateful to whoever invented dance!
I'll be sending an e-mail with more details,
but here's a quick summary.
One veteran, one expert...
And two rookies, you guys.
This mission will have a four-person crew.
At that moment, it was like I'd been reborn.
Or I should say...
Like I had finally become an astronaut.
That was how it felt.
Hello?
Yeah, it's me.
Yeah.
Actually, I finally found out about the mission I've been assigned to.
Yep.
Really? That's great.
What will you be doing?
I'll tell you when I get home.
The mission hasn't been announced yet, so we're only allowed to tell family.
I think you'll be excited.
Okay...
Again...
The pain is increasing...
I think...
the contractions have started.
I-I'll call for a taxi!
Stay calm, and wait for me!
I'll be right there...
Hello? This is an emergency! I need a taxi at the following address!
Sorry to bother you this late at night, Komachi...
It's no big deal!
I doubt she'll wake up until tomorrow, but could you please look after Fuuka?
I've got it.
Go have yourself a healthy baby!
She's early...
For now, please wait in this room.
Okay.
Does it hurt, Yuki?
What should I do?
It seems like a lot of pain...
Her brow is all wrinkled...
Why is he rubbing me there?
Why doesn't he rub my back instead?
Do you want to listen to some music?
Yeah, that'd be nice...
One more shot!
From above this time!
D-Doctor... You're gonna fall!
Give me a "Houston"...
In Houston!
It's a healthy baby girl!
Doctor!
Here you go.
Thank you so much, doctor!
Nah, your wife and baby did all the hard work.
Thank you very much!
Do we go with An like Fuuka suggested?
I think so.
Oh, didn't you say something about being assigned to a mission?
Right... I completely forgot.
I know my destination.
Guess where I'm going.
Huh? It's either the moon or the ISS, right?
Nope, look at this.
Your crew has been assigned the mission
of becoming the first humans to explore an asteroid.
An asteroid?
Yes... We'll be going beyond the moon!
That's amazing!
Hey, did you see this?
Looks like...
we have a name.
Wow! She's tiny!
An, I'm your sister!
With An's birth,
I became the father of two daughters for the first time in my life.
I am an astronaut headed for an asteroid. And a father of two daughters.
I'm just getting started!
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#97 Won't Go Away
As I move on to the next stage of my Houston training,
our family spends New Year's together.
Hibito is faced with a harsh reality.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"Won't Go Away"