Previously on
Space Brothers
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
Born under a lucky star, younger brother Hibito becomes the first Japanese moonwalker.
However, a lunar accident has left him struggling on the sidelines, suffering from panic disorder.
But he's about to take a test to return to active duty.
Meanwhile, older brother Mutta continues his long quest.
Chief Butler has summoned Mutta, Kenji, and Nitta to discuss their future missions.
What will their fate be?
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that hot veil aside
#89 Last Words
Morning Radio is here to kick off your day!
Time for the Q&A corner. Yeah!
We have a question from eight-year-old Carl, out in LA.
"If you fart in a crowded elevator, what should you do?"
Ah, we've all been through that.
I get your drift, Carl.
Okay, here's the answer...
When that happens,
to shift the blame, you say, "Huh? Does something smell?"
Man, this show's a crummy way to start the morning.
You were pretty out of it this morning, Mu.
Still a little hung over?
No, I'm sleepy because I slept too much.
Huh? Hibito?
Hmm?
Does something smell?
Cut it out!
I should feel good about myself
for pulling off that lie.
Honestly, last night, I was worried about Hibito's panic disorder.
Mu,
do you know what "PD" stands for?
"PD"?
Oh.
You mean Pretty Dog. What about it?
Not that!
Huh? That's wrong?
Th-Then it must be...
Palladium?
The chemical symbol is Pd.
"Panic disorder."
It's an anxiety disorder.
Oh, that's what you meant.
Panic disorder?
I was busy researching on the Internet and thinking things over...
And the next thing I knew, it was morning.
Which means I didn't get any sleep!
Good morning, Nanba!
Huh? Hmm?
Serika! Good morning!
You're starting a new training program today, right?
Let's do our best.
Y-Yes! Let's do that!
Yeah, she's so cute in the morning!
That woke me right up!
Pretty Dog...
Well, Hibito should be fine.
Based on my reading, Hibito's panic disorder isn't that severe.
Some people can't even drive or ride in taxis.
But Hibito seems to have no trouble with those.
He should be able to pass the test easily.
If I were in your shoes,
I'd probably run away from the test.
But while a carefree guy like you may worry, you'll go through with it.
That's how you are.
Right now, if I told you to quit, you'd still take the test.
Because deep down, you have things within you that are definite.
Okay, then...
Three days left until the test!
I can't wait.
You okay, Mutta?
Oh, Vince.
Good morning—
You're two minutes late.
Oh, sorry.
I couldn't walk straight.
You look terrible. Not enough sleep?
Please try to get to sleep early and to wake early.
Yes, sir.
And so, you three are supposed to run over to the chief's office, one at a time.
Chief Butler wants to see you.
Excuse me!
Mr. Nanba...
I don't intend to pry into your personal life.
But starting now, we will be reading the same manuals,
breathing the same cabin air, sitting in the same seats,
and undergoing the same training.
You need to be able to follow my rhythm.
Yes, sir!
That is your job as my backup.
Nanba Hibito, Azuma Takio, Murasaki Sansei.
The next Japanese astronaut to go the moon...
will be you, Nanba Mutta.
But first, you must build experience on a backup crew.
You have been assigned as Vincent Bold's backup.
M-Me?
I've been assigned to a lunar mission!
And I get to be Vince's backup!
Welcome to Orion.
This is it... I finally made it!
We'll be sitting in the left rear seat, up top.
Yes, sir.
C-Can I sit down for a quick moment?
You have one moment.
Whoa! Coming in!
Wow, this is great!
Nanba Mutta, are you ready to go?
Am I ready?
I've been ready since I was a kid.
What? The weather isn't looking good?
Don't worry about it.
Stop dawdling, and light this giant candle.
How many minutes will your quick moment take?
S-Sorry about that...
Today, we'll start by learning about the Orion spacecraft.
Yes, sir!
Three more laps!
I didn't expect Nanba to beat us into space...
I had a feeling it would happen, so I wasn't all that shocked.
What's going to happen to us now?
Good question.
You're up next, Kenji.
Excuse me.
Come in, Mr. Makabe.
Let's talk over here.
Yes, sir.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
I was told to take a seat first.
Could you bring us coffee?
Yes, sir.
And the chief was being unusually considerate.
That was when I knew...
I see how it is...
I won't get to go to the moon.
I want to make something clear.
We are not saying that Nanba Mutta is a better astronaut than you.
I'm sure that after undergoing NEEMO training with him, you can understand our decision
to send Nanba Mutta to the moon.
Yes, I fully agree with your decision.
Honestly, this makes me wonder why I've been training for the moon
for such a long time.
I know... The answer is obvious.
What took a very long time to build up
takes mere moments to destroy.
So what happens next?
It will probably take some time.
But when you are chosen to go to space...
What's going to happen to us now?
Good question.
We don't get to go to the moon...
But we're still astronauts, Nitta.
As long as we don't give up on being astronauts, we'll make it into space eventually.
Yeah, that's true.
Exiting the atmosphere is an accomplishment in itself.
But I'm curious about Chief Butler's last words.
Oh, there you are, Ken... Rei.
I've been looking for you.
Komachi.
There's been a change in your schedule for the day.
You're about to get real busy!
Huh? Busy?
That's a surprise.
Let's get going.
You'll be undergoing zero-gravity training in the NBL.
Zero-gravity training?
Does that mean prepping for the ISS?
Zero gravity, huh?
Sorry, Fuuka.
Unfortunately, it seems
I won't be going to the moon.
Why won't you be going to the moon?
Why, indeed?
That sucks!
You said you were going to the moon!
That's what you said!
So why not?
That really sucks!
Jeez! Building this took forever!
You know, Fuuka...
You can always start over.
I don't wanna.
Next time around, you'll do a better job.
Can you hear me, Nitta?
Yeah, I hear you.
I was also wondering about the chief's last words.
It will probably take some time.
But when you are chosen to go to space,
you will understand why we decided on
these assignments.
What did he mean?
This is it, Hibito.
Yeah.
Don't worry. Just act normally.
Okay.
I'll b-be here to watch you succeed, Hibito.
Thanks, Lowry.
Why are you more nervous than I am?
Here you go.
And so, I told him that you're a big fan of Japan...
I'm supposed to wear these?
Pretty please? We have to make my lie real...
Beautiful
It's beautiful!
So, Hibito...
Sh-She's wearing my T-shirt!
Th-Thank—
Okay, then.
R-Right...
I'm good.
Are you ready, Hibito?
You bet.
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#90 A Small Note and a Big Lucky Charm
It's finally time for the active duty test.
It's okay. This is the last step.
The question is where you go from here, Hibito.
Can you cope with this surprise?
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"A Small Note and a Big Lucky Charm"