Casting a spell that will make sure they meet.
Futari ga kitto deaeru youna mahou wo kakete.
They pile their hands atop another and see, they smile.
Ryoute wo sotto kasanete hora hohoemu kara.
Pretending not to realize their true feelings
Honto no kimochi kizukanaifuri shite
And the two suddenly
Totsuzenfutari
fall in love.
koi ni ochitano
I want to embrace only you.
Dakishimetainoni.
Let me be with you.
There we go.
All right, that's all.
You're sure nothing's unpacked?
I'll go take a quick look.
Sorry to trouble you.
Chi.
So that he could live with Shimizu-sensei...
...Shinbo decided to move.
Everything really is gone now...
BChi Answers B
The kidnapping scandal's over now.
Everyday life has returned.
I still go to prep school...
...and still work at My Pleasure.
Japanese Pub
My
Pleasure
Still, everything looks like it's the same as before...
...but there's something slightly different all around.
Chi has resumed going to work at Tirol.
She works happily now, as if
nothing had happened.
As if nothing had happened...
Hey, Motosuwa!
Is something wrong?
You're fine! You didn't leave anything!
And that's it!
Thanks for helping out.
Well, Motosuwa, see you.
Yeah, at prep school.
Yeah, something is different...
And that's why I wanted to
find out more about it...
Why did you put your hand on my head?
Kotoko really is as tall as Sumomo.
Yup, Sumomo is 16 cm tall!
I didn't ask!
Oh, hello, this is Motosuwa.
And how is it on your end?
Yeah...
Okay, I'll head there now.
See you.
Hideki heading out?
Yeah. Chi, come with me.
Chi will go.
You know, Chi...
Chi?
Is work and stuff fun?
Chi has fun at work.
What's fun about it?
Chi works. Hideki is happy.
No, that's not what I mean...
You know, like it's fun to actually be doing your tasks...
Chi prefers now over work.
Together with Hideki.
Chi has fun.
I see...
It's kind of strange.
I don't know much about persocoms...
But masters must be something
special to persocoms.
Or is it that what the last master programmed was left behind?
Chi.
This must be the destination!
I know it!
This place is registered in Sumomo's map data!
Is this the place?
Yeah.
This is Kokubunji Minoru-sama's house!
Yes?
Welcome, Motosuwa-sama.
Hello, Yuzuki-san.
Please enter.
It's always amazing here...
Motosuwa-san.
We're all busy, so nobody can come greet you right now.
I'm sorry, but you can just come to my study.
S-Sure...
Amazing... a PA system in a normal house.
Oh, and watch your step.
This is...
What's going on?
They're looking things up.
Looking things up...
Come in.
Hey.
Sorry, I know you're busy.
No...
Chi-san came with you?
Yeah, I was worried about leaving her alone in the room...
Anything happen since?
No, it's nothing like that...
I see... I'm glad.
I'll take a short break now.
You should rest, too.
Yes.
I compiled all the information I could research about her.
I'm still going through it...
Thanks.
Can't you wait more quietly?
I'm programmed this way!
I have no idea what kind of persocom Chi is.
I thought it was all right that way...
But if something happens to Chi again later...
...and something horrible happens to her...
...I can't do anything the way I am now.
That's why I want to know
exactly what Chi is now.
Yeah, I'm willing to help out
as much as I can, too.
And about the contents.
From what I gather of the data...
...the chobits' development seems to have a hidden side.
Hidden?
Well, most of it doesn't go much further than an urban legend...
...so listen as if it was one.
The "chobits" series, said to be the ultimate persocoms...
...have a certain syndicate influencing it.
When persocoms were first being created...
...the developers of the persocom and their client, the syndicate...
...seem to have had a disagreement.
After much interference from the syndicate...
...the developers started to become irritated.
And then...
They created a special persocom unbeknownst to the syndicate.
That is...
"Chobits"?
That's right.
I think it's something that puts...
...the syndicate at a terrible disadvantage.
And what's their purpose?
Well, I haven't gotten that far...
I see...
I'm sorry, Motosuwa-san.
You don't have to apologize.
You're being very good to me, Minoru-kun.
My careless actions...
...were basically what caused that kidnapping the other day.
That's why I want to help you all.
Minoru-kun...
No, that's not all...
I want you all to be more—
Yuzuki!
I brought some tea.
Why are you serving...
The maid persocoms are
being used by the system.
What are you talking about? You're the center of that system!
You must be tired from it all,
so you have to rest! All right?
Minoru-sama...
Thank you so much.
I'll do the rest, so you relax.
Eh?
Minoru-kun!
Minoru-sama!
It's a relief that he'll be better
after a good night's rest, but...
To be tired enough to collapse...
Can it be he hasn't gotten any sleep recently?
Correct...
Because I asked him to do this research...
It is not your fault, Motosuwa-sama.
It's because I don't have enough machine power...
Not at all!
If my processing speed were faster...
...I wouldn't have stressed Minoru-sama this much.
If only I were more useful...
Yuzuki-san...
If there was a way to do something...
You can't say there isn't a way.
You're Kojima!
How dare you show up...!
Damn it!
Ouch...
What do you think you're doing here, huh?
Wait, M asked me to lend
him my persocoms!
M?
Minoru-sama asked for aid in the research.
Kojima-sama also has much knowledge of persocoms...
I feel bad about what I did the other day.
My curiosity was a bit much.
That's why I'm helping...
And how are you going to?
You heard about the syndicate
involved in the chobits project?
What about it?
The quickest way...
...is to hack into the main
computer of that syndicate.
H-Hacking...
What does that mean?
Is this the place to get upset?
Hacking is to illegally enter a system where you...
...originally have no access.
Right, in other words, tapping into the computer.
You can do such a thing?
Of course.
We have a good idea who we're facing, but there are risks.
Risks? What kind?
We're not facing an ordinary server.
There will be many security programs, of course.
The worst case would be a crash.
A-A crash is...!
Data gets lost, and memory gets wiped.
If it's even worse, the hard disk itself becomes totally useless.
Then that's no good!
You want Yuzuki-san to do that?
Nobody said that, right?
Actually, M was against it.
Minoru-sama?
Yeah, I suggested it.
To gamble and let you hack in.
But then...
Never say that again.
I won't allow it.
But that's the most efficient—
I know that!
I know that, but I can't let Yuzuki do something like that!
Minoru-sama...
It was unexpected.
That M was not jumping out at a tasty morsel of information.
Of course.
Yuzuki-san is no ordinary
persocom for Minoru-kun.
But as long as we don't take that approach...
...we have to keep doing it the long way.
At this rate, I don't know when
he'll collapse again...
To make it easier on Minoru-kun, you just have to work harder!
Work two, no, three times as hard!
I'll keep an eye on you so you don't ditch!
What?
I'll stay the night.
I'm worried about Minoru-kun.
H-Hey, hold on...
Where's your workroom?
I'll go! I'll go so let go! Come on!
He's asleep.
Do your job!
The one who programmed me to only speak the truth was you.
Fine, I'll do it! I'll do it!
Kotoko...
No, most persocoms don't tell lies.
That's because they were programmed that way.
Then Yuzuki-san earlier...
If only I could be of more use...
If that's the truth...
Then there's something...
Chi-san.
Hideki said to check up.
Everything is all right here.
Yuzuki?
That is Minoru-sama's elder sister.
Elder sister...?
Not Yuzuki?
No.
I am different from his sister.
I was made to be just like her...
...and I have various data about her.
But I am not her.
The real elder sister would surely...
...be of better use to Master Minoru.
If you felt you really wanted to be of use to Motosuwa-sama...
...would you do anything?
Anything?
For example...
Something that will break you?
Chi is glad when Hideki is happy.
If it will make Hideki happy...
...I would.
Yuzuki...
What the?
The persocoms are acting funny, too.
If the power is this unstable, it will hinder our operation.
Guess I'll access house security.
What's wrong?
That's strange...
All of the house's power is in one area...
Someone's using the study's system.
The study?
Minoru-kun's?
Come on, who is it this late at night?
Someone is coming in.
Yeah.
Whoa, this guy's coming in over my security program.
Can it be her?
No, it's a pretty good persocom, though.
I'm connecting.
Minoru-kun! Are you there?
The doctor said not to exert...
Motosuwa-san?
Minoru-kun?
Then who's using this room?
The only one other than me with access...
Yuzuki! Yuzuki, you're in there, right?
Yuzuki, open this door!
Minoru-sama...
Yuzuki, what are you doing? Open this door!
Why would Yuzuki-san do this without telling Minoru?
Minoru-sama.
Yuzuki-san?
She's using the mansion's PA circuit.
I am hacking into the syndicate's server...
...as determined by Kojima-sama.
Currently deciphering the fifth password.
Stop it! It's risky!
If you unknowingly unlock it,
the security program will kick in!
I...
...couldn't understand how you felt, Minoru-sama.
Yuzuki...
Though knowing this was the best way...
...you thought about me, and you...
But I'm sure that your real elder sister would have understood...
What are you talking about?
Why are you...
That's right.
What are you talking about?
Because you have data about his sister?
If you can act like his sister, you don't care what else happens?
Is that what the program is?
Something's wrong with that.
That's just so...
I...
...want to be of use to him just as his elder sister had been.
That's not the same...
It's not the same!
You're not my sister!
Decryption complete.
Commencing data download.
Yuzuki!
The lock...
Yuzuki! Yuzuki!
What a rough way of sending them off.
I can't forgive anyone for entering you.
When you say that, you sound
like you're jealous.
We're both persocoms, you know.
Yuzuki,
you came to.
Minoru-sama... Everyone...
Don't overexert yourself.
I'm done with the basic checkups.
It looks like she has no major failures.
I'm glad...
You surprised us.
It was good this guy burnt off relatively quickly.
I am sorry to have worried you.
I will do a self-scan now.
Okay.
Minoru-sama...
What is it?
Some data has been lost.
Data concerning your elder sister.
Minoru-kun...
Please enter the data of
your elder sister again.
What else?
Nothing, it was in another memory partition.
I see, then...
I won't enter any data about my sister.
When my sister died...
I couldn't come to accept it...
...and I couldn't forget her.
No, I didn't want to forget,
so I made you, Yuzuki.
Making you as close as possible to the sister I remembered.
But you're not my older sister.
I am terribly sorry.
Because I'm not—
It's not that.
Nobody can replace my older sister.
That's why there's nothing that can replace you, either.
There's no replacement for me?
That's right.
But I am a persocom...
But I can't think of any other persocom in the same way.
Even if it's all been programmed...
...Yuzuki is Yuzuki.
I won't enter any more data about my sister.
I think I'll always cherish the time I spent with my sister in my heart.
But the times that you've been with me...
...are precious memories as well.
That's why I want to continue making them.
Not as my sister's replacement, but precious time with you.
A lot of time, little by little.
I can stay by your side...
...even if I cannot replace your sister?
I want none other than you to be at my side.
Minoru-sama...
It's already morning!
Yuzuki...
Yuzuki looked happy.
That's true.
Chi is happy too.
Hideki, what are memories?
Oh, well, let's see...
Important things that stick
inside your heart, I guess.
But they're things that can't easily be reentered, unlike data.
Do Chi and Hideki have memories?
Yeah.
Chi!
Things that can't easily be
reentered, unlike data...
There really is something...
Motosuwa-san.
Minoru-kun, are you all right?
Sorry to have troubled you so.
No, it's my fault for asking you to do this in the first place.
It's all right.
I'll continue the search.
Thank you...
But don't go out of your way, okay?
All right.
Take this.
A part of the data that Yuzuki
downloaded earlier.
Oh, that.
I'll take a close look later, but it's probably...
...a list of persocom developers.
There's also an image, but
I think you'll be surprised.
Manager-san! Manager-san!
She's not here?
That's probably the central
figure in the development.
What in the world is going on?
Hibiya-san...
The town in the evening is quiet
Yoru no machi wa shizuka de
and is just like the deep sea.
fukai umi no you.
I am there all alone on the continuous road.
Tsuzuku michi ni tada atashi hitori dake.
Relying on a voice from afar
Tooi koe wo tayori ni
I keep walking.
aruite yukuno.
I have been searching for a while
Zutto sagashiteru
for a feeling that softly glimmers.
sotto hikaru omoi.
A light...
Hikari...
You know, after finding you
Nee anata wo mitsukete
I will never forget about you again.
soshite nidoto wasurezu.
No matter how much my heart hurts
Donna ni mune ga itakutemo
I will be at your side.
soba ni iruno.
Forever...
Zutto...
Hideki, when are you happy?
Let's see...
When I eat lots of yummy food.
When I get a good score on a prep school test.
That and...
When you hold hands?
Yeah, I'm happy when I hold hands, too.
But why are you asking that, Chi?
Chi...
Next time on Chobits.
BChi Wears and Takes Off B
Chi Wears and Takes Off.
Everyone's happy when they hold hands!
Chi!