This is a huge help.
Thanks, Honda-chan!
We don't need anything too concrete
from you this week, Honda-san.
How about you work on poses
and faces for the characters?
That's what Seki-senpai told me
at the end of the camp...
Faces are hard to do, though.
Mine aren't turning out cute at all.
But I have a friend in
the Illustration Club...
Hey, Yumine...
I'm so sorry...
Haruji-kun was seriously god-tier yesteday...
I got on the forum after it was over and was
posting about shipping until five this morning...
It might not be the best day...
Mitsukeyou make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga aru no sa
Sonnan ja hottarakashi de
Sonnan ja hottokenakute
Iesu or noo ha itsumo kakureteru
Daijoubu sa tte ietara
Daijoubu tte omoeta
Akkenai kurai de okashikatta
Konna wakuwaku o oikaketeru kimochi ga
Kinou made no jibun no souzou o koete yuku
Konnichiwa make my day
Minna ga motteru mahou
Isshou de ichiban no nani ka ga mieru
Deaeru yo make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga matteru
Skill Up
I need to make the faces pop,
and on original characters, too.
But how?
Honda-san! What'cha doing?
Lemme in on it!
That's Marika Shimizu.
She's a half-Japanese girl in my year.
You're drawing!
You do manga or something?
Um, something like that...
It looked like you had that whole ennui thing
going on. Got a bit of the creative angst?
I don't think it's that fancy...
How about letting old Marika help you out?
I bet you could totally
make a good portrait of me!
I'm pretty sure she's making fun of me...
Hmm... it might fit the game better
if their expressions were a little livelier...
"Livelier..."
Sounds like someone's an expert!
You do manga too, Fuda-san?
I'm an illustrator.
Well listen to you! Bet
you two're gonna be big!
Whoops...
What's with you, Honda-san?
You can't just go messing
with people like that.
You okay, Honda-san?
I think so...
That's Natsu Iino.
Another one of my classmates
who absolutely loves pets.
I remember now.
You're in that club with the super long name.
The one with the eyes?
The Slack-eyed Night-owl
Shuttle-runners Club.
We make games.
Wow...
What?! You can make games?!
They're doujin games.
Nothing too big, really.
What's a doujin?
They already have a game
and I played it yesterday,
but when I try to draw,
it's like I just don't have the knack...
You're doing it wrong.
You can't play games for more than an hour.
Wha...? Oh, yeah.
You might be right...
But I feel like I've almost got it,
so I start sketching in class
instead of listening...
Honda-san, you take the next sentence.
Honda-san?
What?! Um... "A year after the revolution,
a court of rights had been established..."
I meant the one before that.
S-sorry...
Try to pay attention.
Okay.
The cotton industry went from manual labor
to a mechanical process,
Maybe I’ve been possessed...
and the steam engine became a necessary…
Start scribbling in history class
and next thing you know, your drawings
start looking like historical figures.
R-right...
I wanted to get some more advice
from Yumine during lunch, but...
she's still sleeping...
Hey, Iino! I picked up my first
shoujo manga in a while yesterday!
Oh?
Please read this letter!
Thump
The heroine helps out all sorts of people!
And that includes shy, lovesick boys!
I sure could learn a lot from her!
You know you're not supposed to
bring manga to school, right?
Wrong! That character's...
Rensuke-kyun is a monster of a wanton sub!
Go back to volume sixteen
and you'll all know I was right!
Maybe you should start with volume three
of the absolute masterpiece Majiroma...
I don't think she's taking questions...
So I left school without fixing my problem.
And I still don't have a clue
how to draw a good face...
What do I do?
Oh, yeah!
Granny made me a treat!
Homemade lollipops!
Maybe I could do an exaggerated face
of how happy I feel right now...
And now to eat one!
I dropped it. Forgive me, Granny...
Guess it's just one of those days...
This is the worst...
I wish... I wish I could just be a cat...
Meow...
Meow?
Meow... Meow... Meow, meow!
And a stranger catches me doing it...
Hey little kitty.
Could you meow for me again?
That was super cute!
Hello...
I know it's getting dark out, but there's no need
to be all boohoo over a little candy.
That's not the only reason.
I got asked to do something
and I just can't get it right...
I don't know what to do...
Would you look at those skinny little legs?!
Have you been eating right?
You need a good, healthy meal!
What?! She's not even listening!
Hrm... so you're having trouble drawing?
Yeah.
And my friends were making fun of me...
Well, you can call me Teru!
And don't worry, I won't
razz you or anything.
Heck, I could even model for you
to make sure those pictures turn out good!
Now she's making fun of me, too!
I'm being serious!
To tell you the truth, I'm
pretty particular about art.
Are you really?
How 'bout I take a look?
Wait... Don't tell me...
What is it?
Nothing...
But I think I'll be holding on to this!
What?!
But I've got some magic for my little kitty
that'll make her feel all better!
And now she's treating me
to food at some café...
What is happening right now?
Some of my friends on campus
told me about this place.
They've got the best pancakes!
Eat up now and get nice
and healthy, little kitty!
Um, do you think I could have that back?
My senpai, my friend, they've both looked at it
and it's really important to me...
Why?
I mean making games is pretty hard.
Why worry so much over it?
Are you drawing because they make you?
Well I...
I just didn't want to be lazy anymore...
Okay then. Now you want
to go into blend mode...
What I want is a place we can
be without feeling bored.
Take that first step.
Focus on finishing one thing first.
And I think we can do more with her
being able to hear those voices!
Stop! That's something completely different!
Think I'll try to get in
a little more practice.
That's not why!
We had a training camp and it was
so fun working together, and...
And I...!
Very well!
What?
You'll do fine with that attitude!
I'm looking forward to seeing
the finished product!
Somehow it felt like she
got me in her claws...
Wait a second...
When did I say I was making a game?
Wait... Honda-san?
What're you doing here?
Hey, Iino-san. I'm not sure myself, honestly.
I was having tea with someone
I met by the river...
What?
Didn't anyone ever tell you
not to go places with strangers?
Well, when you put it that way...
Café & Restaurant
Welcome!
Meow!
T...Teru-senpai?!
And she sees right through the disguise!
You're getting better, Fuyon!
Could you please not call me that?
Anyway, I came here 'cause
I've got something for my little Fuyon!
And you still don't listen to people.
Tada!
Your sweet senpai's brought
her kouhai the funds of love!
What?! Is that money?!
I met the cutest little kitten.
Consider it a donation! Spend it wisely, now!
Thank you so much! But why...?
And what kitten?
Meow meow meow.
Meow meow meow meow meow.
Use words, please!
They'll be here soon.
Okay.
Hey, there!
Thanks for coming on the expedition!
It's my pleasure. Thanks for today!
Sorry about the wait.
No, we weren't waiting at all!
Hey, you think you could cut
it out with the explosions?
Where are we going today?
An electronics shop?
Yup. We're going to get you a scanner
so you can put your pictures on the computer.
You bring the club funds, Seki-san?
What?
We used all that up in April.
I thought the Captain was
supposed to bring the money.
What? This is the first
time I'm hearing of it.
Oh no! My daddy said I couldn't get
an advance on my allowance!
And he always means what he says!
Seriously?!
Just kidding. We've got funding
from the OG for today.
Whoa! From Teru-senpai?
She said she was making a donation
'cause she met a cute kitten or something?
She's always been wild!
A kitten?
I'll just be holding on to this!
So that weird thing that happened...
What was her name again?
I was so worried over my
sketchbook I forgot...
What's with you?
I think this one's pretty reasonable.
Sure, why not? Nothing
wrong with going orthodox.
What do you think, Honda-chan?
I'll make sure I learn how to use it!
All you do is put the paper
on and close the lid.
It's not that hard.
I left my sketchbook at the food court!
Wait here while I get it!
O-okay.
Honda-san?!
It started raining, but
my sketchbook's just fine!
THAT'S what you're worried
about? You'll catch cold!
Good thing your house is close, Aya.
We're coming in!
Sure. My brothers will
probably bug you, though.
Here are some towels, Aya!
Well look at you, Nobuhito!
I'm hungry, Aya!
Could you get a clue?!
Let's just make sure your hair's all dry!
Thank you!
Hm? What's with you, Haruma?
Uh, nothing...
but what's with the elementary schooler?
Honda-san's older than you, dummy.
Seriously?!
She's in junior high...
Thought she was my age.
It's going to take a minute to draw a bath.
This is my, or should I say our, room.
Okay!
And oh yeah! Haruma's a pretty savvy artist.
Certificate
3rd Place
Haruma Seki
Would you look at these colors?
You don't have a thing to be shy about!
Maybe you could teach me a thing or two?
Is she talking to him?
Well, well!
Whoa! It's bleeding all over the place!
You gotta let it soak in and spread.
And start where it's thinnest.
The bath's ready!
Oh! Okay!
It's gonna be all blotchy
unless you get it right the first time.
Not like that!
You can't do THIS? It's basic stuff.
Stab
I-I'll do my best.
You went through all that trouble
teaching me. I'm so sorry...
Oh, no... I mean, it's not...
You reap what you sow...
This is good stuff.
Hope she likes wearing my clothes...
Wonder if they'll fit?
Why not? You're like an ironing board.
What's that? You saying
Honda-san's a little stumpy?
Maybe I should let her know?
Then maybe I'll have to show Mom and Dad
your little black book?
Why would you go and do that?!
My big sister's a big chicken!
Would you shut it, you midget?!
Mary Sue!
They're fighting, Shii!
Don't mind them. They'll stop in a minute.
I'll set the clothes down here.
You start where it's thin and
let it soak into the paper...
And then...
You alright in there?
What? I'm okay!
How about you write it
down before you forget?
Yeah! I can do that!
Alright then!
Now put on some clothes
before you catch a chill!
You hear me?
Okay!
Maybe this is right? It's so hard...
You draw super good!
Thanks, Nobuhito.
Do you really think I can make good stuff
for the game by coloring like this?
I think it'll give it a special look.
Can you check to see if I
colored it right, Haruma?
Why're you asking me?
Don't you think that's a little rude?
Wait, what happened to your forehead?
Somebody popped me.
What a dork!
My own big sister!
Of course I did. He wasn't backing down...
Now about my picture...
Wait, where'd it go?
Sorry about that. I borrowed it.
Want to see what it'll look like in the game?
A preview of sorts.
What? Already?
What? We get to see it now?
I don't think I'm ready for this...
I wanna see!
G-go ahead, then!
Never knew you could use
traditional media like that in games!
Right?
It's all blotchy. And the linework's a mess.
You little...
And next up is Samü.
Is it just me, or is that pretty good?
What about the human dialog box?
I haven't finished him yet!
Which means you're still
working out the kinks.
I mean he's an original character.
You've still got some
designing to do, Honda-chan!
I know, but I'm having trouble
getting his face right.
It's the only thing I can think about.
That's what's got you all worried?
Yeah. It just gets more fuzzy
the more I think about it...
You know your head's not the
only thing you can think with!
cool older men
You can look at stuff like this.
Or you could take a walk outside
and try to find a good model.
You wanna draw? You gotta observe.
Y-you're totally right! I
didn't even think of that!
Well, look who's saved the day!
Seriously, this is basic stuff.
I see...
I find someone who fits what I'm thinking of
and use them as a model...
Thank you so much, Haruma-kun!
But don't do a straight-up copy.
Just a hint. Models have rights
about their likeness and stuff.
Sure! Thank you so much!
Look at the little man blush...
Funny, isn't it?
I think I might be able to
get the faces right now...
Oh.
And that girl gave me a hint, too...
Daddy?
You're going to pick me up?!
Aw, man. We could've gone out for dinner.
I think someone's homesick.
Wonder if he'll be here soon!
I can't wait to show him!
I want to ask, Honda-chan.
Is there a boy you like?
What?!
Why are you asking me that?!
Just curious is all!
The only thing on my mind is my daddy!
He said he'd look at my
pictures when we get home!
Wow. You two sure do get along!
Wonder if she's into older men?
Being a first-year and still loving your daddy
that much. Might be a good thing.
Really? I thought it was normal...
She's in HIGH SCHOOL?
Huh? What is it now?
Thank you for all the help!
Good work today!
See you tomorrow!
It's just puppy love, anyway.
No need to hold on to it.
Big talk from someone who's
never even been in love...
Who the heck needs love?!
Easy to say when no one loves you!
Quiet, hobbit!
Mary! Sue!
Loser!
They're doing it again, Shii!
They are... Don't worry,
we'll have dinner soon...
To-do-i-te i-ma-su ka
Akogare shisen tsumasaki senobi
Fu-ra-ra na-ga-sa-re
Muchuu no umi o oyogu
Rurabii
Yurara
Honda-san fainted!
Don't leave me here, Senpai!
Aw, who the heck cares!
I thought we made something pretty fun!
Countdown