What's wrong, Shii?!
Honda-san's fainted!
Let's find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
Because there's a world where
only love will carry on
Left all alone like that
But you still can't leave it be
Yes or no, it's always hiding
If you could say it was okay
You could think it was okay
Strange that it was just that quick
The feeling of chasing this kind of thrill
Will be more than you could
have imagined yesterday
Hello, make my day
The magic that we all hold
You'll see the greatest
something of your life
We'll find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
There's a world waiting where
only love will carry on
Countdown
Shii! How's Honda-san holding up?
Aya...
I'm sorry to tell you this, but...
she's buried under a
mountain of old man manga.
She can hardly breathe.
I'm so sorry. You really didn't need
to check up on me...
It's just a little cold...
I'll be better before you know it.
The seasons are changing.
You need to rest up.
Thank you...
Bless you for coming all this way.
No way! We're sorry for intruding...
Is your mom out today, too?
She's really busy at work.
She told me she'd come home
as soon as she could.
100.2 degrees. That's pretty high.
Do you think you could stay by
Tamaki's side for a bit?
I'll head to the pharmacy and
get her some medicine.
I'm sure we could-
Not on these roads.
It's a real mess on the
other side of the station.
Well in that case, I suppose we can.
Not like there's much for
us to do on a Sunday.
I'm counting on you.
We'll be fine. Don't worry.
Be safe out there!
Weren't you saying something about
old man manga before, Shii?
Oh. About that-
I thought I could at
least draw some pictures,
but when I tried they turned out all wrong.
What do you mean, all wrong?
If I try to draw when I'm not feeling good,
all the characters have old man faces...
W-well I'm just glad you're okay!
Why'd you have to get me all worried, Shii?!
You leave me alone at an away game and
I'm bound to commit some faux pas.
Plus I'm not the best communicator and
I needed someone to come with me.
Always with the negativity...
And I left you a present while I was at it.
When did you do that?!
Hello?
Is this Haruma?
You know the scenarios
Aya has in the living room?
You can go ahead and read them.
What the heck are you doing?! I hid those!
Lower your voice, Aya.
I'm so sorry, Honda-san!
S-sorry! I'm okay...
Hello?! What's going on over there?
Nothing at all.
Go ahead and mark any typos
or missing words you see.
What's Haruma gonna say when I get home?!
Hey! Stop laughing!
You're laughing at my scenario, aren't you?!
Hey, this is editing.
Why am I doing this?!
The jig is up...
I'm so sorry.
You can't relax with us like this, can you?
Want us to go out into the hallway?
Oh, no! I'm fine...
I'm the one who should be saying sorry!
I was supposed to finish today...
That's right. A sheet of
finalized expressions.
I think you just made me feel worse...
How are you feeling, Fujikawa-san?
Can I count on you to finish
up early, Fujikawa-san?
How are you feeling, Fujikawa-san?
Can I count on you to finish up early?
No problem, Captain. Don't worry about a thing.
No problem, Captain. Don't
worry about a thing.
I didn't get anything done, all I did was sleep.
I think I owe you an apology...
What are you saying?
This is our club room for today.
That's enough, don't you think?
What's that supposed to mean?
She's programming now.
Maybe she wants me to get
better so I can draw?
I'll be here until you're cured.
Or maybe she can still program
while I'm like this?!
Captain... I don't understand...
Take good care of her, Aya!
What?! You're running away!
Senpai!
Don't leave me here, Senpai!
Ayame’s house
Wh-what're you doing to Honda-senpai?!
Would you shut up!
You and the Captain have been friends
for a long time, haven't you?
Yeah, since we were
fifth-years in elementary.
She's always been a pushover
with a tongue of lead.
She was even scared of Fujikawa-san at first.
And her whole thing with crowds...
We went to Wintercom and she went home
as soon as we left the station...
Oh!
Wintercom... that's the Winter
Comical Market, isn't it?
Yeah, that's right! Wintercom!
Someone's gotten herself
a little learned, I see!
Anyway, back to Shii.
She's never been one to blurt
out what she's thinking.
Maybe she's getting used to being Captain,
but when I was trying to catch
up on the plot at camp...
We miss the deadline for the plot and
there's going to be trouble down the line.
Maybe I should do the odd-jobs?
No way, I'm going to do
everything according to plan!
Or maybe you break the next deadline
and I give our friends a little
history lesson on Aya's dark past?
Take them. I beg you.
Talk about effective...
It sure is taking her a while...
But... what did she mean
by what she said before?
Hm? Before?
She said this was our club room for today.
Maybe she's mad at me since I can't work?
I'm pretty sure she's having
the time of her life.
You can tell?
We've been together for a while.
"This is our club room today."
Probably her way of saying
you don't have to worry
about work while you're fighting that cold.
Like you're doing your
job as a member and all.
Shii really cares about the SNS Club
in her own weird way.
And you always give it 110%.
She'd never want to
discourage our dear kouhai.
Oh.
Try to keep the rumors
to a minimum, Mary Sue.
Welcome back!
Oh! You were heating up some okayu!
Store bought Okayu. I brought it from home.
Thank you so much.
I'll have some now.
I gave us plenty of leeway between
our planned finish date and Summer Comiket,
That's so good!
so we don't have much to worry about
in terms of schedule.
Really?
We're in the first half of June.
(Today)
Title
Poses                                                 Other
Poses                              Color, final touches
Line work
I'd planned for us to have
the character art done this month.
(Today)
Title
Poses                                                 Other
Poses
Line work                                                                             Unfinished
Finished
Most of the line work's already done.
We can probably spend the whole month
making sure everything's done right.
Mid-August
Title                                 Loss time
Other
Summer Comiket
And you can take it slow
since we have exams in July.
Finish the title art and we should be done
with plenty of time to spare.
That makes me feel better.
You took care of everything.
Right now you need to
focus on getting better.
What's with you, Aya? You're so quiet.
Huh?
D-don't tell me you caught my cold?!
No way! I'm A-OK!
I'm home!
I snapped up some medicine!
Granny's home!
Now you just take that medicine and relax.
Okay!
And the next day I was all better.
Honda-chan! Over here!
Hi, everyone!
Sorry I couldn't make it yesterday.
The Captain told me I needed to work at home.
Sorry to make you worry.
And thank you so much for yesterday.
Tell Haruma-kun I said thanks, too.
Oh, sure!
Never been in love and
you're writing this romantic stuff.
Wonderful senpai and a
wonderful high school...
It makes every day amazing.
I wish it could stay like this forever...
Oh, and we're out.
Out of what?
Summer Comiket.
What?!
Sorry! I just couldn't tell you yesterday!
Dear Slack-eyed NS,
We regret to inform you that you were
not picked in this year's drawing.
not picked
W-well, I can't say I wasn't expecting it...
But that means...
...we'll have a finished game
and no way to show it off.
What?!
I-it's fine!
I got us into Disc Only
just in case this happened!
And all we have to do is finish it in time!
Disc Only
What a relief, am I right?!
And when does it start?
Huh?
Entry Ticket
Event Date:  Sunday, June 9th
In six days.
I'm going now!
Tama-chan! What're you doing in
your uniform on a Satuday?
We've got a club sleepover.
Like a work camp?
Yeah!
And you got permission for that?
We talked to the student council.
The deadline's a little harsh,
but we're going to give it our best shot.
We all worked on it.
And look! I'm bringing the scanner,
my sketchbook, and my sleepover stuff!
And when are you supposed to finish?
They said tonight!
And then we're supposed to go
straight to the event the next day.
Wow...
I'll see you later, Yumine.
Sure.
Have a good time.
Maybe I could borrow that pillow?
Good morning!
SNS
Club
Thanks for coming out!
That makes three of us.
Fujikawa-senpai couldn't make it?
Apparently, it's hard for her to finish the songs
without her home equipment?
Oh...
The best she can do outside
is mess around with melodies.
She said you really need a good
set of headphones for mastering.
She sure sounds like a professional.
Though I don't really get it...
Alright, then.
Did you two bring what I told you?
Didn't you say bring something that
would give us some energy
when we feel worn out?
I brought this.
And I brought this.
What'd you bring, Honda-san?
I brought this...
A photo...
Is that your dad?
Yeah!
My grades weren't all that good back then,
but whenever I looked at this picture,
I wanted to study my heart out...
I... I can't look directly at her.
Should she be here?!
She's too good for the killing floor!
Let's start by going over our tasks.
Honda-san:
Cover art (by the 19th)
Use the remaining time
to flesh out different faces
Honda-san, I'd really appreciate it
if you had the jacket done by 7:00 PM.
Okay!
I brought a laptop that you can use.
Understood.
Wait up!
Isn't my list a little long?!
Seki:
Finish scenarios
Script reading
Debugging               Supplies
That's your penalty for
keeping it quiet for a whole day.
Well I was pretty sure we
weren't gonna try to do it in a week,
so maybe I could get a suspended sentence...
Me and my senpai are going to
do our best today, Daddy!
Aw, who the heck cares!
It's just a little work!
Good hustle.
Hm? It's a tap from Fujikawa-san.
I knew all the royalty-free sound effects
would be super boring.
Mind if I start with those
instead of the background music?
We don't have time! Just do what I told you!
I'll get it done, promise!
Am I doing the line work right?
You are. It looks good.
I think it's a little different
from what I drew before...
You think so? We don't mind.
I mean, I got a little worried when I was
looking at my old pictures and I
thought I could do them over...
Just a thought...
We don't have time for that.
You're so right!
I'm mostly finished doing the designing.
Oh! It looks so cool all monotone like that!
You sure you didn't just paint over everything
and slap on some icons?
Test
Flat design is very in these days.
I dunno. Looks like amateur hour
with a whole pile of cut corners-
Flat. Design.
Uh, right...
It's lunchtime and I'm
getting a little sleepy...
But I can't give up.
There's not much time left
and they're working so hard...
Just leave the scripting
to me. It'll be cake...
Bugs at the front gate, abends at the back.
Bugs... Bugs...
W-we can do this!
Bugs...
It's getting late. How are we doing?
N-normal... I think...
That's no good!
What we need is focus!
Senpai! You can't sit
cross-legged in a skirt...
Later for that!
Lai Lai Xuan
Hello! Three orders of Szechuan noodles!
Later!
Have any of you seen a delivery man?
I was hoping maybe I could join your club...
Later!
The artwork's finished!
I'm not happy with some of the details,
but I think we can manage...
It's so late!
You said I had to be done by 7:00!
S-sorry I'm late! I, um-
Oh. Honda-san...
We can't get in contact with Fujikawa-san.
Sh-she might just be taking a nap.
A five-hour nap?
Well...
I'm calling her again.
She's not picking up.
I'll go to her house!
I'm sorry. I don't know where she lives...
Maybe we shouldn't have asked her
to do all those songs.
Probably.
She probably wants to make her own stuff
and we just throw this at her...
Worst case scenario she doesn't come back.
We need to do what we can for now.
Right. I'll look up some
royalty-free stuff...
But why?
Captain? Seki-senpai?
Are you telling me you don't trust her?
I may not know her as well as you,
but I thought we made something pretty fun!
We had a camp, we went shopping!
I just know Fujikawa-senpai...
Wait?
She's...
How do I know she's hard at work?
How can I say that we had fun making this?
Don't feel sad.
I told you at the beginning, right?
Making games is hard.
We're just a club.
We can't just rope someone into working.
She's not getting paid for this.
If she wants to quit, then
we just have to accept that.
Make doujin games!
Slack-eyed
Night-owl
Shuttle-runners
I know that, but I... I want trust her.
You've received 6 files.
Accept                           Reject
Whoo!
Here're those six songs you ordered!
I'm gonna catch some well-deserved z's!
I knew she could pull it off!
That's a relief.
She just came up with these!
This is quality stuff!
Yeah! They're really good!
Alright! We need to get
ready for the final stretch!
Okay!
Alright!
Aya, you need to go print out Honda-san's work
at the convenience store! 30 copies!
Roger!
I finished a sheet of the variations!
Okay! I'll switch it with the placeholders!
Did you make sure you can play it?
I didn't, but it'll probably work!
What about the installer?
We can use a zip file!
That's the last of the variations!
I'm sending it to you now!
Switching it in!
And we're gold!
Burning it now!
Okay!
"Magic of Stella," that's such a cute name!
Well it is the name of the heroine,
but there's another, secret meaning to it.
Another meaning?
Exactly. It's how we divided
up the work for the game.
How you divided...
Programming, artwork, scenario, sound.
It's pretty hard to finish a game just by
putting together the things people make...
Art, CG
Scenarios                                                                                    System
Music
Scheduling, odd jobs,
management, etc.
Art                                                                                                           System
Music                                                                                              Scenarios
But putting someone in charge to effectively
manage everything from the beginning...
It's a phenomenon I call
the "Magic of Stella"!
Stella does mean "star."
Right. The magic of the pentagram,
thus the Magic of Stella.
What? Is it morning already?
I remember...
We were all up late working...
Magic of Stella...
We did it, Daddy...
I feel like I took a big step today...
No time to bathe in the afterglow!
We're going directly to the show!
Okay!
It's so bright...
How much sleep did you get?
I got in a light nap.
We'll be fine! All that high energy's
gonna blow that fatigue away!
This is such a big event!
I've got the shivers!
I wonder how many clubs
are going to be there?
180!
And they had 1,300 people
come through last year!
It's certainly nothing to sneeze at.
I was so busy making it,
I never really thought about it.
This is my first doujin game event...
I wonder what it's going to be like?
Hurry up, Honda-san!
O-okay!
Have they reached you?
Longing gazes, standing on tiptoes
Washed away, reeling
Swimming through a sea of dreams
A lullaby
Swaying
I did it!
It's my treasure.
I can't go on...
I heard someone stuck up for me.
Tamaki's a top!
Direct Sales