We ended up having an unplanned
sleepover at the Captain's apartment.
We're trying to get our new game ready
in time for Summer Comiket.
And the title of the game?
Stardust Desires
Stardust Desires!
The story centers around the heroine Aya,
a girl with special powers,
and her fateful meeting with Baruta.
It's a heartwrenchingly beautiful
visual novel that's packed with drama!
I think I might need to redo this linework...
Ha-chan!
Tamaki Honda, hurry up and finish the rest...
I am.
Why would you go to sleep
when we just got to the final stage?
Now, now...
Pushing yourself won't get results,
and you're only going to feel worse later.
Just have to accept it.
We've got school tomorrow, anyway.
We still have some wiggle room in our schedule,
so we should probably call it a day.
No...
If I go home... my grandmother, she'll...
Get up if you're going to get up!
It's one in the morning...
Might be a neighbor here to
tell us we're being too loud.
Sorry for the late night
visit. My name is Iino.
I think my little sister might be here.
Sister? Well...
Let's find it, make my day
Why don't you splash some water on your face?
Thank you me for being clumsy
Oh!
Because there's a world where
only love will carry on
It's my sister!
Hey!
Left all alone like that
But you still can't leave it be
Yes or no, it's always hiding
If you could say it was okay
You could think it was okay
Strange that it was just that quick
The feeling of chasing this kind of thrill
Will be more than you could
have imagined yesterday
Hello, make my day
The magic that we all hold
You'll see the greatest
something of your life
We'll find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
There's a world waiting where
only love will carry on
I'd Prefer Not To
Were you NOT supposed to be
back by curfew, Minaha?!
Er... the thing is...
Iino-san?!
Grandmother's having a fit!
Do you have any idea what I've had to deal with?
Now you get yourself in the car.
Iino-san? What's going on here?
You're here too, eh?
Sorry for all the ruckus.
It's a family thing.
I'll get everything taken care of.
See you at school!
Did she just raid us?!
They're gone...
Never seen a car like that before.
She did say she had a big
sister when we first met...
So squinty girl's a classmate of yours?
Her name's Natsu Iino.
She sits next to me and she always
shares her textbook when I forget mine.
Wait, she's a first year like Ha-chan...
So they're twins?
But we've got more important
stuff to worry about.
Black car... Attacking...
You live here! Don't hide from guests!
The next day was Saturday.
Ha-chan didn't come to the club room.
Iino... You mean the one
with the huge estate?
I see it on my way to work.
I got to talk to Iino-san
today in class, but...
Sorry my little sis bothered you.
She's not supposed to be in any clubs
while she's in high school.
Our family's pretty strict about that.
Especially our grandmother.
Which is why she won't be
coming to Summer Comiket with us.
We did all of that work together...
What am I supposed to do?
I mean, it's a family thing.
Opening your mouth might
just make things worse.
But Ha-chan gave us the idea
for the game in the first place.
And aren't you making the music
that she asked you to, Fujikawa-senpai?
That is true...
That doesn't bother you?
Someone butting in on OUR game?
A little, I guess?
Always with the dry humor.
I'd prefer quick-witted.
Stardust Desires
Well her being gone means
our schedule's going to take a big hit.
I planned under the assumption
we'd have two artists...
I'd really prefer to have her back...
What d'you think, Honda-san?
Isn't that what you wanted at first?
To do all of the artwork yourself?
I can't accept that.
We started Stardust Desires because it's
the game Ha-chan always wanted to make!
She gave us the idea and
she's worked harder than any of us.
Now someone comes in and says
she can't do it anymore...
I'm going to her house!
I'm going to talk to Iino-san
and ask her to let Ha-chan come back!
The direct approach...
Oh, yeah! That's what I've
been waiting to hear!
Well, it wouldn't feel good
finishing the game like this.
Alright! How about we all
march right into their house?!
A crowd's just going to make it
a bigger deal than it has to be...
I think what you mean to say
is you have a heck of a time trying
to talk to people you just met.
I'll take Seki-senpai and Iris with me!
What? I'm supposed to be two people?!
I mean, we're both artists,
and I think Iris being there might
give Ha-chan a nice dose of courage!
You want to tell her who I am?!
Fujikawa-senpai, I need you
to tell me where Ha-chan lives!
You move fast don't you, Honda-san?
Well, I'm really ticked off!
Ha-chan always picks at my pictures,
and she's so selfish.
It can't just be over all of a sudden!
You said I should go as Iris, but I don't even
have my makeup today. I can't do it.
It'll be fine! If we do this right,
she'll definitely know you're Iris!
This four-eyes is Iris?
Talk about a downer.
Downer
To think I was so happy to bust my butt
making a game out of your scenario.
Is this really a good idea?
It's huge! Is all of this all their house?
It's so big!
Wait. Don't you live in one of these, too?
Oh, no. This place is at least
five times bigger than my house.
But you're probably loaded, right?
You know, with maids and everything.
We've only got the one that comes in.
She really does...
The Young Miss has been expecting you.
This way, please.
Th-thank you!
Beg your pardon!
It's an estate on the inside, too...
O-of course it is!
Honda-san and... Is this
a senpai from your club?
Were you worried about Minaha?
I appreciate that.
I do hope your school companions
don't mind me taking down their address
so I can contact their homes.
I'm Ayame Seki.
You can leave now, Tayama-san.
You deal with that a lot
in an old house like this.
You don't say...
I was hoping Minaha could
spend a little time relaxing.
Have a seat, Minaha.
Every time someone's gotten
on your case about you
missing curfew or your grades,
I've calmed them down.
In my own way, that is.
Abiding by the household rules and customs.
A bit old fashioned, isn't it?
But these past few weeks
you've been coming home even later.
You're out wandering around all weekend,
staying up all hours of the night.
Your grades are slipping,
and I can't even keep up.
And yesterday was a mess.
Grandmother looked ready to hit the roof.
Minaha, isn't there something you want to
tell Honda-san and your senpai?
I'm sorry.
Look at people when you apologize!
Honestly...
Why are you so stubborn over
some drawings and a club?
Isn't that right, Honda-san?
Pros do it as their job,
and you aren't even trying to be a pro.
Listen! I always wanted to-
I've heard it all before, Minaha.
You want to make a game
out of that story you like so much.
Shouldn't you be over it by now?
I mean, plenty of people
out there draw as a hobby.
So you're saying it doesn't
matter who does the art?!
That there aren't things
that only I can draw?
Sounds like you're full of yourself to me.
Everybody makes stuff
that only they can make.
The same goes for Honda-san.
She's really doing a number on her.
Look at that glare! She's
going to let loose on me!
Get it? The world's not going to end
just because you didn't do a little art.
You need to think a little more about
how you look as the youngest
daughter of the Iino family.
Lots of people draw as a hobby...
and there are a lot of
people better than me...
and you'd be full of yourself if you think
there's something only you can do...
and even if I didn't, someone else would-
Wrong.
You're wrong, Sister.
And that means?
You don't make something
because you want to change things,
or because you're doing it for someone else.
You do it because it's fun.
You do it because you're alive.
Like eating or breathing.
It's your hand that writes a tale
the world's never seen before!
Who cares about what people think?
Making: That's what gives life it's meaning!
Oh my gosh, your glasses are way too dorky
for you to talk like that!
That's what makes her melt?!
Ba-dump
Wow, "making's what gives
life its meaning," eh?
Then I suppose that would make those poems
in your elementary school
anthology your bedrock?
Isn't that right?
She's good. Iino-san definitely knows
her way around these types.
These types
E-exactly! Everything I've written has
led me to be who I am today!
Very well. Tayama-san.
Ayame Seki.
This is the 78th Tsukimoto
Elementary School Anthology, is it not?
Please. Read us one of your prized works.
No need to be shy.
What are you, in cahoots?!
"I'd hear your voice one day.
I could swear it floated through the window...
Time kept in the creep of the rust,
searching on and on for my retrospective.
Gazing at a night sky that almost seems
to wither, singing and singing.
An empty voice without an echo.
Seeing nothing and nothing.
Hearing nothing, reaching nothing.
An insensible sign ringing through a town
warped by nihilism, shivering and then gone.
Oh, gosh... What's this
feeling welling up in me?
Ah, my hand is here if
only I could reach it...
Don't tell me Spectacle's poem
is making me feel something?
Ah, my hand is here if
only I could reach it...
No! I'm supposed to be Iris'...
An eternity of isolation, ringing onward."
She really loves your writing
doesn't she, Seki-senpai...
An eternity of isolation, ringing onward."
She really loves your writing
doesn't she, Seki-senpai...
I want to crawl into a hole...
Don't sweat it.
Out of respect for your senpai,
I'll talk to Grandmother one more time.
Under one condition.
You and Honda-san will both
have to get a 70 average on your finals!
In everything?!
Why me?!
You did do pretty badly
on your tests, didn't you?
You don't have to choose
between a club and your studies!
Why shouldn't fellow members prove that
they can help each other to get better grades?
Not to mention it'd be easier
to convince our grandmother.
Our guestroom could certainly handle
a nice study session.
Help yourself to anything
in the refrigerator.
I'm getting déjà vu!
We'll start with the wide world of science!
Endo-sensai's a tough one, so you'd better
memorize every one of those reactions!
We're finally done with finals!
Good work!
I don't think I got a perfect score,
but a 90 wouldn't be too far out there!
Especially since I studied my butt off
at Iino-san's house!
That sure was hard, though.
Especially those last ones.
The last one? It was pretty much
straight out of the textbook...
No, the ones after that. Five and six.
Final Exam - Science
There were questions on the back?!
And how are you feeling, Tamaki Honda?
Sorry, Ha-chan. I was taking a nap.
You alright? You'd better
not go and catch a cold.
I was dreaming it was the last day of finals.
I missed the questions on the back
and my grade was so bad...
And then you got the high
score because I messed up?
Then I get forced to study again
because I just missed a score of 70?
You need to focus on your homework!
I'll get back to work.
I wanted to be finished with the poses
by the day after tomorrow.
I'll start once I'm done studying.
See you later.
Things get tough when you
have a deadline coming up.
And we've only got two weeks left.
I'm sad you can't come back
from your job this week,
but I know you're just working so hard!
I need my dose of Daddy!
What do you and your dad usually do?
You sound like a cat getting a good pet...
I forgot to hang up the phone!
The only thing I've done
these past few days is draw.
Although I was playing card games
in my living room this time last year...
Card Games
That sure was fun!
Yumine and me had such a
good time playing, too...
Hello? Ha-chan? I was working, I swear!
I was so tired of studying I ended up
reading Iris' stuff for an hour.
Sorry. I was reading something else, too.
We need to do this.
Oh, this is what I was working on before.
I couldn't even get the colors right...
I wish I could do it again.
Hey! You can't do that!
Ha-chan! Don't try to tell me you don't feel like
redoing some of your pictures sometimes!
I always feel like that!
But right now we need to move forward!
I'm so glad you understand!
Ha-chan just might make fun of me again
if I show her something like this.
I've been coloring these past few days...
What is it...
So you're saying it doesn't
matter who does the art?!
That there aren't things
that only I can draw?
Sounds like you're full of yourself to me.
That's it... I don't need to do this myself.
I'm going to take a walk, Ha-chan.
Tamaki
I shouldn't even be thinking like that.
I just can't think straight.
Who cares about what people think?
Making: That's what gives life it's meaning!
Especially when Seki-senpai said all that...
I need to go home and get to work.
But it's going to be a mix of mine
and Ha-chan's artwork, isn't it...
Maybe she'll tell me it doesn't
fit the scenario again...
Why do I even draw?
Good evening!
Got something you want to talk about?
I just can't get excited about it...
It's weird, isn't it?
I told Ha-chan we'd be ready in time
for Summer Comiket...
That I'd draw lots of pictures...
I mean, Ha-chan's the one who said
we should do the art in the first place.
I thought maybe I wouldn't have to try...
that's bad, isn't it?
Tell me how bad I am, Teru-san.
Well, you're having trouble
because you're not having fun.
Are you really drawing what
you want to draw, Tamatama-chan?
What is it you want to do?
I want...
I want my daddy...
Why aren't you my daddy, Teru-san?
That's a good question...
Tamatama-chan, how much
do you love your daddy?
I love him a whole bunch!
He always had these manga with old men
in his study that I loved reading...
I tried copying them,
but none of them were as cool as him!
That's what I thought when I drew...
I wanted to draw an old
guy as cool as my daddy!
Did I just say that out loud?!
Well, there you go! Now
you know why you draw!
You just need to chase that feeling!
Thank you so much!
I feel so much better! I
really think I can draw now!
A cool older guy, just like my daddy!
Daddy?!
Oh, it's you Ha-chan.
Hold on. You don't even care that I'm here?
Do you have any idea what
I went through to get here?
It's the last stop on the train!
Thank you so much for coming!
That sounded a little forced!
Sorry about before.
Kind of feels like I was rushing you...
Oh, no...
And I didn't even give you
a proper thank you for before.
Before?
Well, thanks.
You helped me with my finals
and with making the game...
It made me happy.
I'm the one who needed help studying.
I should be thanking you, Ha-chan.
Tamaki Honda...
I'm going to draw me some older men!
Older men?!
Granny, I'm home!
I don't feel right quite yet.
I should draw a few more guys...
You meant right now?
Wait... What are you doing at my house?!
A little late for that.
We can work for two or three hours
and then I'll go home.
That's what I was planning
on in the first place.
What? Really?
Two heads are better than one and all that.
We can keep an eye on each other's work.
That's not what I meant.
There won't be a train back in three hours.
And today's a weekday.
You're right! You really
do live out in the sticks!
It's not the sticks!
Well, it might be...
Wh-what do I do about my curfew?
I'm going to get an earful
if I stay out again...
Well, you might be okay if you leave now.
Then what was the point of coming here?!
I could just text them...
Nah...
Maybe my sister'll cover for me.
You don't have a thing to worry about!
I've prepared myself to stay out today!
Why did you come in through the window?!
That's what you're worried about?!
Oh, who even cares!
It's a message from Iris the Divine!
And now she's a goddess...
A message telling us to work our butts off
while in this house!
We'll make it in time for
Summer Comiket, Tamaki Honda!
Yeah!
The way things are going...
I should be saying, "Leave the drinks to me!"
I'd be the one who opens the fridge.
I wasn't ready for this. I'm so sorry...
You don't have to worry about that...
We've only got two weeks 'til the deadline!
Let's do this!
So Teru-senpai and Ha-chan
ended up spending the night.
And we've only got three weeks left
until Summer Comiket!
Have they reached you?
Longing gazes, standing on tiptoes
Washed away, reeling
Swimming through a sea of dreams
A lullaby
Swaying
I forgot something really important!
I didn't join this club just to draw!
I did it to make a game that
would make people smile!
Back to the Start