Tama-chan!
The school's pretty far away!
We need to get going!
Just a sec!
Sorry for the hold up...
What's with you, Yumine?
No good! Try again!
Tama-chan...
We're supposed to be high
school students now.
Don't you think your uniform
should fit better than that?
Well, Granny said I should get me
a big one since I'll be growin' like a weed.
And no provincialisms.
Standard Japanese only!
But...
O-okay...
I get it, though. These
uniforms are pretty expensive.
Me, I went to this school
for junior high, too.
But you went to a school out
in the boonies, Tama-chan.
You've got some high hurdles to jump.
I ain't no hayseed!
There goes your accent again!
Okay...
My name is Tamaki Honda, and today's
our high school entrance ceremony.
Hoshi no Tsuji Academy.
It's a private junior and senior high school.
Its open atmosphere means
it has a lot of active clubs.
It's made them pretty famous.
Once today's ceremony is over,
there'll be an event where the clubs have
stands and whatnot to get new members.
The school's right in the middle of the city.
It's not like my junior high at all,
so I think it'll take some getting used to.
Look. We're here, Tama-chan!
Hoshi no Tsuji
Junior and Senior High School
2016 Entrance Ceremony
Hoshi no Tsuji
Junior and Senior High School
Let's find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
Because there's a world where
only love will carry on
Left all alone like that
But you still can't leave it be
Yes or no, it's always hiding
If you could say it was okay
You could think it was okay
Strange that it was just that quick
The feeling of chasing this kind of thrill
Will be more than you could
have imagined yesterday
Hello, make my day
The magic that we all hold
You'll see the greatest
something of your life
We'll find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
There's a world waiting where
only love will carry on
The Starting Line
We're done with the ceremony and homeroom,
so now it's time to check
out the clubs' PR event.
I've waited so long for this day,
to join up with a nice club.
Dance | Club | Table Tennis | Volleyball
I'm looking for something
that'll really draw me in,
but I don't know what that is yet.
Our first PR event, huh?
I wonder what the new blood is like.
I thought you had a shift with
the Desktop Music Club, Fujikawa.
Well, yeah. But this is important, too.
I'm hoping we get a good artist!
An aspiring voice actor would be nice, too!
I don't think it'll be that easy...
That reminds me. Mind wearing this?
Only the club captain wears that.
That's not true. And starting
today, the captain is...
Oh, that's right.
Done. We need to hurry.
Break a leg, Ms. New Captain!
Tea
Ceremony
Club
There sure are a lot of clubs here!
I wish I could've seen more,
but it's getting a bit late...
I understand. Starting a new club
here is so very easy.
Wow! This green tea is something else!
I'm glad to hear it.
It's so good!
Hey there, Tama-chan!
Yumine!
Track Team
So, found a good club yet?
Not yet.
There are so many,
and I have to talk with all of them...
Oh my. Well, I joined the Illustration Club.
Didn't know they had one of those.
Have you thought about what
kind of club you want to join?
Mmm... I'm not sure.
I want to find something that grabs me
like it's my divine calling.
It's nothing to worry about.
You'll find something for sure!
SNS
Club
Anyway...
They've got all sorts of clubs, don't they?
The smiles of youth are so bright...
Calm down, Shii!
I promise I'll reflect on why
I kept you up all night.
SNS
Club
Excuse me, what kind of club is this?
Oh!
Well, uh...
Our club makes doujin games.
You can even play something we've made.
Doujin...
Note: "Doujin" means fan-made media.
You make games yourselves?
That's amazing!
What's a doujin game?
It's nothing fancy, but we have
a promo video for it right here.
The computer froze!
Sorry! I'll restart it!
The tea! It's gonna get on the computer!
Calm down, please!
It's a puzzle game?
The graphics are so cute.
Do you mind if we play?
Go ahead.
My stomach's doing flips.
Maybe I should just leave...
Um, guess I need to pick a character.
You can start first, Tama-chan.
Thanks, Yumine.
How adorable!
I think I just got inspiration
for my next script!
Bwehehehe
Try smiling a little less creepily, Aya.
They're already throwing bad guys at us!
Oh, it's giving us control cues!
I wonder if the tutorial is any good.
I tried hard to get all the bugs out.
There's a real trick to
moving the balls around.
This is pretty cerebral!
Yes, my little kittens,
become enamored with my story!
It's just a puzzle game, right?
We got it!
My heart was pumping like crazy,
but it sure was a rush when it disappeared!
Aren't they cute... Nothing
quite like newbies.
That wasn't what you were
saying before, Shii...
But it is nice...
Aw, we ran out of time.
We almost had it cleared.
If I hadn't messed up...
Sorry for getting all excited!
No way. That's what makes it all worth it.
Well, you sure put your
hearts and souls into it.
It's hard to believe a club made it.
Thank you very much.
It's true! I got a game called Hoyofuyo once
and it was just like that!
It reminded me of how into it I was...
Was that your inspiration for this one?
You could say that.
We based it on rules that are
pretty common for action puzzle games,
so it was bound to show
up in there somewhere.
And I kind of knew what I was doing...
Shii! Snap out of it!
Huh? Did I say something wrong?!
And both of you made it?
Made it we did!
We've got two more people
on our team, though.
Check out the jacket!
So how do you make them?
We do the artwork, scripts,
and music on the computer.
A young man is washing himself
in the river one day when a boss
comes from upstream!
From the river, a girl...
And we start putting them together
into a proper game format.
It's like we all come together to
make the world of the game.
It's super fun!
So you use computers...
I like to draw, but I haven't
done much digital stuff...
No way, you just have to
ease yourself into it!
It's tough.
Huh?
Erm...
It's tough.
I'm sorry, I don't think
I can join your club.
I'm probably going to be busy
with the Illustration Club.
What about you, Tama-chan?
I remember how much you liked to draw.
A little back in elementary school, is all.
I don't know much about
drawing with computers,
and I don't think I could
make stuff for a game like this...
It's not that big a deal, honestly.
Why does she look so serious?
Well, I guess we'll get going.
Sure. Thanks for stopping by.
Basketball Team
Those new students were so adorable!
You're telling me!
I can't believe it's over already.
Maybe I should just join
the Tea Ceremony Club.
The captain was such a sweetheart...
Maybe you could join
the Illustration Club with me.
I sat in with them and it seemed really relaxed.
I think it might be a nice place to draw in.
That game sure was fun, though.
So sparkly and cute...
They're all super serious about making games.
Not like me...
What the heck do I want to do, anyway?
Junior High Third Year
Card Games
Get really into card games and
study a lot about single player games...
Junior High Second Year
Reading
Sit on the riverbank watching the clouds
and blowing through the classics...
Junior High First Year
Tracing
Spend pretty much all
my time copying manga...
Elementary Fifth Year
Manga
Go into the closet and get
lost in a nice manga...
Elementary Third Year
Doodling
See how good I could
doodle in my textbooks...
Elementary First Year
Bug Catching
Catch bugs and study them on my porch...
Why can't I just stick to a hobby?!
What the heck am I supposed to do?
Hey!
SUPER SUGOROKU
GOAL
Prize:
1,000,000 yen
Look, Grandma!
Did you make yourself a board game today?
You're something else when it comes to
making games, aren't you?
When I'm an elementary schooler,
me and my friends are gonna play lots of 'em!
I bet you will.
Lots of games for a sweetie pie like you!
I remember now.
That's how Yumine and I got to be friends...
I made a new game for today!
Hey!
I said "Hey," Tama-chan!
Thinking of games...
That means...
What's going on with you?
Sorry, Yumine! You can go on ahead!
Tama-chan!
There they are!
Oh, is that a first year?
Um...
The name's Fujikawa.
I'm a second year with the club.
That and the sound director
for this puzzle game.
Did you get to play it?
The music...
Well, I was just so into
the game I didn't really...
Oh. I guess I get it.
Background music doesn't exactly stick out...
Not like there're many people who'd notice
how much work somebody put into a bass line.
I'm so sorry! I didn't mean it that way...
Oh, I'm pulling your leg!
Making a game where nothing sticks out
means the sound person's done their job!
So why'd you come back?
Well, I really liked the art.
Plus it got me interested in making games...
I don't know if I'd be a good artist,
but maybe the person who did it could teach me.
And then maybe I could do it, too.
She's not here anymore.
What?
She put this club together a year ago.
She pulled us in and this puzzle game
was our debut project.
She did the art, the planning,
and managed it all by herself.
She really was amazing.
But then she graduated.
So that left the three of us...
Without an artist or
anyone who wanted to be a leader.
We're kind of up the creek here.
You said you don't have an artist?
We thought maybe one of the
new students could be one...
But we didn't get a single new member...
But it's the first day of the new semester!
The game hasn't even started yet!
Well I...
I'll be your new member!
Oh! Please and thank you!
And I promise I'll learn
how to use a computer!
Really? That means so much! Thanks!
So, do you draw?
Have you done illustrations before?
I've traced manga before.
But I thought I'd like to try
making a game if you'd let me...
Well, you're more than welcome!
Why don't you draw something now?
And that's what she draws!
Does it look weird?
I haven't sketched for a while.
Ah. Well I think it's pretty good...
Thank you so much!
I'm Tamaki Honda, and
I'm going to make games!
So you ended up joining
the game club, Tama-chan?
Yup. They didn't have anyone who could draw,
so I thought maybe they could take me.
Well look at you!
And they're already meeting up today.
I wonder what they get up to
at a game making meeting.
It seems so cool!
Are you going to the
Illustrator's Club, Yumine?
Yeah, we have to do introductions today.
Don't you get nervous when you
show your art to other people?
Well, yeah.
But one of the art seniors got his tea drunk
by this kinda cute guy next to him...
And he looked super embarrassed about it.
The day has come at last, Shii!
Oh, how long our club has waited for this!
You know the semester's just started, right?
They put a new flavor on sale.
It's a nice little bit of chaos,
the mixing of these two mundane flavors.
Matcha Tea
Pudding
Lemonade
It's such simple stimuli that free us
from the humdrum, wouldn't you say?
Whatever. Could you just drink it, already?
SNS
Club
Well, newbie! How about
you introduce yourself?
Welcome, newbie!
We're glad you're here!
Y-yes, ma'am!
I'm Tamaki Honda and I'm a first year!
I still have a lot to learn about making
games and art, but I'm glad to be here!
Oh, and I brought this...
Granny said I ought to greet people properly
when I get to my new place.
Wow...
Well, well.
How is it?
It's good.
Super tasty.
It's so flavorful. That's some good kinpira.
Note: Kinpira is a dish generally made out
of chopped burdock and carrot sautéed
in soy sauce and sugar.
This is good and all, but is this
what our club should be doing?
Anyway, we're glad to have you.
The Captain's up next.
I'm Shiina Murakami, second year.
I'm our programmer.
I'm glad to meet you, Ms. Captain.
It feels like I just barged into the club-
No way! That kind of energy is great
when you're making something!
Well when I saw how serious you were,
it really made me think how much
I wanted to make games with you.
Is that how I looked?
I believe I was thinking of
how best to punish a certain script writer
who'd gone crazy the previous night.
Gone crazy?
I got a call in the dead of night telling me
how we need to add a secret boss to our demo.
Well, I just thought it
might not be hard enough
for any veteran players who
stopped by our club for the event.
My job being only to adjust the values of the AI,
I figured we'd be able to manage something.
And yet the one who proposed
this idea in the first place
decided she wanted to play another game...
Wait! That wasn't just playing!
I thought it'd be good
to study a classic RPG!
I think I might want to
stay on her good side...
So, when did you get to sleep?
5:00.
Well, there we go!
I'm the script supervisor,
second year Ayame Seki.
I'm a second year, too.
Background music and
SFX director Kayo Fujikawa.
It's so nice to meet you!
Same here!
Something wrong?
It's just, you all can do such amazing stuff.
In this club, the...
The Slack-eyed Night-owl
Shuttle-runners Club.
Wha...?
The Slack-eyed Night-owl
Shuttle-runners Club.
It's not exactly a story
you can tell in one night.
Now, about where we go from here...
Last year, we managed to make a single puzzle game
at the behest of our founder and senior member.
But being that she's no longer here,
and us being amateurs,
I think it would be best to start with
a small plan and step up from there.
Hmm?
And I've cooked up a new
scenario just for today...
Planning Sheet
Consider me the leader of
the SNS Club's second project!
Leader? You?
You sure you can handle it?
I... I'm feeling kind of hurt, here.
I see. You want to do a
spin-off of the puzzle game.
E-exactly. I thought we could do
a short, simple visual novel.
And I could make the music arrangements
out of stuff from the old game.
That could be good!
Oh, isn't this so exciting?
And you'll be doing the art, Honda-san.
Oh! Well, then...
I'll have to use a computer... won't I?
That's right.
But if it doesn't work
out, it doesn't work out.
Character poses and variations,
UI design, stills...
You'll be in charge of making all of that.
And, because this is a group project,
you'll have deadlines to meet.
Maybe you could ease up
on the pressure, Murakami.
I don't want to force anyone into this.
Making a game is hard work.
She's right. It's probably
going to be hard...
I can't even picture what it's like to make
art for a game, so maybe I can't do it.
But I...
I don't want to spend any
more time without a plan!
I want to make the games I can make!
I...
I can do this!
I like the sound of that, Honda-chan!
Everything will be fine!
S-sure!
Our New Plan
- Deadlines
- Volume
- Scheduling
I'd like to go over our schedule once again.
Now, while we have any number of
doujin fairs to choose from...
We'll be aiming for Summer Comiket.
"Summer Comiket"?
It's a really large doujin event
held during summer break.
And our goal is to join it
with our newly finished game.
Yeah. That could work.
We'll be flirting with disaster
with such a hard schedule.
Oh, yeah.
I wanted to give you this.
This is the game you made!
But you don't have to
base the art off of that.
What we want is a game
with your personal touch.
My touch?
I should probably try to get
a song done by tomorrow.
Wha...? You can make music that fast?
I should do something, too-
Slow down! You're making me feel pressured!
Think you could've gone a
little easier on her, Shii?
Honda-san's probably going to
have a lot more work to do...
If she can't keep up and
ends up keeling over...
I...
I get it. But let's keep
our eyes on the prize.
I haven't seen you that
excited in a long time, Shii.
What, me?
You might be right.
Maybe because we've never had
a junior member before.
There'll be failures and setbacks along the way,
but we can get there with the four of us!
And I'll be hard at work, too.
Right, Captain?
Thanks, Aya.
I feel a little better now.
Consider this a thank you.
I told you to keep that to yourself!
New Game
Continue
Options
Help
You're up drawing at this hour, Tamaki?
Grandma!
Shut off that TV and get some sleep!
Okay. Good night.
So, what now?
I guess this looks pretty good for a copy...
"What we want is a game
with your personal touch."
All right, just one more!
I think I know what I want to do now!
Have they reached you?
Longing gazes, standing on tiptoes
Washed away, reeling
Swimming through a sea of dreams
A lullaby
Swaying
Behold, the evening dew upon the leontochir!
Please stop with the names.
I thought maybe there's
some room for an older man.
Drawing with a face like that, I figured that
our characters would look all happy...
You're the one who drew
the pictures, Tama-chan.
A Fun Production