SNS
Club
Seven days 'til Summer Comiket!
It may be summer break,
but the SNS Club is working full shifts.
Some days it's at someone's house,
Do it again! Are you even trying?!
What's wrong with it?
some days it's in the club room.
Right here! Where's the love?! Do it again!
And sometimes there are creative differences...
QUIET, four-eyes!
Ha-chan still hasn't figured out
Seki-senpai is the great Iris...
Fujikawa-senpai keeps getting lost
in her own little world...
We've got a lot going on,
but with the Captain managing the schedule,
we're somehow making progress.
Iino-san
Cover art
Honda-san
Main characters…           TWO DAYS 'til Summer Comiket!
Seki
Debugging
Fujikawa
One song left
-Distance-
Stardust Desires
Slack-eyed Night-owl Shuttle-runners Club
And before I knew it, our game
Stardust Desires was finished!
Back To The Start
Love you, Daddy...
Well, look who's slumbering peacefully?!
We've got Summer Comiket today!
Ha..Ha-chan...
You know we're supposed to help
Temawari-san's group this afternoon, right?
Hop to it!
Oh, my... You're leaving
when you just got here?
Yes, Ma'am! Thank you!
See you later!
Be careful, now.
All that fuss? Must be a club day.
So long as she's enjoying herself.
Too true.
Tamaki in the morning... Wait'll
her father sees this...
This is nice!
I always wanted to come to
the convention center by boat!
...And what's that for?
I'm not good with crowds, so
I brought a full-body suit...
What's it say?
It's from Ha-chan-san.
She snatched up Honda-san and
they're on their way to the center now.
So we're all going to meet up later, right?
And why do you look dead on your feet?
Someone I know suddenly
wanted to make a CD...
I've been helping and managing and mixing
and mastering the whole thing...
So you were working on
something else besides this?
Our senpai are already on
their way to the center!
I called and called and you're
the only one who didn't pick up,
so I had to come get you!
I'm sorry, I forgot to set my alarm...
And I had a heck of a time getting grandmother
to let us use the car.
Thank you, Iino-san. You didn't have to...
Have to what? I've been wanting to
go to one of these conventions.
You know, see what Minaha's
gotten herself all worked up over.
Wait. Are you coming to the center with us?
We'll be taking the freeway.
It's bound to be faster than a train.
We're getting out here?
Right! You can't just park anywhere
in front of the center.
Thank you so much! We'll be going now!
Eyes on the prize, now.
Are all these people here
for Summer Comiket?!
This is just the tip of the iceberg.
There are a lot more inside.
Oh, yeah, Murakami-senpai said to be
careful we don't get separated...
Guess I could hold your hand or something...
Someone tell me why I have to see
YOU on Comiket, of all days?!
Why don't you tell me why you're here?!
They aren't exactly friendly, are they...
We're selling stuff today, aren't we?
Right. And since we'll be with the group,
it should be a real learning experience.
You're an artist, so you'd better go out there
and get some inspiration.
I got plenty at the last convention...
They're really good, aren't they?
These are the seasoned ranks
of Comiket soldiers...
Feels like I might get lost...
You can walk around and look at other booths,
but don't forget you're a
participant and not a guest.
Not everyone here is a professional.
Read this!
I want
to draw
Comiket
The most important thing is to enjoy
the festivities along with everyone else!
Like someone who's going to spend
all her time gabbing about boy's
love with the Illustration Club?
This relationship between
the main character and his
best friend is way beyond platonic!
So not everyone thinks
that way, but it's true!
You could at least be respectful!
So this is a doujin convention...
Certainly more people than I expected.
An event where people buy and sell
self-published manga and novels...
Or so I've been told.
Wonder if it's worth spending weeks of
your youth on like Minaha does...
But of course, Big Sis!
I could show you around if you'd like!
And who might you be?
Now where are they...
Don't get lost now, Tamaki Honda.
Why don't we go around this way?
A World
Nobody Knows
Hold on, this is BL Island!
And it's the hardcore stuff!
It's not like we don't have time!
Just look at how innocent she is!
Have you no shame?!
Well, it'd be so nice if I could get
Tama-chan interested in BL-
You fiend!
But they're all such good artists...
Maybe I could learn a thing or two...
Not that I know where I'm supposed to look...
Tama-chan!
Yes?
Feel free to look.
300 yen
a copy!
Do you mind if I look?
Er... sure!
Well, then...
Is she in high school?
Our new stuff isn't exactly wholesome...
Find something you like, Tama-chan?
Well, the old guy on the
cover was just so cool...
If that's how you feel, you
should let the group know!
Oh...
Can I buy one?
Sure!
That'll be 2,500 yen, please!
I absolutely love your work! This is for you!
Thank you so much!
That girl looked so happy...
Maybe I looked that way
at the last convention...
Honda-chan!
Maybe I looked that way at the last convention...
That sounds like Fujikawa-senpai...
Over here! Hurry, Honda-chan!
Would you look at that line?!
There you are, Honda-san!
We need all hands on deck! Hurry up!
And would you mind putting
on these rabbit ears?
Did you bring these for me to wear?!
Hm? Where's Murakami-senpai?
Right here.
Would you take that thing off already?!
I'm wearing it until I adjust.
It's our game...
You can get sentimental later!
These are the new albums
and these are the free CDs!
And this is the stuff we got consigned
from other groups! Got it?
Got it!
Now let's get to work!
Alright!
I'll take three of the new album!
R-right away!
That'll be 2,100 yen! And
you get this for free...
I'll take a new album
and the one before that.
The new album and the one before!
Now which one was that?
It's so busy my head is spinning!
It's better than doing sales.
We're supposed to switch off, though.
That means you'll be up there later.
West-A 18
Suisan Temawari
End of Line
New Albums
Choose from three at 1,000 yen each
Comes with a free CD
(a present for customers who purchase
two or more of the above items)
Music Scores I and II
500 yen each
Sold out
I'll take the new album... and this and this.
I'll take two of each CD!
Um...
Hello!
Is Temawari-san here today?
I'm a huge fan and I
wanted them to have this.
Thank you very much!
And people buy you things like this!
We finally get a breather...
Tama-chan! Got a minute?
Oh, sure. We're on break right now.
Wait!
Marika-san?
I always wanted to get myself
down to Summer Comiket!
Not to mention I wanted to see you!
She surprised me, too.
And I bought this!
Thanks!
And a whole bunch of cute figurines!
A girl could get into this
whole Summer Comiket thing!
That sure is a lot...
Did you buy one of the
group's new CDs, Yumine?
Sure did! And I got an autograph!
Sounds nice!
So how many copies did we sell?
Looks like a whole bunch.
It might be a new record.
Maybe one day we'll make something
good enough to get a line like that on our own.
On our own...
Ow!
Get your head out of the clouds!
What am I supposed to do
with a co-artist like you?!
Sorry, I was just thinking.
Excuse me...
Yes?
You were at the convention in June...
You remember me!
I looked at your homepage and
it said you were selling here today...
so I made my way down!
So did you buy our new game?
Well, I was just about to...
We've got a demo you can try out if you want!
Stardust Desires
-Distance-
New Game
Continue
Options
Stardust Desires
-Distance-
New Game
Continue
Options
The artwork is just as good as before!
I'm glad you think so!
Did you do it all by yourself this time, too?
No, Ha-chan and I both did it together.
She decided on what kind of art
and where it would go,
what kind of game we should make...
What kind of music it should have, all of it.
That's amazing! You're a real leader!
Oh, no... Leader... It wasn't
all that big a deal, really...
But picking Iris' story, telling us which art
went where... didn't you do all of that?
That's right! She's a real go-getter!
That she is!
I don't think it would be out of place
to call her our leader on the project.
Right?
Well, I can just tell I'm
going to have fun playing it.
Sure! Thank you so much!
Sure looks like they're enjoying themselves.
You could've gone inside instead of
staying all the way out here, you know.
No way. I could never be like those people.
It was Teru Hyakutake, wasn't it?
Getting an invitation from such a famous
school figure has certainly piqued my interest.
I'm more interested in why your family
carries around spy gear, Miss Squint...
Oh, never mind that.
Well, considering how excited she was,
I thought Tamatama-chan
needed a lighter touch...
I'd heard that you'd poked your
nose in at various points.
Though I greatly prefer to live
the more settled life, myself...
But what about just a little?
I mean, you're only young once!
You need to take the youth they have right now
and really make them run with it...
If you say so.
I suppose I'll allow it.
They do look like they're having fun.
And so our Summer Comiket came to an end.
For some reason, I felt something
I couldn't quite put my finger on...
But then I figured out why...
It was a while after the convention.
We decided to go to the beach to celebrate...
You get out there, Murakami-san!
I don't want to! I'm going home!
That suit looks good on you, Captain!
Good thing we went to all those stores!
You're not going to spurn the
ensemble your kouhai picked
out for you and run away, are you?
Well, I'm sorry I don't have your
can-do attitude, Fujikawa-san!
I know what I'm doing is all an act,
but what's wrong with faking
it 'til you make it?
Maybe you could try doing what
Fujikawa-senpai does, Captain?
I-I guess I can, maybe... I can do it.
You really do take charge, Tama-chan!
When did you get here?
Here goes!
There!
Feel that sun eh, Murakami-san?
Now that's what I call a return!
Captain?!
Are you okay?!
I've done enough communication
for one lifetime.
I'll never talk again.
What?!
Celebrate?
Yup, and you should come!
You made the game with us, and we're friends!
I sure don't remember
making friends with you!
We're rivals and that's it!
It's not like I'm an official
member of the SNS Club!
Like I want to mingle with you!
So you're not coming?
Well... um...
I get it... It's too bad, but
if that's how you feel...
Wait just a...
I didn't say I wasn't
going! I didn't say that!
A swimsuit is meant for swimming, Young Miss.
Well this is my underwear!
Looking good!
Over here?
I've been meaning to ask...
We went shopping together...
Why are you wearing your school swimsuit?
I was short on funds...
Hold on. Yumine Fuda isn't
even in the SNS Club!
Young Miss? It wouldn't do to hang back here
if you really want to go.
Honestly, you're acting
like a bit of a stalker.
You're one to talk!
I want to take a break.
I'm feeling a bit overheated...
Could be a bit of heatstroke.
We could go to those rocks over there.
It'll be cooler in the shade, definitely.
I'll go and buy some drinks.
What is it?
I just thought of a new game!
What kind of game?
Tell us!
It's cops-and-robbers mixed with hopscotch!
You have to hop away from the cop!
That sounds fun!
Let's play it!
Okay! Everybody draw a circle in the sand!
One, two, three! One, two, three!
Wait up!
I know this...
Honda-san! Over here!
Welcome back! Thanks, Tama-chan.
How are you, Captain?
A little break is all I needed.
Sorry for making you fuss over me.
We were worried about what
was taking you so long.
I'm sorry...
You okay, Honda-chan?
I...
I'm not okay!
I forgot something really important!
I didn't join this club just to draw!
I did it to make a game that would
make people smile!
Well, I guess the Art and Illustration Clubs
are there for you if had just wanted to draw.
What is it you want to do, Honda-chan?
Well, I... I want to come up
with my own idea for a game!
Let's find it, make my day
Thank you me for being clumsy
Just like Ha-chan did!
Because there's a world where
only love will carry on
But I can't do it by myself...
So I was thinking maybe you could help me...
I've been waiting to hear that!
I'd love to see what kind
of game you could make!
You joining the SNS Club is the reason
we were able to make two new games.
Left all alone like that
Now it's time for us to support you.
But you still can't leave it be
Yes or no, it's always hiding
Oh, Captain...
Then I'm going to make a game
with tons and tons of wonderful old guys!
If you could say it was okay
Of course she is!
And oh... the Winter Comiket application
deadline is tomorrow. Are you okay?
You could think it was okay
Strange that it was just that quick
I completely forgot!
Winter Comiket! So that's next!
The feeling of chasing this kind of thrill
Yup, at the end of the year.
I also have to do the cultural festival.
Will be more than you could
have imagined yesterday
But Winter Comiket's the next big event.
Who knows if we'll get in, though.
Alright, then! Starting next semester...
Hello, make my day
No, starting tomorrow...
The magic that we all hold
No, starting today I'm going to
work on my next game!
You'll see the greatest
something of your life
The girl's on fire!
Good stuff! Sounds like it's
time for a dev meeting!
We'll find it, make my day
Ideas, scheduling, we have a lot to do.
Thank you me for being clumsy
There's a world waiting where
only love will carry on
We're going to be busy, Honda-san.
Yes, Ma'am!
I'm going to work hard!
I got it!
Mizutama moyou no sora ni
In the polka dotted sky
Masshiroi kumo ga ukanderu
Bright white clouds are floating,
Oudan hodou no sutoraipu
The stripes on a crosswalk
Acchi koccho ittari kitari
Coming and going here and there
Socchi kocchi nobotte orite
Climbing up and down here and there
Kyou mo furidashi ni modottari shite
And today and I’m right back at the start again
Mae mukitai no ni mae ga wakaranai
Wanting to face forward but not knowing where forward is
Dame nante iwanai de umaretate no kouya e
Don’t say it’s impossible, just go toward the newborn wilds
Yoroshiku ne make my day
Let’s get along, make my day
Mawarimichi shite mo ii yo ne
It’s okay to take a detour
Nakibeso mo mato hazure mo oome ni mite ne
Tearing up, a missed target, it’s okay to let it pass
Mitsukeyou make my day
Let's find it, make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Thank you me for being clumsy
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga aru no sa
Because there's a world where only love will carry on
Dare mo minna hoshi ni narerun da
Anyone and everyone can be a star
Kizuite inai kedo kagayakerun da
Unaware that they’re shining
Kokoro no netsu moyashitsuzuketa nara
If you kept that fire in your heart burning
Itsu no hi ka hikari o hanatsu koto ga dekiru yo kitto
Someday that light will shine forth, count on it
Next Game
1st Meeting
Konnichiwa make my day
Hello, make my day
Minna ga motteru mahou
The magic that we all hold
SNS Club
New game for Winter Comiket
Isshou de ichiban no nani ka ga mieru
You'll see the greatest something of your life
Deaeru yo make my day
We'll find it, make my day
Bukiyou de arigatou watashi
Thank you me for being clumsy
Daisuki dake ga tsureteku sekai ga matteru
There's a world waiting where only love will carry on
Fall Semester